<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>Snap Hutao</title>
    <link>https://hut.ao/en/</link>
    <description>Super utilitarian Genshin Impact Toolkit</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:04:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>@vuepress/plugin-feed</generator>
    <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
    <category>Feature</category>
    <category>Tutorial</category>
    <category>open source</category>
    <category>development</category>
    <category>Dev Logs</category>
    <category>Announcement</category>
    <category>FAQ</category>
    <category>i18n</category>
    <category>Third-Party Tools</category>
    <category>announcement</category>
    <category>project</category>
    <category>features</category>
    <item>
      <title>ðŸŽ‰ Successfully Updated to Version 1.12.8</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/latest.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/latest.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">ðŸŽ‰ Successfully Updated to Version 1.12.8</source>
      <description>ðŸŽ‰ Successfully Updated to Version 1.12.8 | English [ðŸŽ‰New] Added keyboard F key auto-press feature, which can be enabled and configured in the settings page [ðŸ”¨Fix] Fixed an is...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:54:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/zh/statements/latest.html" target="_blank">ç®€ä½“ä¸­æ–‡</a> | <strong>English</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added keyboard F key auto-press feature, which can be enabled and configured in the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program would crash when entering the game launch page without having any game path</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support us</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/support-us.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/support-us.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Support us</source>
      <description>The Snap Hutao project accepts donations from the community to keep the project operations, and we sincerely thank everyone who has supported this project.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:13:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao, as an open-source project licensed under the MIT License, is dedicated to creating a completely free, ad-free, and privacy-focused program. The members of our development team are currently self-funding the project's operation. We used modern software to reduce our operation costs, with the main expenses being the network system components required by server (you can find our annual expenditure summary below on this page). If you have surplus funds to support Snap Hutao, your generous donation will not only assist the development team but also benefit every Snap Hutao user. Currently, you can donate us in the following ways:</p>
<h2>Donation</h2>
<p>We accept sponsorship with following methods:</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/support-us.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feedback Center</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/feedback-center.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/feedback-center.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Feedback Center</source>
      <description>The built-in Feedback Center in Snap Hutao includes important links related to the Snap Hutao project and incorporates a document search engine. This enables players to resolve common issues and find solutions within the program itself.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:46:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01oOYqZC1g6e0rgyJ3G_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="dashboard" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The Feedback Center is a feature page provided by the Snap Hutao development team to help users solve common problems. This page is laid out in a left-right structure.</p>
<p>On the left side of the page, we provide a convenient entry point for searching Snap Hutao documents. You can get relevant page search results by entering keywords in the search box.</p>
<p>On the right side of the page, we provide several useful features.</p>
<ul>
<li>The first part displays key information about Snap Hutao, including the version of Snap Hutao, device ID, device network information, and Webview 2 runtime version information.</li>
<li>The second part includes links to Snap Hutao project issues, roadmap, and service availability monitoring.</li>
<li>The third part includes documents of the main functions of Snap Hutao. You can click on the corresponding function to jump to the corresponding document page.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01oOYqZC1g6e0rgyJ3G_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snap Hutao Account</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-passport.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-passport.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Snap Hutao Account</source>
      <description>The Hutao Passport is the account system under the Snap Hutao project, which allows players to log in to the Hutao Cloud system and access benefits.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:46:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote>
<p>Hutao Passport is the internal name of Snap Hutao Account, they are the same thing</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Snap Hutao account is an account system created by the DGP-Studio team to serve Snap Hutao, which will be used to provide cloud-based services in the future, including wish records synchronization.</p>
<p>If you have Hutao Cloud privileges, you will have the following permissions:</p>
<ol>
<li>The <code>Prediction</code> function in the Wish Record page</li>
<li>Cloud synchronization function of wish records</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>After your Snap Hutao account cloud synchronization permission expires, you will not be able to upload, download, and delete data, but your data will not be deleted. You can re-operate your cloud backup data after restoring privilege.</li>
</ul>
<p>Since cloud synchronization is a function that consumes Hutao server resources, this function has a time limit. Currently, Snap Hutao provides the following methods to enable the cloud synchronization function:</p>
<ol>
<li>For users who reward Hutao on Aifadian, we will automatically add usage time to the Hutao account that matches the Aifadian email account as a thank you from the Hutao Toolbox development team to the reward users.</li>
<li>For all registered users, after successfully uploading the Spiral Abyss challenge record to the Hutao database for the first time in each schedule, they will get 3 days of privilege time.
<ul>
<li>You can use Hutao Cloud for free for a long time through this method.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Users who contribute to the Snap Hutao open source community (including but not limited to code development, program UI design, localization translation) can directly contact the development team to obtain a developer license.
<ul>
<li>We are currently designing a complete and automated developer license issuance process, which will be launched with the improvement of the Hutao account system.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join the Develop Team</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/join.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/join.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Join the Develop Team</source>
      <description>If you possess expertise in any of the technologies mentioned on this page and are interested in joining the Snap Hutao development team to enhance the project and engage with more open-source projects related to Genshin Impact, we welcome you to join us!</description>
      <category>open source</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you have one of the following experiences and are interested in joining the Snap Hutao development team to improve this project and get in touch with more Genshin Impact open source projects, welcome to join us!</p>
<p><strong>We will not set any specific skill requirement. Willingness to explore new areas, passion for technology and responsible attitude are more important to the open source community.</strong></p>
<blockquote>
<p>Too busy? Just wanna give a quick fix to issue you faced? Check the <a href="/en/development/contribute.html" target="_blank">contribution manual</a> and start your Pull Request directly, we will take constructive code commits seriously.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2></h2>
<p><strong>DGP-Studio Members can</strong></p>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-0" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-0"> contribute features wanted by themselves into Snap Hutao and associated projects</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-1" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-1"> get touch with other well-known Genshin Impact community developers</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-2" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-2"> get free GitHub Copilot</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-3" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-3"> get free 1password Team account</label></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/development/join.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Logs</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/blog/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/blog/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Dev Logs</source>
      <description>Dev Logs</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 08:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/blog/version-1-9-0-breaking-changes.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/blog/version-1-9-0-breaking-changes.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0</source>
      <description>Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0 This document is applicable to users upgrading from Snap Hutao versions 1.4.11 to 1.8.4 to version 1.9.0 and higher. Introductio...</description>
      <category>Dev Logs</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 08:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This document is applicable to users upgrading from Snap Hutao versions <strong>1.4.11 to 1.8.4</strong> to version 1.9.0 and higher.</p>
<h2>Introduction</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao is a Windows sandbox application in MSIX format, providing the convenience of installation and the security of AppX applications. Mandatory code signing in installation packages is a crucial factor in ensuring security. If the installation package is modified, Windows App Installer will raise an error due to the signature being compromised, preventing user installation. We can see this practice everywhere in today's mobile operating systems. On the Windows platform, due to strict identity verification procedure, the prices of code signing certificates have remained high.</p>
<p>Before version 1.4.11, Snap Hutao used a self-signed certificate. In this mode, users had to manually install DGP-Studio's certificate to allow the installation of applications signed by DGP-Studio's certificate on their computers. Starting from version 1.4.11, Snap Hutao was listed on the Microsoft Store, and Microsoft provided a GUID <code>35C8E923-85DF-49A7-9172-B39DC6312C52</code> for Hutao's developer account. This GUID was used as the publisher name of Snap Hutao, providing a special free signature (only used for Microsoft Store apps). If you are accustomed to updating the Snap Hutao with MSIX packages, you should always see this GUID in the publisher column.</p>
<p>Listing on the Microsoft Store eliminated the need for Snap Hutao users to manually install the signing certificate and supported the distribution of Snap Hutao installation packages, reducing a significant amount of costs for the development team. However, the cumbersome approval process often disrupted the development plans of the Snap Hutao. Therefore, over the past six months, the development team has been seeking a solution. SignPath is a company based in Vienna, Austria, that provides code signing integration software. In early December 2023, the Snap Hutao development team successfully obtained sponsorship from the SignPath Foundation, allowing us to use their code signing certificates for Snap Hutao free of charge. This greatly assisted the Snap Hutao project by not only allowing the Snap Hutao to get rid of constraints of the Microsoft Store but also avoiding the high annual certificate fees.</p>
<p><strong>Due to the migration to a new certificate causing package name conflicts, Snap Hutao provides the following detailed explanation to assist all users in updating to version 1.9.0 and future versions.</strong></p>
<h2>Upgrade to Version 1.9.0</h2>
<h3>Version Release</h3>
<p>Snap Hutao version 1.9.0 is scheduled to be released on the weekend before Christmas 2023. We will publish the download links for the installation package through GitHub, Jihu GitLab, this official website, and the community.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>1.9.0 version has been released, please download from <a href="/en/quick-start.html" target="_blank">Quick Start</a> page.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3>Uninstall Old Versions</h3>
<p>Directly installing this package will cause problems depending on your system version due to package name and signature conflicts.</p>
<p>| System Version |                                                      Expected Issues                                                      |
| :</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hut.ao/images/202312/1-8-5-installer.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute Your Code</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/contribute.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/contribute.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Contribute Your Code</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao is developed using C# and the .NET framework for both the desktop client and the server. We greatly appreciate feedback from the open-source community, and if you&amp;apos;re willing to contribute your code, please refer to the instructions in the documentation on this page.</description>
      <category>open source</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 07:23:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao is using C# and .NET Framework to develop both client and server. If you are willing to contribute your code
to the project, please read the following guidelines.</p>
<p>You can find all <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues?q=is%3Aissue+is%3Aopen+-label%3A%E5%B7%B2%E4%BF%AE%E5%A4%8D+" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">unsolved opened issues</a> on GitHub</p>
<h2></h2>
<ol>
<li>Download and install <a href="https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/downloads/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Visual Studio 2022</a></li>
<li>Open Visual Studio Installer to complete Visual Studio installation
<ul>
<li>You need to install <code>.NET desktop development</code>, <code>Desktop development with C++</code> and <code>Windows application development</code> components</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Install <code>Single-project MSIX Packaging Tools for VS 2022</code> provided by Microsoft in Visual Studio marketplace</li>
<li>Use git to clone the project <code>https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.git</code> to your local device</li>
<li>Switch git branch to <code>develop</code></li>
<li>Open project solution with your Visual Studio and then you are ready to go</li>
</ol>
<h2></h2>
<ol>
<li>Download and install <code>Sysinternals Suite</code> from <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/productid/9P7KNL5RWT25" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Microsoft Store</a> or <a href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/sysinternals/downloads/sysinternals-suite" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Microsoft website</a></li>
<li>Locate and run <code>DebugView</code> program in the installed app list or unzipped folder</li>
<li>Run Snap Hutao client</li>
<li>Check DebugView output</li>
</ol>
<h2></h2>
<ul>
<li>All code-related changes from authors' own branches are only allowed be merged to <code>develop</code> branch</li>
<li>Please use <a href="https://docs.github.com/en/get-started/writing-on-github/working-with-advanced-formatting/using-keywords-in-issues-and-pull-requests" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">keywords</a> to link your PR or commits with issues, so issues can be automatically closed once commits are merged into <code>main</code> branch.</li>
</ul>
<h2></h2>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Warning</p>
<p>You need to install <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Automation/Hutao-Auto-Release/releases/download/certificate-ca/DGP_Studio_CA.crt" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DGP-Studio CA certificate</a> as <code>Trusted Root Certification Authorities</code> to allow Alpha versions be installed.</p>
</div>
<p>Once you <code>push</code>, a GitHub Actions script will automatically run to build the latest solution for your branch. If the branch name is one of the <code>main</code>, <code>develop</code>, or <code>feat</code> branches, the script will also automatically upload the <code>Snap Hutao Alpha</code> archive of its build for testing; other branches will only validate buildability and will not provide an upload.</p>
<p>You can find the full build log in the <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/actions/workflows/alpha.yml" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Snap Hutao Alpha pipeline</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/development/contribute.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster WIKI</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/monster-wiki.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/monster-wiki.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Monster WIKI</source>
      <description>The Monster Wiki is an integrated monster database within Snap Hutao. Players can use this feature to access detailed information on all monsters in Genshin Impact. By analyzing the monsters, players can strategize and reduce the difficulty of the game.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:35:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01bvAkZo1g6e0xyNooh_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="monster-wiki" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Monster WIKI is an embedded WIKI database used to look up each monster's
<strong>Base ability, ability in each level, RES, drop items</strong></p>
<h2>Included Data</h2>
<ul>
<li>Monster list
<ul>
<li>Use the icon above the list, you can change the view between <code>list</code> and <code>grid</code></li>
<li>Click on monster's icon or title, and you will be directed to its WIKI page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>WIKI data
<ul>
<li>Monster's ability
<ul>
<li>Monster base HP, base ATK, base DEF</li>
<li>Monster's HP, ATK and DEF in each level <strong>switched to</strong></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Drop items</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01bvAkZo1g6e0xyNooh_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial Setup Guide</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/setup.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/setup.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Initial Setup Guide</source>
      <description>The new user onboarding feature in Snap Hutao helps users quickly check the availability status of specific program functionalities and set them to an available state.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 19:09:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>When launching the Snap Hutao for the first time, the client will automatically enter an initialization setup guide to assist users in configuring the client correctly.</p>
<p>Currently, Snap Hutao will guide users through the process of setting the language, confirming user agreements, checking necessary environmental configurations, and downloading static resources.</p>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>Language Setting</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01wBgRV01g6dyC2bc62_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In the language settings section, you can choose from the interface languages currently supported by Snap Hutao. If you change the language, the Snap Hutao will automatically restart.</p>
<p>Snap Hutao uses Simplified Chinese as the base language and actively maintains English text.
Traditional Chinese, Korean, and Japanese texts are translated by community contributors.
If you're interested in contributing translations, you can lend your support at <a href="https://translate.hut.ao" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://translate.hut.ao</a>.</p>
</details>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>User Agreement Confirmation</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01Zv1EGr1g6dy8E1fpj_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In the user agreement documents confirmation section, you will need to confirm several documents provided by Snap Hutao.
These documents can help you understand the nature of the Snap Hutao project and will be beneficial for your future usage.</p>
</details>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>Environment Checking</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01LYYIB41g6dyDFB6I9_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In the environment checking section, Snap Hutao will utilize two small tests to assist users in determining whether the system environment, which will enhance user experience, has been installed: the Segoe Fluent Icons font and the WebView2 Runtime.</p>
<p>You can assess whether these two environment packages are installed based on the prompts. If they are not installed, you can click the corresponding link buttons to download and install the required content.</p>
<p>The image above is the expected outcome in this step.</p>
</details>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>Assets Download</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01XlICiR1g6dyC7Qpy6_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In this step, Snap Hutao will automatically download the required static image resources.
Once the download is complete, Snap Hutao will close the initialization setup interface and automatically load the main program.</p>
</details>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/features/setup.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hutao Open Platform</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/platform.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/platform.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Hutao Open Platform</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao incorporates ideas from the community, and as our way of giving back, we also make certain services available to the community. If they are helpful to your development, feel free to use them, and we will do our best to maintain these forked projects.</description>
      <category>open source</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Snap Hutao project has received wide supports from the open-source community and users since its
inception on GitHub on April 18, 2022. As the project has evolved, we have created a series of supporting services
as middleware for Snap Hutao.</p>
<p>Now, the development team is making some of these practical services available to the open-source community in the
form of open interfaces, for use by developers who share our vision. We will be writing usage documentation for these
interfaces, maintaining the services, and providing answers to frequently asked questions. Whether you are an
experienced developer or a beginner, we hope that these interfaces will assist you in creating applications.</p>
<h2>Hutao API &amp; Hutao Cloud Open-source Developer's License</h2>
<p>Hutao API is an interface service that exposes the Hutao Abyssal Database.
Open-source software authors can use the Hutao API to retrieve data from the Hutao database or upload data.</p>
<p>Developers who gain access to the Hutao API also receive full privileges to the Hutao Cloud feature
within the Snap Hutao as a benefit.</p>
<p>Developers can apply for access by submitting their information through the Hutao API Open Platform
at <a href="https://homa.snapgenshin.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">homa.snapgenshin.com</a></p>
<h2>Enka API with China Acceleration</h2>
<p><a href="https://enka.network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Enka Network</a> is an excellent Genshin Impact tool that provides detailed data on characters in
the user's current character showcase. However, due to restricted access to certain network services in China,
the stability of Enka Network's functionality in the region is compromised.</p>
<p>To ensure a smooth user experience for Snap Hutao users in China, the development team has utilized Enka Network's data
for the development of the <a href="/en/features/character-data.html" target="_blank">My Characters</a> feature and established a proxy server.</p>
<p>Developers can ask for access in Snap Hutao development group chat or discord group from administrator.</p>
<h2>UIGF Interchangeable Game Data Format</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao aims to enable the free flow of user data among various open-source tools with different features.
To facilitate this, Snap Hutao has established the initial version of the <a href="https://uigf.org/en/standards/UIGF.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Uniformed Interchangeable GachaLog Format
Standard (UIGF)</a>.</p>
<p>Since then, this standard has gained more recognition among developers, leading to the promotion of additional
standards. Many developers have now gathered under the <a href="https://github.com/UIGF-org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">UIGF organization</a>. Our goal is to
maintain this organization, allowing developers to connect with more users, receive feedback, make technical advancements,
and create outstanding open-source Genshin Impact tools.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/development/platform.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Development</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Open Source Development</source>
      <description>Open Source Development</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:35:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site Menu</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/menu.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/menu.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Site Menu</source>
      <description>Site Menu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:41:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/dashboard.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/dashboard.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Home Dashboard</source>
      <description>In the dashboard of Snap Hutao, users can not only quickly view an overview of their current account data but also access real-time in-game announcements.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 01:37:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01KtqmTn1g6e0ylZXLp_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="dashbord screenshot" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Snap Hutao will enter home dashboard by default when it's opened. The top part is your personal gaming data; the bottom
part is recent game notice and event countdown in days and hours.</p>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao Announcement
<ul>
<li>If Snap Hutao dev team publish a new announcement, it will be shown on the dashboard, it can be manually closed</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Game launcher
<ul>
<li>You can select your account and start the game from dashboard</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Wish history
<ul>
<li>Game UID and progress bar styled pity count will be display in the dashboard</li>
<li>If you have multiple wish history archives, you can use arrow button on left and right side of chart to switch archive</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Achievement statistics
<ul>
<li>Achievement statistics charts includes gained achievements count, percentage, and the latest gained achievements</li>
<li>If you have multiple achievement archives, you can use arrow button on left and right side of chart to switch archive</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Real-time Notes
<ul>
<li>Real-time notes data will be displayed on home dashboard</li>
<li>If you have multiple activated real-time notes account, you can use arrow button on left and right side of
chart to switch account</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>In-game Announcement
<ul>
<li>You can find realtime in-game announcement at the button part of the dashboard</li>
<li><strong>By default, the source of in-game announcement are CN server, you can modify the source in Snap Hutao settings page</strong></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01KtqmTn1g6e0ylZXLp_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/quick-start.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/quick-start.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Quick Start</source>
      <description>Follow the quick start instruction on this page, you can set up your Snap Hutao quickly.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 11:59:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Follow the quick start instruction on this page, you can set up your Snap Hutao quickly.</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>| Requirement             | Attribute                                                        |
|</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01mpzxPR1g6e22IjFMh_!!1797064093.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Community</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/community.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/community.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Join Community</source>
      <description>You can join Snap Hutao&amp;apos;s social community here, to chat with others players in various of topics.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 11:59:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As open-source software, community power is an important part of the ecology of Snap Hutao, and you can join our user community by following ways.</p>
<div class="vp-card-container">
  </div>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01mpzxPR1g6e22IjFMh_!!1797064093.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Advanced</source>
      <description>Advanced</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 05:38:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall Snap Hutao</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/uninstall.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/uninstall.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Uninstall Snap Hutao</source>
      <description>Uninstalling Snap Hutao is a simple and fast process. You can follow the instructions on this page to uninstall Snap Hutao.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:53:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Remove the Snap Hutao Application
<ul>
<li>Open <code>Start Menu</code></li>
<li>Find or search <code>Snap Hutao</code></li>
<li>Right click on it, and select <code>Unstall</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Remove data folder (If you want remove it completely)
<ul>
<li>Open and delete <code>%userprofile%/Documents/Hutao</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>FAQ</h2>
<h3>How to Fully Backup/Recover Client Data</h3>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Data Security Warning</p>
<p><code>Userdata.db</code> contains all client data, including MiHoYO BBS Cookie, please save the data file properly and do NOT share it
with anyone.</p>
</div>
<p>Copy <code>Userdata.db</code> from Snap Hutao data folder (<code>%userprofile%/Documents/Hutao</code> by default) to your backup location, this
file contains entire data of the client.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/uninstall.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known Issue</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/known-issue.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/known-issue.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Known Issue</source>
      <description>We use a variety of labels on our GitHub issue page to categorize and track the status of user-submitted issues. You can rely on these labels to determine the status of issue.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 08:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You can view all issues on <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues?q=is%3Aissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GitHub Issue page</a></p>
<p>| Category                                                                                                                                          | Flag                                        |
|</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/known-issue.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Logs</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Update Logs</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao strives to provide users with the best user experience by continuously updating and fixing known issues and releasing new features. We will always publish update logs to track the changes made to the program.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 08:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>1.12.8 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added keyboard F key auto-press feature, which can be enabled and configured in the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program would crash when entering the game launch page without having any game path</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program would crash when entering the game launch page without setting the game path</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.6</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> The game launcher now automatically detects the game path</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The "Remove team configuration progress bar" feature is now only effective when team switching is allowed</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where updates could not be checked without logging into Hutao Passport</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the background color of the homepage calendar card might be incorrect</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a potential memory leak when modifying the speed limit during game download</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue that might occur when canceling a game download</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when reading Unity logs to get wish records using web cache without setting the game path <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2272" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2272</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.5</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added quick resolution switch customization in the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added historical pool records to the wish history countdown</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added resin estimation to the cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/323" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#323</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1540" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1540</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the background might not change when switching themes</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some elements might display the wrong color theme in certain situations</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a potential vulnerability through metadata initialization injection <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2240" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2240</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the local game version might not be read in certain situations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2251" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2251</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the international server could not refresh wish records in certain situations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2252" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2252</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where characters or weapons might appear without materials after overwriting the cultivation plan</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the transparency settings of the compact web window were not effective <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2258" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2258</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a buffer overflow issue when exiting Snap Hutao from the tray menu on some systems</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game launcher page will now replace the account with the same name instead of creating a new one</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The cultivation plan will now attempt to obtain more accurate backpack material quantities</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the size of Snap Hutao</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the resolution settings could not be saved after launching the game <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2229" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2229</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the achievement completion time was displayed incorrectly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2184" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2184</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the cultivation plan's backpack could not be refreshed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2212" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2212</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the shortcut keys for fast-forward/rewind in the compact web window were not working</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where selecting a file window would cause a crash on some systems</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where selecting a download source when updating Snap Hutao was not effective</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now checks proxy and loopback status at startup and guides users to remove loopback restrictions if unable to connect to the internet</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The compact web window now remembers the page from the last close</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.3 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue caused by the tray icon not syncing <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2198" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2198</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program became unusable due to metadata initialization failure caused by tray icon initialization failure <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2202" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2202</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added shortcut keys for fast-forward/rewind in the compact web window</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the cultivation plan's abnormal selection state prevented Snap Hutao from starting <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2174" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2174</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the tray icon might not be created correctly after restarting as an administrator from the tray menu</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the announcement time was displayed incorrectly before the game version update <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2175" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2175</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where reselecting the game path when starting the game might cause a crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where game file management might get stuck when repairing the game</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the achievement profile could not be switched using the mouse when the window was too small <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2181" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2181</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where uploading Sprial Abyss records without logging into the Hutao Passport caused a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2169" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2169</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the international server could not refresh the Imaginarium Theater properly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2170" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2170</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where adding weapons to the cultivation plan might cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2168" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2168</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the display effect of the pre-download prompt icon in game file management</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added a launch game button for each game character on the Real-time Notes page, which will jump to the game launch page and automatically switch the MiYouShe/HoYoLAB user to the corresponding user of the note <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1318" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1318</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the loading speed of character and weapon icons</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.1 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the program could not start due to database migration failure <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2159" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2159</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Upgraded to .NET 9</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a command to the right-click menu of the notification icon to launch a compact web window
<ul>
<li>The compact web window is a topmost window that can become semi-transparent when not interacted with</li>
<li>You can set the shortcut key for playing/pausing videos in the web window on the settings page</li>
<li>Using the compact web window requires running as an administrator</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a new page for Role Combat <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1671" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1671</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when switching game servers using the SophonChunk mode</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a logic error in some specific cases with the game launch injection option</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some switches in the injection options were not interactive after a forced game termination due to injection failure</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the international server could not refresh wish records via web cache <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2141" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2141</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the attack wave details on the Spiral Abyss page might not fully expand in non-Chinese languages <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2152" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2152</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue caused by the failure to initialize the auto-click hotkey in special cases</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> When launching the game from the Real-time Notes notification, the MiYouShe/HoYoLAB user will automatically switch to the corresponding user</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.9 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added countdown for wish history pools <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1341" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1341</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game launch injection option did not match the actual situation <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2134" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2134</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where enabling field of view adjustment could cause stuttering in team and some character elemental burst scenes <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2137" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2137</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where WebView might crash when it fails to pop up normally</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.8 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the injection feature for the oversea server was not working <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2121" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2121</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where refreshing wish records via web cache was not working <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2124" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2124</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the logic between the game launch injection option switches <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2122" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2122</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> / <strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the UI of the game launch interface
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Removed the progress bar from the team configuration interface</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added "Let me in! Mickey Mouse Clubhouse" feature (yes, really)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added chunk mode for server switching in the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added character name cards to character WIKI <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1424" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1424</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where Snap Hutao might crash on the first launch of the day <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2101" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2101</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the error report window might not display correctly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue with incorrect duration of homepage announcements</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where game file management might crash on certain types of disks <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2077" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2077</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where refreshing wish records via web cache might cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2083" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2083</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where window size might be incorrect after restarting across monitors</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The calendar card now highlights materials that can be farmed today in the current cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2045" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2045</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The "My Characters" and character WIKI no longer show filters for 1-star to 3-star items <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2110" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2110</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adding MiYouShe/HoYoLAB accounts now displays a dialog to prevent user operations until completion</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.6 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where features requiring verification would crash after verification <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2074" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2074</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where features requiring resource downloads might freeze</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.5</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added MiYouShe / HoYoLAB account login in the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added filters on the My Characters page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1786" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1786</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an option to save images from web activities in the settings <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1804" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1804</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added account and third-party login for oversea server <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1966" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1966</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when refreshing background images</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed display issues with multi-monitor scaling</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the error report window might not display correctly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed incomplete display of real-time note settings in some languages <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2040" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2040</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some lists were not processed correctly when updating the cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2022" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2022</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where syncing backpack items in the cultivation plan might not respond <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2044" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2044</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the number of backpack items might be incorrect when syncing the cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2061" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2061</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when entering the verification code directly without clicking "Get" during MiYouShe phone login <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2058" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2058</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the enable logic of the game update button</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Increased the monster level cap to 110 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1988" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1988</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The verification window will now automatically pop up when encountering a CAPTCHA <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1616" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1616</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an error report window that pops up when the program crashes</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the program might crash on the first launch after installing/updating Snap Hutao</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where multiple Discord statuses could be set simultaneously <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2024" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2024</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the first line of the game announcement might not respond to clicks</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where international server announcements could not be retrieved <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2030" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2030</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where unlocking the frame rate might not take effect after the 5.1 version update</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where game updates could not be completed properly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the installation progress in the game update window might exceed 100%</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game resource pre-download might get stuck <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2029" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2029</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the completion mark might not display when the game resource pre-download is finished</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the material statistics on the cultivation calculation page might not respond <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2014" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2014</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where MiYouShe phone verification code login might fail</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added "Priority for incomplete sets" in the material statistics on the cultivation calculation page</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now displays materials that can be obtained today in the material statistics on the cultivation calculation page</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.3</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a calendar card on the homepage <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1923" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1923</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added artifact attribute recommendations on the My Characters page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where some monsters were not displayed correctly on the Spiral Abyss page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the character/weapon data page could freeze <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1999" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1999</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the crash issue when switching game servers</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Prevented closing the operation window directly when game file operations are not completed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2002" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2002</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added import/export buttons on the Wish Records page for easier access to the import/export buttons on the settings page</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the ability to filter only commission achievements in the achievement management page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/897" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#897</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added download game speed limit feature in the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added web tool link for upgrading UIGF versions in the wish records import/export section of the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where copying files within the application package on certain devices would prompt that the specified file cannot be encrypted
<ul>
<li>This issue previously caused
<ul>
<li>Inability to create desktop shortcuts</li>
<li>Inability to unlock game frame rate</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue of abnormal CPU usage when downloading games on the launch game page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1964" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1964</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where game updates were not taking effect</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where switching to a character without artifacts in the My Characters page would cause the program to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1954" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1954</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue of real-time note requests failing with error code -1</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where some devices were unable to switch save files in the achievement management page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1987" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1987</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Achievements titles and tooltips in the achievement management page can now be selected and copied <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1726" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1726</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Searching achievements in the achievement management page now filters by achievement category as well <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1907" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1907</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the interface link for the CN server announcements <a href="https://github.com/Scighost/Starward/issues/1089" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Scighost/Starward#1089</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.1</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a command to execute debug scripts in the right-click menu of the notification icon</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a command to restart in administrator mode in the right-click menu of the notification icon <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1825" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1825</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> The update log window on the first launch after an update now correctly recognizes Snap Hutao's language <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1900" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1900</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the download and repair game functions in the game launcher could not be used properly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the launcher background option did not work properly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1908" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1908</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where importing UIGF v4.0 files did not select the correct parts for import <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1941" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1941</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the dialog layout was incorrect when importing UIGF v4.0 files</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where checking or unchecking achievements in the achievement management would deselect the achievement category if an achievement category was selected <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1946" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1946</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now the HoYoLAB text will be hidden when hovering over the HoYoLAB user in the user panel <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1824" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1824</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The cultivation plan can now correctly recognize the talent and weapon breakthrough materials of Natash</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the field of view for unlocking the frame rate</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the multi-threaded download logic when switching servers</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the UI of the pop-up window for the download and repair game functions in the game launcher</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added long-term expedition point display on the Real-time Notes page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1841" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1841</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> <strong>[BETA]</strong> Added game download/repair/pre-download/update functionality to the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where can't logging in to MiYouShe via QR code, removed QR code login option, added phone verification code login method <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1819" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1819</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where character skill levels displayed inconsistently in the My Character page list and grid view due to constellation bonuses <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1838" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1838</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where switching to another page while the home page announcement was still loading would cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1845" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1845</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where reading local package version information failed when switching game servers would cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1851" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1851</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where obtaining wish records on the international server displayed "AuthKey Expired" <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1873" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1873</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where navigating to My Character/Spiral Abyss pages without logging in to MiYouShe or HoYoLAB prevented further operations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1877" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1877</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where refreshing Real-time Notes on certain devices would cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1893" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1893</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where home page announcements were not displayed correctly and some text colors were rendered incorrect in dark mode</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the application background did not switch correctly</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the display position of in-app notifications <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1832" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1832</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the in-app error messages for network requests</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved the experience of downloading updates, now you can choose a mirror for downloading</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the frame rate unlock feature, removed classic mode, added field of view modification/fog removal/compatibility mode in injection mode</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the feature to export selected character's information in text to the clipboard on the My Character page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1497" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1497</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added UIGF 4 import and export support in the settings page, removed UIGF 2 and UIGF 3 import and export support in Wish Export feature</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the view would not refresh when deleting a save file on the Wish Export page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where Real-time Notes auto-refresh was enabled by default</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the title would not display correctly when the webview width was too narrow</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where HoYoLAB accounts could not add characters or weapons in Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1810" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1810</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue of failing to unlock the frame rate <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1820" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1820</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the navigation interaction of the main window, now navigate to other pages when the page is not fully loaded is disallowed, and the update log window will now be displayed on the first launch after the update</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the display of in-app notifications</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the process of adding items to the Dev Plan, now you can choose the save mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the information prompt for HTTP requests <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1720" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1720</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.6</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the application could not start due to user changing the game path manually <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1792" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1792</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the content of the page was not updated after refreshing the wish records <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1791" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1791</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash that occurred when the refreshed wish records differed from the current UID <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1794" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1794</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the web window size was incorrect on monitors with a scaling rate other than 100% <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1795" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1795</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash that occurred when binding the Real-time Notes UID on the game launcher page</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the time display format for expedition dispatches in the Real-time Notes <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1796" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1796</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.5</h2>
<ul>
<li>Added injection unlock mode, which can be tried when classic mode is ineffective</li>
<li>WebView now displays in a separate window</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where switching from OS server to CN server could cause game data abnormalities <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1750" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1750</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where certain screen recording software could capture the wrong window <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1771" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1771</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where adding a HoYoLAB account under specific conditions could cause the program to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1774" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1774</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where certain controls displayed incorrectly in dark mode <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1633" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1633</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where importing achievements via URL protocol would not display the interface correctly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1763" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1763</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where skill icons would not display correctly in certain scenarios <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1784" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1784</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where some event announcements had incorrect time</li>
<li>Fixed alignment issues with multiple elements</li>
<li>Optimized the display effect of some pages</li>
<li>Refactored the underlying code</li>
<li>Other QA issues</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added previous data comparison in Spiral Abyss - Current Statistics/Character Data/Weapon Data section of Snap Hutao Database</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the ability to obtain backpack materials in Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1651" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1651</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added right-click copy support to all images</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the functionality to display game character avatars in the user panel</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where unlocking the frame rate would prevent game server conversion due to file occupation <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1703" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1703</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where importing achievements from other programs using URL protocol would cause freezing when Snap Hutao is not running <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1704" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1704</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the actual refresh time of real-time notes was magnified by 60 times <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1710" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1710</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Boost the maximum resin notification threshold to 200 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1711" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1711</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> The background image of the launcher now uses the version without text <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1688" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1688</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Changed the logic of activation from the Windows notification center, fixing the issue where notifications could not be correctly redirected in administrator mode</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where all materials or all backpack items would be rendered incorrectly on Dev Plan page in certain scenarios</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved the display effect of some controls</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Changed the activation/closing logic of windows, now they are directly closed instead of being hidden when already open</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the UI for displaying package lists in the Launch Game - Game Resources section</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Weapon data page now uses in-game sorting</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized punctuation and wording of some texts</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other performance improvements and QA testing issue fixes</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.3</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> The notification area icon now supports show the menu with a left click <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1656" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1656</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the frame rate unlock feature in the game launcher failed in version 4.7 of the game <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1675" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1675</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where closing the main window on Windows 10 system would not correctly pop up the tray icon notification</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the tray icon location could not be correctly obtained on Windows 10 system, causing crashes</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the window would not be remembered when resized to smaller than the initial size <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1657" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1657</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where application redirection failed in some scenarios</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the launch game window data expired in some scenarios</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where all materials in the cultivation plan are highlighted on Sundays</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the guide window can be maximized</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game screenshot folder cannot be opened when it does not exist</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the dev version and the official version use the same notification identifier, causing repeated activation </li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Temporarily disabled the MiYouShe web login entry in the user panel</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Removed the jump list of the right-click menu of Snap Hutao icon in the taskbar and the start menu</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the style of in-app notifications <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1650" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1650</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the style of the character property panel in My Characters</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the style of real-time notes settings in Real-time Notes</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the brightness performance of the game announcement images on the homepage in dark mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the brightness performance of the pool images in the global wish statistics in the wish records in dark mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the display effect of some texts</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the loading speed of some pages</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other performance improvements</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŒLocalization]</strong> Added Vietnamese language support</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Introduced retry mechanism for static resource downloads</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added Real-time Note feature to view Archon Quest progress <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1203" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1203</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Highlighted all relevant materials on Sunday in the Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1607" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1607</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added option to display icon in system notification area (system tray)
<ul>
<li>Added notification area icon switch in settings</li>
<li>Application behavior changes when notification area icon is enabled</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Application will not exit when all windows are closed; only exits when selected from the right-click menu of the system tray icon</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Closing the window triggers a prompt if the icon is in the collapsed area</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization/Break Change]</strong> Real-time Note timed refresh no longer triggers when not running in the background (refresh by Windows Scheduled Task is removed)</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Real-time Note refresh switch/refresh time settings no longer require administrator mode</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where images might not load when switching to list view if the default view of character data/weapon data/monster data/achievement management interface was not list view</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where occasional inability to exit the program normally was caused by checking system proxy settings</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the bag items did not switch accordingly when switching the growth plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1609" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1609</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where modifying the completion status of a single achievement would incorrectly deselect the achievement category <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1631" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1631</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where the shortcut key settings would be obscured by the title bar when opening the auxiliary button panel near the title bar <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1632" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1632</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where the time range of some new announcements did not match correctly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1613" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1613</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where the statistics tab on the wish record page would show the pool ratio of 0 draws as NaN <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1588" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1588</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Removed the task list from the right-click menu of the taskbar icon</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added a second confirmation dialog for deleting a growth plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1608" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1608</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added a prompt for HoYoLAB error code 2001 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1542" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1542</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added quality comparison tab to the quality selection page of the guide interface <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1595" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1595</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Disabled auto-click shortcut settings in non-administrator mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other performance improvements</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŒLocalization]</strong> Added French language support</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.1 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the game server conversion issue</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added options for image quality, users can now choose a significant smaller size with nearly lossless image quality. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1430" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1430</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added display of not obtained items in the Character and Weapon tabs of the Wish Export. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1355" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1355</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a new method to start the program in administrator mode by default. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1558" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1558</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the option to display only unfinished achievement categories on the achievement record page. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/896" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#896</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the hidden taskbar couldn't be displayed when maximizing the main window in Windows 10. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1571" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1571</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the incorrect top card margin on the settings page.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game or program would crash when starting after hot-plugging a monitor.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the Global Wish Statistics on the Wish Export page couldn't be viewed when there was no wish record.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the cache image lookup pointed to the wrong path, which caused the need for repeated image resource downloads.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the announcement start and end times were incorrect when the version was not yet updated.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where launching Hutao in Discord's update check could cause a crash.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved the display effect of the floating window before and after clicking the show button in the password input box. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1485" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1485</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The software update process now starts only after user confirmation, no longer starting by default. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1297" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1297</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> When users are not logged in to Hutao Cloud, they will be prompted with a pop-up before uploading Abyss records to avoid missing the opportunity to claim rewards. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1245" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1245</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the game launch feature, it will now attempt to generate the configuration file automatically when it can't be found, and also provides a manual generation function.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Updated Windows App SDK to 1.5.2.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized overall memory usage of the program.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now clearing the cache folder when resetting image resources.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the creation of shortcuts to start in administrator mode, now even if pinned to the taskbar, it can be used normally.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the login pop-up for Hutao Passport, now viewing the password in plain text does not cause the dialog width to change repeatedly.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other significant underlying refactoring.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.9</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add âž•
<ul>
<li>Added Chronicled Wish in Global Wish Stats tab under Wish Export page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the interact launch error with Better Genshin Impact <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1467</a></li>
<li>Fixed the full package name error in Advanced Game Launcher - Resource Download page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1476" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1476</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that game would be launched when failed to unlock frame rate limit <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1495" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1495</a></li>
<li>Updated outdated links in Settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1503" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1503</a></li>
<li>Fixed the crash issue when adding accounts; fixed sporadic issue that selected users and characters could not be cleared correctly; optimized the UI display after logging in. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1504" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1504</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Optimized keyword searching UI in WIKI pages <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1475" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1475</a></li>
<li>Optimized UI in WIKI page when search result is empty <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1479" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1479</a></li>
<li>Optimized collected item display in Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1513" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1513</a></li>
<li>Optimized the smoothness and stability of the waterfall layout in the Dev Plan page</li>
<li>Optimized the default sorting of backpack materials and material stats tabs on the Dev Plan page, and now displays completion markers for items with sufficient quantities <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1510" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1510</a></li>
<li>Optimized the alignment of the scroll bar at the bottom of the Statistics tab on the Wish Export page</li>
<li>Optimized the logic of displaying items in the Global Wish Stats tab on the Wish Export page</li>
<li>Optimized the smoothness and stability of the grid view on the Achievement Management page</li>
<li>Added security hint in Web Login page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.8</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added support for Chronicled Wish <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1470" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1470</a></li>
<li>Added support for UIGF v3.0 wish data format</li>
<li>Added dark/light mode setting option in the settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1434" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1434</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the card display issue under some particular Windows display settings values <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1429" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1429</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that network issue may cause client conversion between CN server and oversea server failed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1433" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1433</a></li>
<li>Fixed the wrong OTA package name and link in downloadable resource page in Advanced Game Launcher</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>The WIKI search/filtering feature has been greatly enhanced, users will now get prompts when typing <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1120" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1120</a></li>
<li>Optimized the text in some InterProcess features in Advanced Game Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1432" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1432</a></li>
<li>Optimized the display UI of Wanderlust Invocation in Wish Export page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1460" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1460</a></li>
<li>Optimized the time range text when the wish data is empty <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1443" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1443</a></li>
<li>Re-enabled the background material in main window</li>
<li>Background image will now be refreshed immediately after changing the background image source setting</li>
<li>Optimized the Teams UI in Spiral Abyss page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.7</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added <a href="https://bgi.huiyadan.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Better Genshin Impact</a> joint start up option in the advanced launcher, users now can start Genshin Impact and BGI together in Snap Hutao <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1388" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1388</a></li>
<li>Added multiple client background wallpaper sources, including:
<ul>
<li>No wallpaper (default)</li>
<li>Random images in local background folder</li>
<li>Bing daily wallpaper</li>
<li>Hutao daily wallpaper</li>
<li>Genshin Impact official launcher background</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that when Discord is running with administrator privilege and Snap Hutao is running in normal privilege, Snap Hutao will crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1400" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1400</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that reorder game account in Advanced Launcher with administrator privilege would cause the clint to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1379" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1379</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that scroll down the in-game announcement in Dashboard would cause the announcement disappear <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1365" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1365</a></li>
<li>Fixed some human unreadable text in character WIKI, again <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1316" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1316</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that searching result in Feedback Center was not HTML decoded <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1391" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1391</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Added two 4K resolution options in Advanced Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1375" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1375</a></li>
<li>Client will now memorize selected character in each account in MiHoYo BBS account panel <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1233" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1233</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.6</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added customized background image feature, users now can open background image folder and add images they like <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/357" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#357</a></li>
<li>Added responsive settings page, layout will be updated while window size and shape changes, <a href="https://github.com/Scighost" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@Scighost</a> realized this feature <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1337" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1337</a></li>
<li>Added container loopback status and unlocker feature in Feedback Center</li>
<li>Added displaying current network proxy status feature in Feedback Center</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed <code>653366069</code> error when submit Spiral Abyss data <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1351" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1351</a></li>
<li>Fixed <code>653366069</code> error when sync character from MiHoYo BBS Battle Chronicle and Development Plan sources</li>
<li>Adapt new Asia server UID rule</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that font size in game announcements is too small <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1347" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1347</a></li>
<li>Fixed MiYouShe QR code login issue, now ZZZ login page is used to handle QR code login method <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1345" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1345</a></li>
<li>Replace unreadable text in character voice/story with normal text in Character WIKI <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1316" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1316</a></li>
<li>Fixed the display issue in Home Dashboard when Parametric Transformer is not achieved <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1331" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1331</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that in some cases, swap Home Dashboard to bottom side would cause the client to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1365" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1365</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>User's MiHoYo BBS accounts in Account Panel can be dragged and reordered now, to allow users to have a better operation experience <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1334" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1334</a></li>
<li>Game account records in Game Launcher can be dragged and reordered now, to allow users to have a better operation experience</li>
<li>Optimized title text in Wish Export (<code>Statistics</code> is renamed to <code>Global Wish Stats</code>) <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1344" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1344</a></li>
<li>Optimized text under Resource Download page in Game Launcher (<code>Client</code> is renamed to <code>Full Package</code>) <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1279" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1279</a></li>
<li>Optimized image download error hint in wizard <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1333" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1333</a></li>
<li>Update Spiral Abyss wave information text of Genshin Impact version 4.4</li>
<li>Added permission error hint in Realtime Notes notification settings</li>
<li>Limit active thread count when downloading client update package</li>
<li>Added two new resolutions in Game Resolution Quick Settings</li>
<li>Allow developers using NamedPipe to activate the application </li>
<li>Make Windows App SDK embedded</li>
<li>Optimized Win32/COM API calls</li>
<li>Redesigned client UI to fit background images</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Localization ðŸŒ
<ul>
<li>Portuguese (PT-BR) is now a new client language, thanks to contribution from <a href="https://github.com/t0piy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@t0piy</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.5</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added monitor identification button in game launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1261" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1261</a></li>
<li>Brand new Feedback Center is introduced <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1039" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1039</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that when the game in under <code>Program Files</code> path, <code>server conversion failed</code> error would be raised <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1262" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1262</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that static packages download cannot be completed in the setup wizard <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1242" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1242</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Added support of changing proxy settings during Snap Hutao is running</li>
<li>Added game status in Game Launcher Card in the dashboard</li>
<li>Added data folder size auto refresh after server conversion cache is deleted</li>
<li>Optimized the logic to identify whether server conversion is needed when game launch process is requested</li>
<li>Optimized the English translation</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.4 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the crash issue for Bilibili server users when entering the main window</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.3</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the crash issue for new users when entering the main window</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.2</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added Windows native HDR option in Game Launcher</li>
<li>Added support of HoYoverse accounts in Game Launcher account switch feature</li>
<li>Added option of deleting server conversion cache file in Settings page</li>
<li>Added restart as admin option in Settings page</li>
<li>Added the function of sharing pictures to the clipboard in WebView</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that some MiHoYo BBS pages operations cannot be done in Webview</li>
<li>Added conspicuous mark of Admin Mode on windows title to indicate whether if Snap Hutao is running as administrator</li>
<li>Fixed game path error after server conversion</li>
<li>Fixed the document link on Spiral Abyss page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Added account identification field in Real-time Note data forwarding webhook</li>
<li>All options in Danger Zone on Settings page now have double confirmations</li>
<li>Change to way of game account switch from PowerShell of directly modify regedit to avoid error when Windows Long Path is not enabled</li>
<li>Optimized UI of auto-click feature shortcut settings card</li>
<li>Added checks for special paths such as Program Files during server conversion</li>
<li>Optimized the scrolling performance of WebView on some pages</li>
<li>Optimized the performance of Discord Activity</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.1 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Fix ðŸ”¨</strong>
<ul>
<li>Fixed crash on Game Launcher page when user text zoom is not set as 100%</li>
<li>Fixed crash caused by Realtime Notes during the program startup</li>
<li>Fixed the issue where Realtime Notes may be loaded simultaneously with user account information, result in reentrancy</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Optimizations âœ¨</strong>
<ul>
<li>Enhanced prompt to add or select game path in Game Launcher</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.0</h2>
<div class="hint-container important">
<p class="hint-container-title">Breaking Changes</p>
<p>Snap Hutao recently obtained sponsorship from the SignPath Foundation for code signing certificates. Starting from version 1.9.0, we will use a brand-new certificate to sign Snap Hutao installation packages.</p>
<p>Programs with the new signature will be incompatible with old versions. Users updating from versions 1.8.4 and older to 1.9.0 and newer versions need to uninstall the old version first and then perform a fresh installation of the new version of the client. Due to the design of Snap Hutao's data directory, users will not lose any important data.</p>
<p>You can read the article <a href="/en/blog/version-1-9-0-breaking-changes.html" target="_blank">Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0</a> for a deeper understanding of how the signature changes in this version update affect the Snap Hutao project.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>New Features âž•</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The game launcher now supports multiple game paths <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#525</a></li>
<li>Added QR code login method for miHoYo in the user panel <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/870" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#870</a></li>
<li>The client now automatically detects network status and displays the results in the settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1161" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1116</a></li>
<li>Added an option in the game launcher to start Genshin Impact in touch mode <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1173" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1173</a></li>
<li>Add option to change in-game announcement source in the settings page, now you may select oversea severs as the source and display announcements with same lanague of your Snap Hutao <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1112" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1112</a>
<ul>
<li>Only available when there is valid regular expression in Crowdin translation (Simplified Chinese, Traditional Chinese and English are supported now)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Added an option in the settings to enable the console. Users can now get more error prompts when troubleshooting by enabling this option.</li>
<li>Introduced a completely new logic for software updates.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Bug Fixes ðŸ”¨</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue with miHoYo API returning a <code>5003</code> error when fetching character information <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1060" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1060</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that Game Launcher cannot unlock framerate limit in Genshin Impact 4.3 version <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1190" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1190</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue with incorrect countdown data for miHoYo announcements in specific situations.</li>
<li>Fixed incorrect PowerShell statements.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Optimizations âœ¨</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Improved error prompt statements in development calculations, making error messages more explicit <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1163" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1163</a></li>
<li>Optimized the interface of development calculations, now showing specific goals for each item <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1016" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1016</a></li>
<li>Optimized the display of Hutao account information on the main interface, no longer displaying user email addresses <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1160" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1160</a></li>
<li>Updated error prompts for Hutao API.</li>
<li>Optimized the settings page interface; users can now view the size of data and cache directories generated by Snap Hutao in the settings.</li>
<li>Removed Microsoft Store buttons</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Localization ðŸŒ</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Added Indonesian language option in the client, thanks to contribution by <a href="https://github.com/NatsumeAoii" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@NatsumeAoii</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1188" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1188</a></li>
<li>Added Russian language option in the client, thanks to contribution by <a href="https://github.com/QweRezOn" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@QweRezOn</a></li>
<li>Improved client localization string character coverage <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1198" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1198</a></li>
<li>Updated translations for existing languages.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.5 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Tested changes caused by certificate change</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.4 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that daily-checkin shows activity end</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that <code>pwsh.exe</code> cannot be selected as PowerShell host <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1145" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1145</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1153" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1153</a></li>
<li>Fixed display language error when Snap Hutao being pulled up by third-party software <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1147" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1147</a></li>
<li>Fixed PowerShell not found error on desktop shortcut <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1151" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1151</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1154" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1154</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Updated Snap Hutao Cloud prompts text</li>
<li>Optimized Discord Activity tracking performance at the beginning and the end of game</li>
<li>Optimized resize performance on Character WIKI/Weapon WIKI/My Character pages</li>
<li>Optimized performance of server conversion, multi-thread downloading on multipart content is now enabled</li>
<li>Optimized server conversion logic, Snap Hutao will not check folder writing permission before the task</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.3 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the crash issue when Discord client is not running <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1134" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1134</a></li>
<li>Fixed wrong wish record time <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1138" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1138</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Includes .NET environment with the package</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.1</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added Discord Activity synchronization functions in <em>Game Launcher</em>, it syncs game status when playing Genshin Impact <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1082" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1082</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue where navigating from <em>Wish Export</em> page <em>Hutao Cloud</em> panel to <em>Spiral Abyss</em> page would not synchronize the navigation bar options <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1116" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1116</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that <em>Auto Click</em> feature cannot bind with <code>Alt</code> key <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1119" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1119</a></li>
<li>Fixed item refresh issue after switching plans in <em>Dev Plan</em> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1099" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1099</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that only blank name json file can be imported in <code>Achievement</code> page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1124" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1124</a></li>
<li>Fixed full package download link under <em>Resource Download</em> page in <em>Game Launcher</em>, it is replaced with split files link <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1126" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1126</a></li>
<li>Fixed the notification issues from <em>Realtime Note</em>, includes wrong content, repeated notifications and unexpectedly bypass client mode <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1123" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1123</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Added overtime refresh rules for Fingerprint/CookieToken, users don't need to click <code>Refresh Cookie</code> in <em>User Panel</em> so often <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1121" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1121</a></li>
<li>Remake <em>Character WIKI</em> page UI</li>
<li>Added hint text when there is no signed in MiHoYo BBS account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1127" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1127</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Upgraded .NET version to 8</strong> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1103" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1103</a></li>
<li>Fixes
<ul>
<li>Fixed translation issues with <em>Hutao Passport</em> registration/logoff/reset password prompts <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1087" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1087</a> by @Tangweirui2021</li>
<li>Fixed an issue with the first-row items on the <em>Dev Plan</em> page not refreshing correctly after switching plans <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1099" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1099</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue on the <em>Game Launcher</em> page where borderless and exclusive fullscreen could not be set simultaneously <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1106" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1106</a></li>
<li>Replaced the file pickers implementation, resolving the problem of being unable to use the file pickers under administrator privilege <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1096" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1096</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where initializing user information at startup could lead to program freezing</li>
<li>Fixed unnecessary exceptions occurring on certain pages after being switched from</li>
<li>Fixed issues with some exceptions not being captured properly</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Added more detailed failure information for metadata initialization</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.17</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that the first item in Dev Plan won't be refresh after switching the plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1079" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1079</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that wish record URL for global server cannot be found <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1081" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1081</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that error log cannot be captured correctly in some specific situations</li>
<li>Fixed wrong wish record time issue</li>
<li>Fixed the data exception in MiHoYo BBS web pop-ups</li>
<li>Fixed the issue of wrong corner radius settings of mask of history/character/weapon page in Wish History</li>
<li>Fixed the wrong announcement time in time zone other than UTC+8</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimized the UI of MiHoYo BBS web pop-ups, supports backward and refresh feature, supports showing the web title</li>
<li>Auto click feature now can be switched off and hot key can be changed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/961" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#961</a></li>
<li>Added support of UIGF v2.4 format import and export
<ul>
<li>Added time zone inference based on account's server <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/830" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#830</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.16</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Add screen resolution quick switch dropdown in Game Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1062" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1062</a></li>
<li>Add support to allow user to cooperate <a href="https://github.com/Scighost/Starward" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Starward</a> with Snap Hutao to collect game play time stats <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1071" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1071</a></li>
<li>Add resource download link copy option in Game Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1074" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1074</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue that MiHoYo BBS returns <code>5003</code> error when fetching data <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1060" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1060</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that page cannot be scrolled in some particular situations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1068" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1068</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1072" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1072</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that characters' skill levels are not shown in My Character <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1069" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1069</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimized update log display logic <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1015" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1015</a></li>
<li>User's setting selection on each button will be memorized in global scope <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/778" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#778</a></li>
<li>Improved client stability</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.15</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added option to recover full wish history record backup from Snap Hutao Cloud service into new archive <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/886" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#886</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue that invalid game launching parameter can be parsed; added switch for some launch parameters <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1052" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1061</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that user cannot register Snap Hutao account in the client <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1059" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1059</a></li>
<li>Fixed notification issue after Realtime Note Webhook Url is set</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimized Snap Hutao account's change password and delete account logic in the client</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.14 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue causes the program to crash when opening some specific dialog boxes <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1052" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1052</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1054" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1054</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.13</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added option to forward Realtime Note data to specified webhook <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/431" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#431</a></li>
<li>Added date range of wish history records <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/899" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#899</a></li>
<li>Added detail view of Adventure Encounter Points in Realtime Note, support view of current Adventure Encounter Points status <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1021" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1021</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed <code>Argument error</code> when using quick launcher from task bar in some conditions <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/925" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#925</a></li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when using advanced launcher in some conditions <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1035" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1035</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that cannot go back on embedded MiHoYo BBS browser <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1023" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1023</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue on converting server from bilibili server to global server <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1041" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1041</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that Snap Hutao cannot identify game client status</li>
<li>Fixed issue on Snap Hutao Cloud status on wish export page, after switching Snap Hutao account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/903" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#903</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Added localization support on prompts that returned by Snap Hutao Cloud server</li>
<li>Redesigned Snap Hutao Passport UI, and now it is embedded in settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1021" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#911</a></li>
<li>Redesigned advanced game launcher page UI</li>
<li>User now can view and select launcher parameters in advanced game launcher</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.11 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed the game launching arguments error (hotfix)</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.10</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed login issue with HoYoverse account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1011" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1011</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1012" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1012</a></li>
<li>Fixed daily check-in issue on HoYoLAB account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1013" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1013</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that <code>Invalid item</code> error show up when language does not match in UIGFv2.2 data file <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1001" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1001</a></li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when an invalid CAPTCHA Url is input in the setting</li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when an invalid channel setting is given when launching the game</li>
<li>Fixed crash when switching account while WebView2 Runtime version is too low to have necessary feature</li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when an invalid record is displayed in Spiral Abyss page</li>
<li>Fixed a memory overflow issue in embedded pages</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Current game account now can be automatically identified when reaching the game launcher page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.9</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue that prevented the program from launching with the correct window size after the monitor
resolution was changed after exiting the program</li>
<li>Fixed login issue of MiHoYo BBS <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1005" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1005</a></li>
<li>Fixed HoYoverse login issue <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1007" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1007</a></li>
<li>Fixed crash log upload issue in version 1.7.7</li>
<li>Fixed UI display issue on Team Lineup page in Spiral Abyss feature <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1008" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1008</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.7</h2>
<ul>
<li>Added card shadow in the following elements to optimize visual effect
<ul>
<li>Dashboard and in-game announcements</li>
<li>Download resource card in advanced game launcher page</li>
<li>Overview card in wish export page</li>
<li>Statistics card in wish export page</li>
<li>Real-time note card</li>
<li>List view in my character page</li>
<li>Image card in character WIKI</li>
<li>Image card in weapon WIKI</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed top margin error under grid view</li>
<li>Fixed grid view crash issues from multiple causes</li>
<li>Fixed server conversion issue from CN server to Bilibili server</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Optimize button position for manual account validation
<ul>
<li>You can now find it directly from account panel</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Added retry logic for fetching abyss record and record upload
<ul>
<li>User who does not set up CAPTURE verification API can retry after manually validating account from account panel</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>## 1.7.6</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added mouse auto click feature triggered by F8, under Administrator privilege mode
<ul>
<li>In the upcoming Genshin Impact 4.1 and 4.2 version, this feature may help you skip some task conversation you dislike</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed crash issue when switching account after validating cookie on Realtime Notes page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/947" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#947</a></li>
<li>Fixed failure of matching current in-game account after rebooting Snap Hutao and game client <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/865" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#865</a></li>
<li>Fixed display issue on Achievement page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/956" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#956</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue that Genshin Impact 4.1 version metadata will cause program to crash on Spiral Abyss page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Optimized some user interface details on some pages</li>
<li>Optimized announcement text color in some particular situation</li>
<li>Optimized download logic of downloading static images</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.5 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added version number for each achievement</li>
<li>Added monster waves data in Abyss Data page (data provided by <a href="https://space.bilibili.com/3537104994831140" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@å¦®å¯å°‘å¥³</a>)</li>
<li>Added Microsoft Store rating button on settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/876" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#876</a></li>
<li>Added a document button above user panel, user will be redirected to current page's document when click on it <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/875" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#875</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed game launcher card on dashboard showing empty account issue <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/924" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#924</a></li>
<li>Fixed achievement status cannot be saved when be manually unchecked <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/880" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#880</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that Realtime Note verification on wrong MiHoYo BBS account</li>
<li>Fixed issue that sometime spiral abyss statistics data are missing</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimizations
<ul>
<li>Optimized some error messages, added solution hints <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/930" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#930</a></li>
<li>Snap Hutao Announcements content on dashboard now is copyable <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/929" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#929</a></li>
<li><strong>Abyss Stats page is now merged into Abyss Records page</strong></li>
<li>Optimized time format in multiple places</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.4 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added option to change PowerShell entry in settings page</li>
<li>Added option to create desktop shortcut in settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/912" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#912</a></li>
<li>Added option to switch display of cards on home dashboard</li>
<li>Added batch-add to Dev Plan option on My Character page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue which event start time is not accurate on Home Dashboard <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/887" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#887</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue on My Character page that caused crashes when clicking on weapon that is not synchronized by Enka API <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/904" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#904</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue of weapon value display error on My Character page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/907" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#907</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where Bilibili server cannot be converted to some other servers <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/893" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#893</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where fetching Novice Wish history will cause the program to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/917" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#917</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where a Dev Plan was not pre-selected before entering the Dev Plan page, which had caused the
Dev Plan page to need to be entered at least once to add a Dev Plan archive</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that failed to claim checkin reward when triggered anti-bot verification, even when anti-bot API returns success result</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Optimized monsters' display order on Monster WIKI page</li>
<li>Optimized launch speed of Wish History page</li>
<li>Optimized local database thread on UI display functions</li>
<li>Optimized the scrolling experience for some views of Dev Plan, it may now take longer for views to be loaded</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.3</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue of HoYoverse web login not working</li>
<li>Upgraded the Windows App SDK version to fix the issue where the top of the title bar could not resize the window</li>
<li>Adjusted the prompt for UIGF v2.2 file import failures, now allowing for faster issue identification based on IDs</li>
<li>Fixed the issue where the user panel would display a successful claim of login rewards even if it failed</li>
<li>Fixed the problem where launching the game from the taskbar would open both the game window and the main program window simultaneously</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.2</h2>
<ul>
<li>Wish Export
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue where full refresh was not working correctly.</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where no-error UIGF files were not being imported correctly</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where Hutao Cloud records were not being retrieved correctly</li>
<li>Adjusted the UI of the Hutao Cloud window to display the number of wishes corresponding to the UID archive</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>My Characters
<ul>
<li>Adjusted the UI to make it more compact</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Adjusted the UI of the homepage notifications to align them with the right edge</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.0</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add a startup guide to help user familiarize Snap Hutao on start launch
<ul>
<li>Guiding users to select a language</li>
<li>Guiding users to confirm terms of service</li>
<li>Guiding users to install Segoe Fluent Icons font and WebView2 Runtime</li>
<li>Guiding users to download static assets</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Main Interface
<ul>
<li>Adjusted icon styles in the navigation bar</li>
<li>Fixed a bug where adjusting window size could lead to unexpected crashes</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>User Panel
<ul>
<li>Adjusted styles of the user panel</li>
<li>Added a button to allow the current user to claim sign-in rewards</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where in some cases, the current user and character could not be selected correctly on startup</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Home Dashboard
<ul>
<li>Added Snap Hutao announcement</li>
<li>Real-Time Note now display refresh time for each card</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where Real-Time Note card fail to load correctly, leading program to freezing or crashing</li>
<li>Corrected start/end times for certain event announcements</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where some paragraphs were not displaying correctly when viewing details of certain announcements</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Game Launch (Advanced Launcher)
<ul>
<li>Added game status indicator text to the command bar</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where server switch function was not working</li>
<li>Adjusted server switch function logic to allow retries after resource download failure</li>
<li>Adjusted unlocked frame rate logic; game process will automatically end if unlocking fails</li>
<li>Removed multi-client</li>
<li>Fixed an issue in resource download page where game client had no names and couldn't be downloaded</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Wish History
<ul>
<li>Adjusted card style on the overview page, making items larger and collapsing multiple text items</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where entering the wish history page without logging in or without Snap Hutao Cloud service caused errors</li>
<li>Fixed progress bar and color display issues in the card list view on the overview page</li>
<li>Fixed incorrect text for Snap Hutao Cloud's upload reward</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that UIGF formatted data file with incorrect item ID can be imported</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that failed to locate game cache directory</li>
<li>Optimized page load speed when there is a large amount of items</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Achievement
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting achievement categories in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
<li>Optimized page load speed</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Real-Time Notes
<ul>
<li>Adjusted the style of the <code>Verify Current User and Role</code> button</li>
<li>Adjusted the style of the notification settings view</li>
<li>Added an option to disable auto-refresh for real-time notes (toggle available only in non-administrator mode; users who have previously accessed the real-time notes page in administrator mode might not be able to toggle this option)</li>
<li>Adjusted the style of real-time notes</li>
<li>Adjusted text prompts for locked Serenitea Pot and unowned Parametric Transformations</li>
<li>Added previous refresh time for each Real-time note cards</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>My Characters
<ul>
<li>Adjusted width of character list when using list view</li>
<li>Added a button to toggle display of refresh time in command bar</li>
<li>Added previous refresh time for each refresh function</li>
<li>Added display of times artifacts were enhanced in character details</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Dev Plan
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue failure of saving active archive when switching page from dev plan to others</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Character WIKI
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting character in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Weapon WIKI
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting weapon in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
<li>Added ascension material section for each weapon</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Monster WIKI
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting monster in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Settings
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue that unable to clear game cache directory</li>
<li>Added configuration field for Geetest CAPTCHA verification API, correct configuration on this field can handle anti-bot verification from MiYouShe</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Improved program frame rate performance</li>
<li>Optimized memory usage for multi-thread scheduling</li>
<li>Optimized loading speed of item image assets</li>
<li>Adjusted database read/write methods to optimize memory usage and responsiveness</li>
<li>Adjusted text prompts for return codes <code>-100</code> and <code>-10001</code> to help users better understand their meanings</li>
<li>Other minor changes</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.6</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao Cloud tab will show expiration time and developer's license on the wish history page now</li>
<li>Wish statistics are now available on the wish history page, with data supported by Snap Hutao Cloud</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fix failure of web cache refresh method for wish history export</li>
<li>Fix Traditional Chinese metadata loading error</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.5</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Japanese is now a new language option;
community members can contribute Japanese language on <a href="https://translate.hut.ao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">translate.hut.ao</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue that cannot add weapons to dev plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/747" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #745</a></li>
<li>Issue on some users failed to unlock frame rate limit under certain environment
<a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/747" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #747</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Refine dashboard UI</li>
<li>Introducing Metadata v2</li>
<li>Sorting order of materials in dev plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/749" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #749</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.4</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Export wish history data with <a href="https://uigf.org/zh/standards/UIGF.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">UIGF v2.3</a> data format</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>FPS unlocker <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/733" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #733</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>When running program without administrator privilege, features require administrator privilege will have text hints</li>
<li>Support of HoYoLAB</li>
<li>Localization updates</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.3</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Home dashboard, including Hutao Cloud account, game launcher, wish history, achievement stat and real-time notes</li>
<li>Enable notification box will now automatically hide in-app notification</li>
<li>CN server option without TapTap account</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue that user cannot get Hutao Cloud bonus after uploading Abyss record</li>
<li>Issue that cannot sign in to HoYoLAB with Facebook</li>
<li>HoYoLAB check-in issue</li>
<li>Issue when facing empty value during wish history fetch progress</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li><strong>Project refactoring, brings a 20% performance improvement</strong></li>
<li>Add localization support for WIKI features</li>
<li>Add support for all international channels (which affect payment gateway)
<ul>
<li>Supporting HoYoverse official, Google Pay, Epic</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>When Unlock framerate limit is enabled, limit value can be modified during the game, and will take effect immediately</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.2 </h2>
<ul>
<li>New Feature
<ul>
<li><strong>Wish history cloud backup</strong> based on Hutao account system
<ul>
<li>Currently, sponsors on AFDIAN and beta users will receive corresponding cloud membership time; All registered users will receive 5 days membership time after uploading Abyss record.</li>
<li>This feature will be optimized constantly in the following 1.6 versions</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue that BiliBili server account cannot receive data for Real-time Notes</li>
<li>Issue on HoYoLAB login</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Static assets download logic</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.0</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Hutao account system with registration and login available now</li>
<li>Support of HoYoLAB account login, and add its support to the following features:
<ul>
<li>Web login and Stoken Cookie login</li>
<li>Abyss record</li>
<li>Daily check-in reward</li>
<li>My character</li>
<li>Real-time notes</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Performance of frame rate unlock</li>
<li>Multi-client</li>
<li>Now users must unlock advanced features in the settings page before actually using them</li>
<li>Settings page layout</li>
<li>Tiles image on Windows 10</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.5.4</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Game Launcher
<ul>
<li>Game resource package download</li>
<li>Allow multiple Genshin Impact process to run</li>
<li>Allow users to select the specified monitor to start the game</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>New icons have been used</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue caused unlimited file writing during server switch</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimize default language selection</li>
<li>Allow device ID be copied with button</li>
<li>Setting page UI optimization</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.5.1</h2>
<ul>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Replace <code>JumpList</code> menus with <code>JumpTask</code>,</li>
<li>Add option to allow user set language over system default setting</li>
<li>Add translation contribution entry</li>
<li>Add options to reset the image resource</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Monster WIKI</li>
<li>Korean translation</li>
<li>Internationalized Metadata</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.4.15</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Static image reset method</li>
<li>Cookie refresh</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fix <a href="/advanced/known-issue.html#_2-%E6%9C%8D%E5%8A%A1%E5%99%A8%E5%88%87%E6%8D%A2%E5%AF%BC%E8%87%B431-4302%E6%8A%A5%E9%94%99" target="_blank">#2 31-4302 caused by server switch</a></li>
<li>Fix the failure of clearing scheduled task in some specific situations</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimize Dev Plan UI <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/486" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#486</a></li>
<li>Optimize English and Traditional Chinese translations</li>
<li>Add hints when Windows long path limits are triggered</li>
<li>Optimize wake-up for scheduled tasks</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.4.14</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix issue that new dev plan cannot be added</li>
<li>Support English UI</li>
<li>Other minor bug fix</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.4.11</h2>
<ul>
<li>First version on Microsoft Store</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Program Exceptions</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/exceptions.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/exceptions.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Common Program Exceptions</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao utilizes specific error codes to indicate particular errors. If you encounter a program error during usage and have an error code, you can try searching for it on this page.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 06:20:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This document covers solutions of <strong>foreseeable client error</strong></p>
<h2>Return Code: 2002</h2>
<ul>
<li>This error comes directly from MiHoYo BBS: <code>Ruturn Code: 2002</code></li>
<li>Issue source:
<ul>
<li>MiHoYo BBS account is not initialed yet</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Solutionï¼š
<ul>
<li>MiYouShe account: Use official MiYouShe mobile app, login to your account, set the community username to initial account</li>
<li>HoYoLAB account: Use official HoYoLAB mobile app or the web application, login to your account, set the community username to initial account</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Return Code: -10001</h2>
<ul>
<li>This error comes directly from MiHoYo BBS, prompts include
<ul>
<li><code>Return Code: -10001</code></li>
<li><code>Return Code: -100</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Issue source
<ol>
<li>Cookie expired</li>
<li>Network error</li>
<li>System time is not accurate</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Solution
<ol>
<li>In the account panel, execute <code>Refresh Cookies</code></li>
<li>Remove your account and add it again</li>
<li>Sync your system time</li>
</ol>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Return Code: 1034 Verification Failed</h2>
<ul>
<li>If Snap Hutao returns <code>1034</code> status code and hints verification failed (usually during the operation of Realtime Notes),
it means the operation is blocked by MiHoYo BBS anti-bot system</li>
<li>Solution:
<ul>
<li>Enter <code>Realtime Notes</code></li>
<li>Click on <code>Verify Current User and Role</code> button</li>
<li>Follow the instruction in MiHoYo BBS to verify</li>
<li>After finishing the verification process, click <code>Complete</code> to close the verification window</li>
<li>Now, the account should back to normal; If not, process the step above again</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>If the risk prompt is too frequent, or the verification cannot be triggered at all, it means that the risk of your
account is too high, please change the password, so that the simultaneous login status of multiple devices will be reset</p>
</div>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Warning</p>
<ul>
<li>You hardly cannot pass imperceptible verification when your account is <strong>login at other remote Genshin tools</strong> or
<strong>login at multiple devices</strong>. This is a security designing of MiHoYo BBS, and cannot bypass</li>
<li>If you are using <strong>multiple MiHoYo BBS account in your device</strong>, <strong>frequent usage with MiHoYo BBS API</strong> will
result in your IP address being banned for a period of time (usually no more than 24 hours). This is a security
designing of MiHoYo BBS, and cannot bypass</li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2>HttpRequestException Metadata Download Failed</h2>
<h3>ConnectionError</h3>
<p>Failed to connect to Snap Hutao server, please check your connection</p>
<p>If you are using a network proxy, please check if you have <a href="/en/advanced/FAQ.html" target="_blank">unlocked Windows container Loopback limit</a></p>
<h3>403 (Forbidden) / 404 (Not Found)</h3>
<p>Solution: Update your Snap Hutao to <a href="/en/quick-start.html" target="_blank">the latest version</a></p>
<h3>502 (Bad Gateway)</h3>
<p>Failed to connect to Snap Hutao server, please check your connection</p>
<h2><code>653366069</code> Request Exception</h2>
<ul>
<li>Failed to connect to MiYouShe or HoYoLAB server
<ul>
<li>if the error occurs not frequently, you may ignore it</li>
<li>if the error constantly occurs, please check your local network</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>If you are using a network proxy, please check if you have <a href="/en/advanced/FAQ.html" target="_blank">unlocked Windows container Loopback limit</a></p>
<h2>Error Finding Required Modules</h2>
<p>When user launching game with unlock frame-rate feature on, the game may be failed to be launched with the following error shows up:</p>
<ol>
<li>Error finding required modules: could not read any module, the protection driver may have been loaded</li>
<li>Error finding required modules: timeout</li>
</ol>
<p>This issue only occurs when Genshin Impact's anti-cheat module starts earlier than frame-rate-unlocker module.
When these errors happen, Snap Hutao will exit game process, and you can re-launch the game.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/exceptions.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localization</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/i18n.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/i18n.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Localization</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao hopes to help players from all over the world. In addition to maintaining the simplified Chinese and English of the program, we also accept translations from community members.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <category>i18n</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 06:31:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Localization Process</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao Project features were originally based on the China server, but we are also trying to expand the coverage globally through the support of the MiHoYo global gaming server &amp; software localization.Currently, our localization process includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-0" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-0"> Localization framework</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-1" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-1"> Client translation</label>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li>Process: <img src="https://badges.crowdin.net/snap-hutao/localized.svg" alt="Crowdin" loading="lazy"></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-2" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-2"> English</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-3" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-3"> Traditional Chinese</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-4" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-4"> Korean (in progress)</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-5" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-5"> Japanese (in progress)</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-6" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-6"> Indonesian (in progress; contributed by <a href="https://github.com/NatsumeAoii" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">NatsumeAoii</a>)</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-7" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-7"> Russian (in progress; contributed by <a href="https://github.com/QweRezOn" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">QweRezOn</a>)</label></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-8" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-8"> Oversea/China server conversion</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-9" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-9"> Oversea server account switch</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-10" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-10"> Oversea server wish history export</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-11" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-11"> Oversea server character stat</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-12" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-12"> HoYoLAB login</label>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-13" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-13"> International server Abyss record</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-14" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-14"> Daily Notes</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-15" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-15"> Multilingual in-game announcements</label></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Snap Hutao Docs
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-16" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-16"> Localization framework</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-17" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-17"> Web translation process:</label>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-18" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-18"> English</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-19" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-19"> Indonesian (in progress; contributed by <a href="https://github.com/NatsumeAoii" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">NatsumeAoii</a>)</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-20" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-20"> Russian (in progress; contributed by <a href="https://github.com/QweRezOn" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">QweRezOn</a>)</label></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Engage our Localization</h2>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao
<ul>
<li>We created an issue thread named <code>[Hoyolab] on GitHub: Globalization support</code> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/144" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue</a>
<ul>
<li>We will update our process in this thread</li>
<li>You can declare your localization engagement in the thread, and we will provide the necessary support
<ul>
<li>We also welcome PR directly</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>You can provide your translation at <a href="https://translate.hut.ao" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">translate.hut.ao</a></strong></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Snap Hutao Docs
<ul>
<li>The developer team is maintaining Chinese documents and working on English documents
<ul>
<li>We thank <a href="https://github.com/QweRezOn" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">QweRezOn</a> for the documentation in Russian</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>You can clone the <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">docs repository</a>, translate docs with your
favorite tools, and make a Pull Request to contribute your work to the main repository</li>
<li>If you are adding a new language, you can copy the entire <code>en</code> folder and rename it with <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_ISO_639-1_codes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ISO 639-1 language code</a>
<ul>
<li>For example <code>jp</code> as Japanese</li>
<li>Do not translate based on Chinese docs (<code>zh</code>) as there are some content only specific useful for Chinese users; they are not useful for international users.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/i18n.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/star-request.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/star-request.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml"></source>
      <description>If you believe Snap Hutao is a good project and helps you, you can support us by the following ways Star our project on GitHub â­ Snap.Hutao hutao.stars Snap.Hutao.Docs hutao.doc...</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>If you believe Snap Hutao is a good project and helps you, you can support us by the following ways</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Star our project on GitHub â­
<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Snap.Hutao</a> <img src="https://img.shields.io/github/stars/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?style=plastic&amp;color=red" alt="hutao.stars" loading="lazy"></li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Snap.Hutao.Docs</a> <img src="https://img.shields.io/github/stars/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs?style=plastic&amp;color=red" alt="hutao.docs.stars" loading="lazy"></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Promote our project in your network</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="https://img.shields.io/github/commit-activity/y/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?style=for-the-badge" alt="commit_activity" loading="lazy"> <img src="https://img.shields.io/github/last-commit/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?label=Hutao Last Commit&amp;style=for-the-badge" alt="hutao-last-commit" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.shields.io/github/stars/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?style=plastic&amp;color=red" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other FAQ</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/FAQ.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/FAQ.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Other FAQ</source>
      <description>This page lists common issues and solutions related to user networking and program lifecycle problems.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 08:44:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3>How to Create Desktop Shortcut (with No Admin Privilege)</h3>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Community Power</p>
<p>Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs/issues/12" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CzHUV</a> for the solution.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Use <code>Win+R</code> to start run, in the window input <code>shell:AppsFolder</code> <img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01Jj8c6i1g6du728e5A_!!1797064093.png" alt="Run" loading="lazy"></li>
<li>In the new pop-up window, find Snap Hutao</li>
<li>Right lick on it, and click <code>Create shortcut</code></li>
<li>Confirm the operation and you will get the desktop shortcut</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Create Desktop Shortcut (With Admin Privilege)</h3>
<p>Click <code>Create Desktop Shortcut</code> in the settings page.</p>
<h3>How to run Snap Hutao when Windows starts</h3>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Warning</p>
<p><strong>This is a workaround solution.</strong> Approaches may fail in practice due to various problems.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Create a bat file, content refers to <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/184" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">this Issue</a>, it allows bat to run Snap Hutao with Administrator privilege</li>
<li>Create a Scheduled Task, run the bat when Windows startup, or drag it to Windows start folder</li>
</ul>
<h3>Unable to Run Snap Hutao as Administrator</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>This issue only occurs in Windows 10 older than 22H2 version</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>When user's OS version older than <code>Windows Build 19045</code> (aka Windows 10 22H2), Snap Hutao is unable to start when
running as Administrator
<ul>
<li>This issue comes from Windows kernel, and it's hard to locate, so we suggest you to update your OS to the latest version</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Use Snap Hutao with Network Proxy</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>Snap Hutao has a well-designed cloud network structure, you should be able to get good network service wherever you are located</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Loopback network are disabled for all Windows Appx container application (including Snap Hutao), so some modern network proxy software will cause container applications to lose Internet access, and lead to application errors.</p>
<p>If you need network proxy to use Snap Hutao, you can try the following solutions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Config in Snap Hutao
<ul>
<li>Open <code>Feedback Center</code> and click <code>Config Loopback Exemption</code> and follow the instructions</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Config in network proxy software
<ol>
<li>Enable <code>TUN Mode</code> in your network proxy software if it supports</li>
<li>Contact your network proxy software provider for help, ask solution of Windows Appx container application proxy configuration</li>
</ol>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/faq.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Data and Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/privacy-notice.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/privacy-notice.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">User Data and Privacy Notice</source>
      <description>Please read this page carefully to understand the user data handling and privacy rights for the Snap Hutao project.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 07:17:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Personal Information</h2>
<p>The nature of Snap Hutao project states it does not collect any personal information data.</p>
<h2>Regular Data Usage</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao respects the privacy of users, and we're currently using data as described below:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Once using Snap Hutao, the database file in the <strong>data directory</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Stores</strong>
<ul>
<li>MiHoYo BBS and HoYoLAB cookie</li>
<li>Snap Hutao program settings</li>
<li>All other user data</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>When using Snap Hutao, we collect <strong>anonymized</strong> logs data for development and statistical purposes when program stops unexpectedly or throw an error, including</p>
<ul>
<li>User device ID</li>
<li>Error or crash log</li>
<li>Active user statistical data</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>When using <code>Hutao Database</code> (<code>Abyss Record</code>/<code>Abyss Stats</code>) feature and select <code>Upload Data</code></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Upload</strong> data to Hutao API, including
<ul>
<li>User's in-game UID</li>
<li>User's Abyss record</li>
<li>User's character information including artifact and weapon data</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>After using <code>Real-time Notes</code> features</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Create</strong> a Windows scheduled task to fetch data timely</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>After using <code>server switch</code> feature in <code>Game Laucher</code>, in Snap Hutao's data directory</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Store</strong> game files for server switch usage</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>After using <code>Hutao Account</code> features, Hutao Account system server will</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Store</strong>
<ul>
<li>User registered email address</li>
<li>Encrypted password</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Trustable Domains</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao project is holding the following domains, they are trustable in this project scope, please be wary of
information provided by domains outside this list (including websites, emails, etc.)</p>
<ul>
<li>hut.ao</li>
<li>snapgenshin.com</li>
<li>dgp-studio.cn
<ul>
<li>We only use this domain for public email contact</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>snapgenshin.cn
<ul>
<li>We only use this domain for system emails</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>snaphutao.com</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/privacy-notice.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obtaining Stoken-containing Cookies Using Third-Party Tools</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/get-stoken-cookie-from-the-third-party.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/get-stoken-cookie-from-the-third-party.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Obtaining Stoken-containing Cookies Using Third-Party Tools</source>
      <description>There are some third-party tools that can help you obtain the cookie from the miHoYo community with the Stoken field value and use it for Snap Hutao.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <category>Third-Party Tools</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:24:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Warning</p>
<ul>
<li>The software, open-source projects, and resources mentioned in the following steps are sourced from the internet and are not affiliated with DGP-Studio.</li>
<li>This documentation provides solutions for educational purposes only. Specific operations and their consequences are not associated with this project.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2>Android</h2>
<p>Android users can utilize the open-source project GetToken to acquire cookies containing the Stoken field.</p>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">GetToken Open-Source Project</p>
<ul>
<li>GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/HolographicHat/GetToken" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HolographicHat/GetToken</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<ul>
<li>The GetToken project's release includes two APK files, both ultimately achieving the same outcome. Choose the version suitable for your device:
<ul>
<li><code>app-release.apk</code> is an LSPosed plugin that enables users to use GetToken functionality within the official miHoYo community app.</li>
<li>APK files ending with <code>lspatched</code> are modified versions of the miHoYo community app with GetToken functionality included.
<ul>
<li>You'll need to uninstall the official miHoYo app to install this version.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After enabling the plugin or installing the modified miHoYo app, open the miHoYo app, click "Me" at the bottom, and log in to your account.</li>
<li>Click ðŸ”‘ icon in the top right corner.</li>
<li>Check the <code>Stoken</code> option.</li>
<li>Click <code>Copy Login Information</code>.</li>
<li>Send the copied Stoken to the computer where the Snap Hutao is installed.</li>
<li>In the Snap Hutao's account login section, click <code>Manual Input</code>.</li>
<li>Enter the previously obtained cookie. You should now complete the login process.</li>
</ul>
<h2>iOS</h2>
<p>iOS Users can download the packet capture software Stream from the App Store to obtain cookies containing the Stoken field.</p>
<ul>
<li>Download <a href="https://apps.apple.com/cn/app/stream/id1312141691" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Stream</a> from the App Store.</li>
<li>Perform packet capture analysis on the domain <code>api-takumi.mihoyo.com</code>.</li>
<li>Locate and copy the data containing <code>Stoken</code>.
<ul>
<li>It will be in the form of <code>stuid=****;stoken=v2****;mid=****;</code>.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Send the copied Stoken to the computer where the Snap Hutao is installed.</li>
<li>In the Snap Hutao's account login section, click <code>Manual Input</code>.</li>
<li>Enter the obtained cookie. You should now complete the login process.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/get-stoken-cookie-from-the-third-party.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development Plan</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/develop-plan.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/develop-plan.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Development Plan</source>
      <description>The &amp;quot;Development Plan&amp;quot; feature in Snap Hutao assists players in quickly creating cultivation checklists for characters and weapons, allowing them to easily track the obtainable targets they own and plan to cultivate.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:18:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01zzcpWb1g6e0m2xFYJ_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="dev-plan" loading="lazy"></p>
<blockquote>
<p>Development Plan is a feature equivalent to <a href="https://act.hoyolab.com/ys/event/calculator-sea/index.html#/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Enhancement Progression Calculator in HoYoLAB</a>, due to limited designing space, we often call it <code>Dev Plan</code> in Snap Hutao</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Add Develop Goals into Material Checklist</h2>
<h3>Add Goals from WIKIs</h3>
<ul>
<li>Click <code>Character WIKI</code> or <code>Weapon WIKI</code> from the left menu bar</li>
<li>Select on character or weapon to want to add</li>
<li>Click <code>Add to Dev Plan</code> on the top right</li>
<li>In the pop-up window, input the base level and target level
<ul>
<li>By default, add goals from WIKIs will set base level as <code>1</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Add Goals from My Characters Data</h3>
<ul>
<li>Click <code>My Characters</code> from the left menu bar</li>
<li>Select the character you want to add</li>
<li>In the pop-up window, input the base level and target level
<ul>
<li>By default, add goals from WIKIs will set base level as player's live data</li>
<li>Refer to <a href="/en/features/character-data.html#sync-character-data" target="_blank">My Characters</a> document to get more guides</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Inventory Items</h2>
<ul>
<li>In the left column of the Snap Hutao, click the <code>Dev Plan</code> feature.</li>
<li>Click the <code>Inventory Item</code> in the function bar</li>
<li>In the upper right part of the overall interface of the Snap Hutao, click the <code>Create New Plan</code> button.</li>
<li>In the pop-up window of <code>Create a New Dev Plan</code>, fill in the name of the cultivation plan to be created.
<ul>
<li>Here you can check "Bind the currently selected account character".</li>
<li>The drop-down option box to the left of the "Create New Plan" button allows you to <strong>switch between different Dev Plans</strong> at will.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01zzcpWb1g6e0m2xFYJ_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapon WIKI</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/weapon-wiki.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/weapon-wiki.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Weapon WIKI</source>
      <description>The Weapons Wiki is an integrated weapon database within the Snap Hutao toolbox. Players can use this feature to access detailed information about all weapons in Genshin Impact and choose suitable weapons for their characters.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 09:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN016BJBYd1g6e0qbvH2x_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="weapon-wiki" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Weapon WIKI is a Snap Hutao build-in WIKI feature used to look up each weapon's information</p>
<h2>Included Data</h2>
<ul>
<li>Weapon list
<ul>
<li>Use the icon above the list, you can change the view between <code>list</code> and <code>grid</code></li>
<li>Click on weapon's icon or title, and you will be directed to its WIKI page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Weapon data
<ul>
<li>Weapon basic information
<ul>
<li>Images of weapon before and after ascension</li>
<li>Weapon's main image</li>
<li>Weapon's introduction</li>
<li>Weapon's numerical value at value you <strong>switch to</strong></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Weapon refinement data
<ul>
<li>Weapon's numerical value at each refinement level</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Weapon's ascension materials</li>
<li>Weapon's <strong>most used by characters</strong> data provided by Hutao Database</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN016BJBYd1g6e0qbvH2x_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Settings</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-settings.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-settings.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Software Settings</source>
      <description>The Settings page of Snap Hutao contains various options to customize different aspects of the program. By modifying the settings on this page, users can personalize Snap Hutao to achieve the desired user experience.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 07:34:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01m1CSiq1g6e0utDIKD_!!1797064093.png" alt="settings" loading="lazy">
The following feature tutorials are introduced in-program order.</p>
<h2>About Snap Hutao</h2>
<p>This part has the following information:</p>
<ul>
<li>The icon of Snap Hutaoï¼šYou can find the original image of the icon at the <a href="/" target="_blank">home page</a>
<ul>
<li>The artist is <a href="https://space.bilibili.com/274422134" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ç”»ç”»çš„èŠ¦è‹‡ (BiliBili)</a><details class="hint-container details"><summary>Drawing Process</summary>
</details>
</li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DGP-Studio</a> is authorized by owner to use it for Snap Hutao Project</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Snap Hutao Account</h2>
<p>You can sign up and sign in your Snap Hutao Account in settings page.</p>
<p>For more detail about this feature, please refer to <a href="/en/features/hutao-passport.html" target="_blank">Snap Hutao Account</a> document.</p>
<h2>Administrator Mode Tools</h2>
<p>On the right side of the settings page, the development team has set up an administrator mode tool for users who need it. Under this module, we provide two functions:</p>
<ol>
<li>Restart the program immediately as an administrator</li>
<li>Create a PowerShell shortcut on the desktop to start Hutao as administrator</li>
</ol>
<h2>CAPTCHA</h2>
<blockquote>
<p>This feature is most likely to be useful for CN server (MiYouShe) users</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If daily check-in and realtime notes functions are essential for you, then the <code>-1034</code> error from miHoYo's anti-bot verification will definitely be a major interference. This is because miHoYo uses Geetest to intercept requests directly executed by non-humans, and some requests from Snap Hutao will be judged by Geetest as robot behavior and cause request failure. If you use a third-party service to verify the Geetest captcha, you can pass the random data generated by Geetest to the verification service provider through this setting.</p>
<p>After successfully configuring this setting, Snap Hutao will directly call this verification service to pass the Geetest verification when performing real-time note automatic refresh and miHoYo community check-in, avoiding the generation of -1034 error by miHoYo.</p>
<h2>Appearance</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Language</p>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao will following system language setting by default</li>
<li>You can force to change to another language in the settings page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Backdrop Material</p>
<ul>
<li>In this option, you can change the backdrop material of the software to
<ul>
<li>Acrylic</li>
<li>Mica (Windows 11 only)</li>
<li>MicaAlt (Windows 11 only)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>The setting will take effect immediately</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Shortcut Keys</h2>
<p>In this module, you can enable and change the setting of auto-click shortcut key</p>
<h2>Home</h2>
<ul>
<li>Dashboard Card
<ul>
<li>You can click on this option to switch display of card on Home Dashboard
<ul>
<li>Game Launcher</li>
<li>Wish History</li>
<li>Achievement</li>
<li>Realtime Notes</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Announcement Server
<ul>
<li>You can change source of in-game announcement in this field</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Game</h2>
<ul>
<li>Delete Game Embedded Browser Web Cache
<ul>
<li>When you are using web cache refresh method in the wish history feature and receiving authkey expiration error, you can try this operation to fix the error</li>
<li>Click on this field to execute the operation</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Wish History</h2>
<ul>
<li>In this field, you can choose to hide wish event that you do not have any record in the period in the wish export feature</li>
</ul>
<h2>Storage</h2>
<ul>
<li>Data Folder
<ul>
<li><code>Open Folder</code>: Click this field to open data folder that contains user data, log, and metadata</li>
<li><code>Change Data Directory</code>: This field allows you to change the data directory to path you want</li>
<li><code>Delete Server Conversion Cache</code>: This option allows user to delete server conversion cache file inside of data folder</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Cache Folder
<ul>
<li><code>Open Folder</code>: Click this field will open cache folder that saves image assets used by Snap Hutao</li>
<li><code>Reset Image Resource</code>: This option allows user to reset image cache when there are too many image failed to load. The program will re-download images resource at next start-up</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Dangerous Features</h2>
<div class="hint-container important">
<p class="hint-container-title">Important</p>
<p>Using any feature within the "Dangerous Features" will trigger a secondary confirmation prompt. You may be asked to enter the <strong>title name</strong> of the feature that is currently being requested to be enabled.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Debug Console
<ul>
<li>After enabling this feature, a command line window containing real-time logs will be enabled the next time you start the Hutao Toolbox. You can obtain error information that may be helpful to you through this window.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Advanced Features
<ul>
<li>With Snap Hutao running as administrator, you can enable this field to enable advanced features in the game launcher
<blockquote>
<p>For referenceï¼š</p>
<p><a href="/en/statements/tos.html" target="_blank">Snap Hutao Terms of Service</a></p>
<p><a href="https://ys.mihoyo.com/main/company/agreement" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Genshin Impact Terms of Service (CN server/Chinese)</a></p>
<p><a href="https://genshin.hoyoverse.com/en/company/terms" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Genshin Impact Terms of Service (Oversea servers/English)</a></p>
</blockquote>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Delete All Users
<ul>
<li>Execute this operation will delete all user data in Snap Hutao</li>
<li>Click on the field to operate, you will be asked to confirm</li>
<li>In most scenario, you don't need to use this field</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01m1CSiq1g6e0utDIKD_!!1797064093.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Notes</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/real-time-notes.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/real-time-notes.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Real-time Notes</source>
      <description>The Real-time Note feature in Snap Hutao synchronizes dynamic information from Genshin Impact to your local computer by periodically refreshing your miHoYo account data. It allows you to set conditions for message reminders and push notifications based on your preferences. This feature helps you stay updated with the latest in-game events, announcements, and other relevant information in real-time.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:26:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Info</p>
<p>This features requires you to login in to your MiYouShe or HoYoLAB account in Snap Hutao,
you can check <a href="/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html" target="_blank">MiHoYo BBS Account Switch</a> for more information.</p>
</div>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01nh4t1T1g6dyI3Ikcn_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="live-data-tracking" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2>Add Role</h2>
<ul>
<li>Click on <code>Add Role</code> button</li>
<li>In the pop-up menu, find the UID you want to add, and click on the add button to its right</li>
<li>Now, the game UID character's Real-time Notes should be displayed in the page
<ul>
<li>The Real-time Notes is set to refresh timely. You can click on the <code>Notification Settings</code> on the top right to manage it</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>If you want to see the data at this moment, you can click <code>Refresh</code> button to refresh data immediately</li>
<li>If a <code>-1034</code> error occurs during data refresh, it means that miHoYo's anti-bot risk control has been triggered. You can solve this problem by configuring the invisible verification in the Hutao settings.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Verify Current User and Role</h2>
<p>If you are using a MiYouShe account, then you account is very likely to be marked as robot-usage and leads to an anti-bot
verification. In this status, Real-time Notes data cannot be updated.</p>
<p>You can click on <code>Verify Current User and Role</code> button, Snap Hutao will pop up verification window. After finishing the
verification, then your account can be used to refresh data.</p>
<h2>Global Notification Settings</h2>
<ul>
<li>In the <code>Notification Settings</code> on the top right, you can change the global settings of Real-time Notes, including:
<ul>
<li>Enable/Disable auto refresh</li>
<li>Refresh rate</li>
<li>Do not disturb setting</li>
<li>Prioritized notification
<ul>
<li>This prevent Snap Hutao's notification being closed automatically</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Customized data forwarding Webhook
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao allows user to forward Realtime Notes data to other applications to reduce account's request to MiHoYo API</li>
<li>Input your third party HTTP API endpoint in <code>Realtime Notes Webhook Url</code> setting field, and Snap Hutao will forward the raw data through <code>POST</code> requests</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Independent Settings for Each Accounts</h2>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao allows different settings on each Real-time Notes account</li>
<li>Hover the cursor over the form of Real-time Notes account that needs to set</li>
<li>Click on the setting button on it, and you can modify these settings:
<ul>
<li>Original Resin threshold value</li>
<li>Realm Currency threshold value</li>
<li>Parametric Transformer notification</li>
<li>Daily Commission notification</li>
<li>Expeditions notification</li>
<li>Display in the main page (feature coming soon)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Click on <code>Save</code> and you can save the settings</li>
</ul>
<h2>Delete Daily-Notes Account</h2>
<ul>
<li>Hover the cursor over the form of Real-time Notes account that needs to delete</li>
<li>Clock on the remove button on it, and you can remove the corresponding account</li>
</ul>
<h2>FAQ</h2>
<h3>Why does setting up automatic refresh of real-time notes prompt "Failed to modify Scheduled Task"</h3>
<p>The automatic refresh of real-time notes relies on task scheduling. In order to avoid possible permission issues, Snap Hutao will force scheduled tasks to be set in non-administrator mode.</p>
<p>If you turned on automatic refresh in the old version, you can solve the problem by manually deleting the old task schedule in Task Scheduler. The name of the scheduled task is <code>SnapHutaoDailyNoteRefreshTask</code>.</p>
<p>If you did not turn on automatic refresh in the old version, then this problem is caused by the Windows user account you are currently using having insufficient permissions. If your current user account is an administrator account, you can only solve this problem by reinstalling the system.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01nh4t1T1g6dyI3Ikcn_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Characters</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-data.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-data.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">My Characters</source>
      <description>The &amp;quot;My Characters&amp;quot; feature in Snap Hutao can retrieve and display specific data of the characters owned within a Genshin Impact account. It provides analytical data such as character level, constellations, talents, and artifact attributes.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 03:38:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Info</p>
<p>This features required sign in to MiHoYo BBS account, please refer to <a href="/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html" target="_blank">MiHoYo BBS Account Switch</a> document for sign in tutorial</p>
</div>
<p>My characters is a character statistics feature that allows Snap Hutao to read character's statistics on the account,
including level, constellation, weapon, talent and artifact set.</p>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01SpkZag1g6e0sAYQKO_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="My Character Screenshot" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2>Sync Character Data</h2>
<p>Recommended usage:</p>
<ol>
<li>Use <code>Sync from MiHoYo BBS - Battle Chronicle</code></li>
<li>Use <code>Sync from MiHoYo BBS - Enhancement Progression Calculator</code></li>
<li>Edit the showcase in the game and then <code>Sync from Enka API</code></li>
</ol>
<h3>Sync from Enka API</h3>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Synchronous Feature</p>
<ul>
<li>Enka API sync data from characters displayed in the in-game character showcase
<ul>
<li>Data includes Artifacts detail data, weapon detail data, talent data</li>
<li>Character costume</li>
<li>This sync method only support 8 characters at a time</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<ul>
<li>In the game, put <strong>characters that you need detailed data</strong> into the showcase
<ul>
<li>The character showcase allows up to 8 characters at the same time</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>You need to wait for data sync to complete after editing the showcase configuration
<ul>
<li>You may need up to 5 minutes after enable the showcase or re-config the showcase</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Enter <code>My Characters</code> page in the Snap Hutao, Click <code>Sync Character Data</code> button on the top-right</li>
<li>Select <code>Sync from Enka API</code></li>
</ul>
<h3>Sync from MiHoYo BBS - Battle Chronicle</h3>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Synchronous Feature</p>
<ul>
<li>Data in this sync method comes from My Characters feature in MiHoYo official BSS
<ul>
<li>This method does not contain any artifacts data</li>
<li>This method can sync all characters data at a time</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Enter <code>My Characters</code> page in the Snap Hutao, Click <code>Sync Character Data</code> button on the top-right</li>
<li>Select <code>Sync from MiHoYo BBS My Characters</code></li>
</ul>
<h3>Sync from MiHoYo BBS - Enhancement Progression Calculator</h3>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Synchronous Feature</p>
<ul>
<li>Data in this method comes from <code>Enhancement Progression Calculator</code> feature in MiHoYo official BBS tool set
<ul>
<li>This sync method contains talent level data</li>
<li>This sync method can sync all characters data at a time</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Enter <code>My Characters</code> page in the Snap Hutao, Click <code>Sync Character Data</code> button on the top-right</li>
<li>Select <code>Sync from MiHoYo BBS Developement Plan</code></li>
</ul>
<h2>Comparison of Synchronization Methods</h2>
<p>|       <strong>Comparison</strong>        | <strong>In-game Showcase (Enka API)</strong> | <strong>Battle Chronicle</strong> | <strong>Enhancement Progression Calculator</strong> |
| :</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01SpkZag1g6e0sAYQKO_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character WIKI</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-wiki.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-wiki.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Character WIKI</source>
      <description>The &amp;quot;Character Wiki&amp;quot; feature in Snap Hutao includes comprehensive information about all the characters in Genshin Impact. It provides essential data such as base information, talent values, constellations, and other important details. This feature helps players easily access and gather information about different characters in the game.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 03:38:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01NbT4Kn1g6e0wf51ft_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="characters-wiki" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Character WIKI is a Snap Hutao build-in WIKI feature used to query each character's information.</p>
<h2>Included Data</h2>
<ul>
<li>Character list
<ul>
<li>Use the icon above the list, you can change the view between <code>list</code> and <code>grid</code></li>
<li>Click on character's icon or title, and you will be directed to its WIKI page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Character information
<ul>
<li>Character information
<ul>
<li>Introduction of the character</li>
<li>Numerical attributes value at each level</li>
<li>Attributes</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Talent
<ul>
<li>Introduction</li>
<li>Numerical talent value at each level</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Constellation</li>
<li>statistical information on <strong>Team, weapon usage, artifact set usage</strong> provided by Hutao Database</li>
<li>Other information
<ul>
<li>Character tachie</li>
<li>Special food</li>
<li>Costume</li>
<li>Character stories</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Add to Dev Plan</h2>
<ul>
<li>At character WIKI page, you can select character and click on <code>Dev Plan</code> on the top right to add it to your Dev Plan
<ul>
<li>The new plan will set the base level as <code>1</code></li>
<li>If you want to make new Dev Plan based on character you already have, you can try <a href="/en/features/character-data.html" target="_blank">My Character</a> feature</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01NbT4Kn1g6e0wf51ft_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Launcher</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/game-launcher.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/game-launcher.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Game Launcher</source>
      <description>The game launcher within Snap Hutao offers additional features that enhance the gaming experience beyond what the official launcher provides. In addition to allowing users to add custom launch parameters, it also includes features such as server switching and unlocking frame rates. These features significantly improve the overall gaming experience.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 03:12:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01RuSYDm1g6e0u3wfIy_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="Game Launcher" loading="lazy"></p>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao offers advanced game launcher feature allows user to launch the game with self-defined settings</li>
<li>Click on the <code>Game Launcher</code> on the sidebar to get into game launcher's page
<ul>
<li>If you are using it at the first time, you will be redirected to Snap Hutao settings page and asked to set your game path
<ul>
<li>When choosing the game path, noticed that you should choose game program instead of launcher program
<ul>
<li>Such as <code>$\Genshin Impact\Genshin Impact Game\YuanShen.exe</code> and <code>$\Genshin Impact\Genshin Impact Game\Genshin Impact.exe</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>You can make launcher configuration options in the game launcher's page, and then click <code>Launcher</code> button on the top-right to launch the game. Launcher options is explained in the document below</li>
</ul>
<h2>Server Switch</h2>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Privilege Notice</p>
<ol>
<li>You need to run Snap Hutao as administrator to use this feature</li>
<li>Snap Hutao will create <code>ServerCache</code> folder in the data directory to save required sever switch files</li>
</ol>
</div>
<p>Enter Game Launcher page
In the <code>Server</code> field, select the server you want</p>
<p>Current available serves options include:
| Option | Server |
|</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01RuSYDm1g6e0u3wfIy_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Agreement and Legal Notices</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/tos.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/tos.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">User Agreement and Legal Notices</source>
      <description>User agreement and legal notices of Snap Hutao project.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 14:59:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>General Provisions</h2>
<ul>
<li>This "User Agreement and Legal Disclaimer" (hereinafter referred to as "Terms" or "User Agreement") applies to all software works developed by the DGP-Studio development team (hereinafter referred to as "the team" or "we"), the official website of each development project, and affiliated self-hosted media accounts.
<ul>
<li>Please read all the contents of this User Agreement carefully. If you have any objections to any terms of this User Agreement after reading it, please immediately stop using any projects developed by the team.</li>
<li>If you are under 18 years old, please read and fully understand this agreement with the accompaniment of a legal guardian, and obtain the consent of the legal guardian before using any projects developed by the team.</li>
<li>If you have installed, used, or referenced any projects developed by the team during development, it means that you have actively read (read it completely) and fully agree to the terms listed in this User Agreement, that is, you have fully understood this Agreement and promised to accept the constraints of the agreement, legal statements, privacy policies, rules, norms, statements, notices, and other content related to any projects developed by the team.</li>
<li>This "User Agreement" is a user agreement and legal disclaimer entered into by the user (hereinafter referred to as "you") and any projects developed by the team. This agreement has legal effect on both the user and the team.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Nature of the Project, Services, and Definition of Responsibilities and Obligations</h2>
<ol>
<li>
<p>As all projects developed by the team are "open-source" and "non-business" in nature, the team can make full decisions at any time, including but not limited to changing the "User Agreement" and modifying any content within any projects developed by the team. If there are any changes to the "Terms" or the content of the works, we will post notices on the relevant project display website. The revised "Terms" will take effect automatically after they are published on the official website.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The development of this software is aimed at "learning development knowledge" and "accumulating development experience." All functions provided by all projects are "open-source" and "non-business" in nature. If you are dissatisfied with the security of any projects developed by the team, please uninstall/delete/stop using them immediately. If you continue to use them normally, it means that you approve of the security of any projects developed by the team.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Any "unexpected losses (including but not limited to: software, hardware, property, virtual items, etc.)", "contractual damage", "defamation", "copyright or intellectual property infringement," and the resulting losses and liabilities caused by the use of any content in any projects developed by the team are all "losses and liabilities" caused by the user's own use behavior of open-source software on the Internet. Based on the MIT license declared in all works at their open-source location (i.e., GitHub) and the content stipulated in this declaration, it should be deemed that the aforementioned "losses and liabilities" have no responsibility relationship with all the relevant developers of the projects.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During the user's use of any projects developed by the team, the team does not make any guarantees that do not occur under the following circumstances:</p>
<ul>
<li>The user cannot use or update normally due to network conditions, communication lines, and other technical reasons;</li>
<li>Negative results caused by using "plug-ins in this software developed by a third party," "modified versions of this software compiled by a third party," and "software compiled by reusing project code created by this development team."</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Users acknowledge that any project developed by our team requires active user trigger for any information upload, except for necessary upload reports or related information in passive receipt of software or other related projects.</p>
<ul>
<li>Users acknowledge that any project developed by our team fully respects and protects the "personal privacy rights" of all users. The project code is also fully open, and users do not have subjective reasons to accuse the development team or team members of "violation of privacy rights".</li>
<li>Any personal information of users will not be shared or transferred to third parties by any project developed by our team, unless with the user's prior authorization or the shared and transferred personal information has been de-identified and the third party cannot re-identify the natural person subject of such information.</li>
<li>Any project developed by our team contains links to other sites. When you visit third-party links, please read the user agreement and statement of the third-party site carefully. Our team is not responsible for the content, privacy terms, and usage agreements of third-party sites.</li>
<li>When using any project developed by our team, we cannot guarantee that the information you submit will be saved successfully. You need to properly store and keep the information you submit. Some projects developed by our team provide storage for "authorized data," but there are various force majeure factors in the storage process. Our team cannot promise to keep users' stored information indefinitely. Please back up your important information yourself.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<h1>Rights and Obligations</h1>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<p>Our team allows any individual or organization to conduct secondary development, functional modification, and reuse of our code for other projects without our team's authorization, for any project developed by our team. However, we reserve the right to pursue legal action against any infringement of our team's computer software copyright.</p>
<ul>
<li>Our team shall not be responsible for any consequences resulting from the public release of the contents of any project developed by our team (including but not limited to video production, articles with content of this software, uploading to download sites not designated by our development team, etc.) by any individual or organization using the project developed by our team.</li>
<li>Our team shall not be responsible for any consequences resulting from the use of "third-party subsidiary programs or additional code that can be used for any project developed by our team", "modified versions of any project developed by our team that have been compiled by third parties", or "software compiled using the project code created by our development team".</li>
<li>Based on the legal definitions of "computer software" and "documents" in Article 2 and Article 3 of the "Regulations on the Protection of Computer Software," DGP Studio reserves all computer software copyright for all of our development projects. This includes but is not limited to all information necessary to construct the project and all document data related to the project (i.e. program design specifications, flowcharts, user manuals, etc.), with the actual content subject to the "Computer Software Copyright Registration Certificate" for each project.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Any project developed by our team is only intended for lawful and compliant learning and research use and shall not be used for illegal activities.</p>
<ul>
<li>Our team is only a development team (not a legal entity composed of natural persons), and shall not be held responsible for any joint liability for any use of the software or any project developed by our team that results in any legal consequences.</li>
<li>If a user has already started using any project developed by our team, it means that they have agreed to the "Usage Agreement" and that our team has already fulfilled the notification requirements in Section 10 of this Usage Agreement.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Copyright of the developed projects.</p>
<ul>
<li>Our software development team holds the ownership of all trademarks in the software itself (excluding display content other than functional modules), all historical versions of the aforementioned works, and the surrounding websites. We also hold any related rights and interests regarding copyright.</li>
<li>All statistical data of any project developed by our team comes from users who submit data voluntarily. After the data is screened, it is displayed. Therefore, our team is not responsible for the accuracy of the data, and the data is not related to us.</li>
<li>During the use of any project developed by our team, there may be data that has original copyright. For these data, our team does not own their ownership. In order to avoid infringement, the user has the obligation to fully read and comply with the content of Section 10 of this Usage Agreement. The resources used in this software (including but not limited to fonts, images, and text) are from public information on the Internet. If infringement occurs, you can contact us at our GitHub to remove it.</li>
<li>Snap Hutao program and hut.ao website are not affiliated with miHoYo.</li>
<li>The copyright of Genshin Impact's game content and various materials and trademarks belongs to miHoYo.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>Other Terms</h2>
<ol start="9">
<li>
<p>Determination of "Non-Business Nature" of Projects Developed by the Team.</p>
<ul>
<li>Any project developed by the team has no business nature.</li>
<li>If individual or certain members of the development team, during their participation in the development of any project developed by the team, have entered into relationships with third-party users, including but not limited to gifts, exchanges, sales, etc., the resulting relationships are unrelated to the development team. This occurrence is not based on the fact that the team developed a related project, but rather on independent events that occurred at the location where the user entered into the aforementioned relationship on the Internet or in reality. The nature of this behavior should be determined based on the user terms of use at the Internet interaction location where the aforementioned relationship occurred, or in combination with specific behaviors that occurred in reality.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Any project (including websites) developed by the team is developed for the purpose of "learning development knowledge" and "accumulating development experience," and is only for learning and communication purposes. It is strictly prohibited to use it for commercial purposes. After downloading or viewing the learning materials, please delete all related information within 24 hours. If you ignore this requirement, the software development team is not responsible for "possible copyright disputes, infringement of intellectual property rights, and civil disputes."</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The establishment, effectiveness, performance, interpretation, and dispute resolution of this agreement shall be governed by the laws of the mainland of the People's Republic of China. If any provision of this agreement conflicts with the laws of the People's Republic of China and is invalid, these provisions will be reinterpreted as closely as possible to the original intent of this agreement. The other provisions of this agreement shall remain in full force and effect.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The place of signing this agreement is Liaohe Oilfield Mining Area, Panjin City, Liaoning Province, China. If a dispute arises in the performance of this agreement, the parties shall resolve it through consultation. If no agreement can be reached through consultation, the Liaohe People's Court shall have jurisdiction, and the appellant shall bear the costs of each stage immediately.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The titles (including subtitles) in this agreement are for convenience and reading only and do not affect the meaning or interpretation of any provisions of this agreement.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Both you and the development team are independent entities, and under no circumstances does this agreement constitute any express or implied guarantee or condition of the development team towards users. There is also no agency, partnership, joint venture, or employment relationship between the two parties.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In this "User Agreement and Legal Statement," the term "our party" or "the development team" (as distinguished from "you" or "the user") refers to the entire team of DGP-Studio Development Team, including each individual member.</p>
</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/tos.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hutao Database / Abyss Record</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-API.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-API.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Hutao Database / Abyss Record</source>
      <description>The built-in Hutao Database feature in Snap Hutao is a database that helps players archive and query data for Abyssal Domains challenges. Players can easily obtain and locally archive data for each period of Abyssal Domains challenges with a single click, and submit the data to the Hutao Abyss Database.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao offers two major statistic features associated with Spiral Abyss challenge</p>
<ul>
<li><code>Statistics</code> on the top function bar is a feature designed to help players who are not familiar with Genshin Impact's battle system to build teams, pass the Abyss and obtain rewards by collecting and displaying challenge stats data from the Spiral Abyss from a large number of players.</li>
<li><code>Schedules Details</code> on the sidebar is a statistical feature that helps individuals review their gaming experience and personal data collection by saving their challenge data from each period of the Spiral Abyss.
<ul>
<li>Many players contribute to the Hutao Database's <code>Statistics</code> dataset by uploading their personal <code>Schedules Details</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>

<h2>View Abyss Stats</h2>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Data Scope Limitation</p>
<p>All calculated data are based on the player data <strong>uploaded to the Hutao Database</strong> and cannot represent the average
data of <strong>all</strong> Genshin Impact players. The data is for reference only.</p>
</div>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Stats Data Refresh Cycle</p>
<ol>
<li>Abyss Stats (character usage, character appearance, teams appearance) wil be automatically reset on 1st and 16th day
of each month on the gaming server timezone of your account
<ul>
<li>You can view real-time total uploaded data by clicking <code>Details</code> button in the <code>Abyss Stats</code> page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>If user does not upload its record for 30 days, its character constellation data will be reset in the database</li>
</ol>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Enter Abyss Records page, and then click <code>Stastics</code> on the top function bar</li>
<li>Click <code>Character Usage</code> tab to view character usage rate statistics
<ul>
<li>Character Usage Rate = Character Appearance in this Floor <sup class="footnote-ref"><a href="#footnote1">[1]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"></a></sup><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"> / Number of Player who Own this Character</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">Click <code>Character Appearance</code> tab to view character appearance rate statistics
</a><ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">Character Appearance Rate = Character Appearance in this Floor <sup class="footnote-ref"></sup></a><a href="#footnote2">[2]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2"> / Total Number of Abyss Record of this Floor</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">
</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">
<li>Click <code>Teams</code> tab to view teams appearance time statistics
<ul>
<li>Team appearance is the appearance time rank of different characters team combination</li>
</ul>
</li>
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">Click <code>Character Constellation</code> tab to view character constellation statistics <sup class="footnote-ref"></sup></a><a href="#footnote3">[3]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
</a><ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">Character Constellation <sup class="footnote-ref"></sup></a><a href="#footnote4">[4]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref4"> = Number of Player who Own this Character / Total Number of Player</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref4">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref4">
</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref4">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref4">
</a><h2><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref4"></a><a class="header-anchor" href="#upload-abyss-data"><span>Upload Abyss Data</span></a></h2>
<h3>Use Snap Hutao Client</h3>
<div class="hint-container important">
<p class="hint-container-title">Snap Hutao Cloud Bonus</p>
<p>If you have already logged into your Snap Hutao Account in your client, after successfully submitting data for the first time in the current schedule, you will receive Snap Hutao Cloud privileges as our thanks (even if the data has not cleared the 12th floor).</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Enter Abyss Records page by clicking <code>Abyss Records</code> on the sidebar menu</li>
<li>Click <code>Refresh Data</code> button to make suer Snap Hutao is storing your latest Spiral Abyss record</li>
<li>Click <code>Upload Data</code> to upload your Spiral Abyss records
<ul>
<li>This may take a few seconds, you will receive a submission success notification</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Use Browser</h3>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Info</p>
<p>This method does not support HoYoLAB</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Open our <a href="/upload-abyss-data.js">JavaScript file</a>, copy the entire content</li>
<li>Create new bookmark in your browser
<ul>
<li>Fill with a suitable name</li>
<li>in the <code>URL</code> field, fill with script you just copied
<img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01p0KOqU1g6dvfDQO6e_!!1797064093.png" alt="add-bookmark" loading="lazy"></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Visit MiYouShe, wait the page to be fully loaded, and then click the bookmark</li>
<li>Wait for a moment, and you will see data upload request window</li>
<li>After confirm it, the browser will upload your abyss record, do not turn off your browser</li>
<li>You will receive a notification when your data is submitted</li>
</ul>
<h2>Data Sharing</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao is contributing data to Hutao Database with other developers. You can view our Abyss Stats, and upload your
Abyss data in multiple applications other than Snap Hutao.
Currently, Snap Hutao is sharing Abyss data with following applications:</p>
<div class="vp-card-container">
</div>
<hr class="footnotes-sep">
<section class="footnotes">
<ol class="footnotes-list">
<li id="footnote1" class="footnote-item"><p>When same character appearances in the same floor but different level, appearance time only count for 1 <a href="#footnote-ref1" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
<li id="footnote2" class="footnote-item"><p>When same character appearances in the same floor but different level, appearance time only count for 1 <a href="#footnote-ref2" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
<li id="footnote3" class="footnote-item"><p>Character constellation data is a separate data set from Spiral Abyss records database <a href="#footnote-ref3" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
<li id="footnote4" class="footnote-item"><p>Once owned this character, it's counted into database even it's not appearing in Spiral Abyss; Once upload your
Abyss stats, all collected characters will be included <a href="#footnote-ref4" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</section>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN018nOrg11g6e0wP73lR_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiHoYo BBS Account Switch</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">MiHoYo BBS Account Switch</source>
      <description>The Multi-account Panel feature in Snap Hutao allows users to log in with multiple miHoYo BBS accounts within the toolbox and switch between them freely. This enables users to utilize various functions within Snap Hutao with different accounts for specific purposes.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 04:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>There are two types of MiHoYo BBS, MiYouShe and HoYoLAB.
MiYouShe refers to Mainland China version, HoYoLAB refers to global version, both of them are accepted by Snap Hutao</p>
<ul>
<li>The document in page is talking about <strong>MiHoYo BBS account</strong>, not Genshin Impact's <strong>in-game account</strong></li>
<li>Before starting using Snap Hutao, you must initial your MiHoYo BBS account by login to your account in official mobile application
<ul>
<li>If your account name shows like <code>user_123456789</code>, then it means the account is not initial yet</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01QN2Nvm1g6e0utHzYa_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="MiHoYo BBS Accounts" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>At the left bottom corner, you can find the account menu above the <code>Settings</code> button. In the pop-up account menu,
you can find the entry to login in to your MiYouShe and HoYoLAB account:</p>
<ul>
<li>Click on <code>Web Login</code>
<ul>
<li>In the pop-up build-in browser, login with your account</li>
<li>Click <code>I'm logged in</code> button on the top right, after you have logged into your account</li>
<li>Then your account will be added to Snap Hutao, the browser will close automatically</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Alternatively, you can enter your MiHoYo BBS cookie list by click on <code>Input Manually</code> button
<ul>
<li>If you do so, the cookies must contains <code>SToken</code> field</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After added your MiHoYo BBS account, you need to switch to account you want in the account menu, to activate it
<ul>
<li>You can always switch your MiHoYo BBS account in the account menu, and you are also allowed to copy account's cookie or remove account there</li>
<li>After select an account in the panel, you can also
<ul>
<li>Click <code>Refresh Cookie</code> to update local cookie</li>
<li>Click <code>Claim Check-In Reward</code> to get daily check-in reward. For MiYouShe account, you need to bypass Geetest verification first.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Security Tips</p>
<ul>
<li><code>SToken</code> is a security sensitive cookie field, you <strong>should NEVER</strong> store it in cloud-based software or device that you cannot guarantee the safety (such as public computers).</li>
<li>You can copy accounts' cookie with <code>SToken</code> from Snap Hutao, but you should carefully consider if the receiver is trustworthy to have <code>SToken</code> cookie</li>
<li><strong>When you are signing in to your MiHoYo BBS account in Snap Hutao, the data are only been processed by MiHoYo's official server and local Snap Hutao program,
no third-party server (including any server from Snap Hutao) will involve in this process.</strong></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2>FAQ</h2>
<h3>MiHoYo BBS Account often Lose Login Status</h3>
<p>Snap Hutao use saved MiHoYo BBS cookies to maintain login status. If you <strong>log out</strong> your account in your browser or
other device, cookie will become invalid, and Snap Hutao will also be forced to log out, account will be automatically
removed.</p>
<p>This problem may also be caused by network error, you should check this first; If it's not caused by network issue,
you can use <code>Refresh Cookie</code> in the account panel; You can also remove your account manually and add it back again.</p>
<p>Since October 2022, MiYouShe (Chinese BBS) rapidly increased bot detection and may set users' account as under-risk status,
this may cause Snap Hutao failed to check validation of the cookie</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Features</source>
      <description>In the Feature directory, you can find a comprehensive list of all the features currently available in Snap Hutao. You can refer to this directory to search for the corresponding documentation of each feature based on your specific needs.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 02:37:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statements</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Statements</source>
      <description>This page contains the toc of statements and announcements of Snap Hutao project.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 02:37:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Snap Hutao project does NOT support, participate in, or cooperate with any project related to Genshin Impact's private server and cheating program.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gacha System and Export Principle</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Gacha System and Export Principle</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao utilizes various methods to obtain users&amp;apos; login information and combines it with the Genshin Impact API to retrieve gacha records.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 01:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao's Gacha system underwent an overhaul compared to Snap Genshin, experiencing a complete architectural redesign.</p>
<p>This article will explain the Genshin's wish logging mechanism and the technical principles behind the Gacha export feature in the Snap Hutao.</p>
<h2>Obtaining Wishes</h2>
<p>Acquiring wish records requires querying miHoYo's API.</p>
<p>Regarding this API, there are a few key points to note:</p>
<ul>
<li>Through miHoYo's server API, you can only access wish records from the past 6 months.
<ul>
<li>This is also the source of wish records in the original Genshin client.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>The API has rate limits; too many requests too quickly can lead to subsequent failures, making it impossible to retrieve data.</li>
</ul>
<p>To request this API, we need four crucial parameters.</p>
<ul>
<li>Currently, several methods can obtain these parameters:
<ul>
<li>Traversing Unity's log files to find URLs for wish records opened by the user</li>
<li>Proxying local traffic to filter wish record URLs</li>
<li>Looking through the CefBrowser's browser cache to find wish record URLs</li>
<li>For Cookies containing Stoken, calling the genAuthKey API to obtain parameters</li>
<li>Advanced users manually inputting relevant URLs</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Upon requesting the API, you receive fragmented wish records. Concatenating them provides a complete wish record list.</p>
<h2>Wish Storage</h2>
<p>After obtaining the complete wish record list, you can easily serialize it into a local database. When necessary, deserialization from the database presents it to the user.</p>
<p>Subsequent requests to the server only need to compare new data requests against the database's existing data.</p>
<p>This way, users can permanently store their account's complete wish records.</p>
<h2>UIGF Format</h2>
<blockquote>
<p>Unified Interchangeable GachaLog Format</p>
</blockquote>
<p>UIGF is a unified wish record data exchange standard, advocated, launched, and <strong>persistently maintained</strong> by us in collaboration with other wish record applications.</p>
<p>Standardized data formats enable users to transfer wish records between different tools for Genshin, each leveraging its distinctive functionalities.</p>
<h3>Importing Wishes</h3>
<p>When utilizing the UIGF data format, you can import data previously stored in other applications.</p>
<p>Hutao, during import handling, compares the earliest index (ID) existing in local storage and only imports older data.</p>
<p>(This is because newer data of higher precision is always available from miHoYo's servers.)</p>
<h3>Exporting Wishes</h3>
<p>Snap Hutao exports wish records in the UIGF data format in Json file, allowing users to share their wish records with others or import them into other applications.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/project.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/project.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Project</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao is an open-source program project, and we widely accept collaborations from the community to keep the project dynamic.</description>
      <category>announcement</category>
      <category>project</category>
      <category>features</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div style="text-align:center">
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01eHCaOA1g6e2ZLa3PA_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="banner" loading="lazy">
<a href="https://trendshift.io/repositories/2009" target="_blank"><img src="https://trendshift.io/api/badge/repositories/2009" alt="DGP-Studio%2FSnap.Hutao | Trendshift" style="width: 250px; height: 55px;" width="250" height="55"></a></p>
</div>
<p>Snap Hutao is an open-source Genshin Impact toolkit under MIT license, designed for modern Windows platform to improve
the gaming experience for desktop players. By combining existing official resources with new features designed by the
development team, it provides a complete and useful set of tools without the need to rely on mobile devices. Snap Hutao
does not take any destructive modification to the game client to ensure the security of the toolkit.</p>
<p>Snap Hutao is using MSIX format package. MSIX is a native Windows application package format that streamlines the installation, update, and removal process of software. One of its standout features is its use of sandbox technology. This means that applications packaged in MSIX run in isolated environments, preventing them from making system-wide changes. This isolation enhances security as it limits the application's access to system resources and user data. Furthermore, when an MSIX-packaged application is uninstalled, it leaves no residual files or registry entries, maintaining the cleanliness and stability of the system. This is a significant improvement over traditional installation methods that often leave behind "digital debris" when applications are removed. The combination of these features makes MSIX a powerful tool for both developers and end-users, providing a seamless, secure, and clean software management experience.</p>
<h2>Genshin Impact's Desktop Issues Snap Hutao Solved</h2>
<p>|           Feature            | Mobile                                 | Desktop                                         | Snap Hutao Solution                                                      |
| :</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01mpzxPR1g6e22IjFMh_!!1797064093.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achievement Management</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/achievements.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/achievements.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Achievement Management</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao provides the functionality to manage Genshin Impact achievements. With it, you can browse and manage the status of all achievements. Using its powerful filtering system, you can easily search for specific achievements based on version number, achievement name, achievement description, and region affiliation.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01Jxk0x31g6e0wP6SNL_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="Achievement Screenshot" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Snap Hutao offers local achievement management feature, users can view and manage status of achievement</p>
<p>At first time use, you will follow the instruction to create an archive and name it. After that, you are still able to make new archives by click on <code>Create New Archive</code> for other game accounts</p>
<h2>Achievement Import </h2>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao is using <a href="https://uigf.org/en/standards/UIAF.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Uniformed Interchangeable Achievement Format Standar</a> to store user's achievement data
<ul>
<li>This standard allows user to transmit achievement data between Snap Hutao wiht other achievement tools, such as <strong>Achievement exporter</strong></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>You can click on <code>Import</code> at top right menu on Achievement Management page, and select file import to load UIAF formatted data</li>
</ul>
<h2>Achievement Export </h2>
<p>You can click on the <code>Export</code> button in the hidden menu in the top right corner of the achievement page. In the pop-up window, select the directory and set the file name, then your data will be exported.</p>
<h2>Delete Archive</h2>
<p>You can delete the current achievement archive by finding and clicking on <code>Delete Current Archive</code> in the hidden menu in the top right corner.</p>
<h2>Achievement Tools We Recommend</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p><a href="https://github.com/HolographicHat/YaeAchievement" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">YaeAchievement</a> </p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://cocogoat.work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">æ¤°ç¾Š cocogoat</a> </p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01Jxk0x31g6e0wP6SNL_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wish History</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/wish-export.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/wish-export.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Wish History</source>
      <description>The Wish Export feature allows players to freely export their current wish data from their game accounts and permanently store and backup it locally. This enables long-term data accumulation for tracking and analyzing wish data.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Gacha is one of the core gameplay in Genshin Impact. Whether it's for commemorative and show-off purposes,
or for serious planning for a gacha strategy, it's very important to perform statical analysis on historical gacha record.
However, Genshin Impact only provides players with six months of gacha records, which is not user-friendly <s>(although they
still keep tracking how many Timmie's pigeons you've killed for the whole year)</s></p>
<p>Therefore, we need to use the gacha records from these six months to retrieve the data and transfer the record to our
local device. This is the purpose of wish history export feature in Snap Hutao.</p>
<p>Regarding the technical principles of exporting Genshin Impact gacha records,
you can refer to our article on <a href="/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html" target="_blank">Gacha System and Export Principles</a></p>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01X360be1g6e0wf4UNv_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="wish export" loading="lazy"></p>
<p><strong>As shown in the above figure, through the wish history feature in Snap Hutao, you can clearly obtain the following information:
total number of wishes, current pity count, quantity and percentage of obtained items with different rarity, number of
times a 5-star rarity item was not obtained and the current pity status.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Additionally, user with Hutao Cloud can view prediction data calculated by Hutao Cloud server</strong></p>
<div class="hint-container note">
<p class="hint-container-title">Delay in Gacha Data Export</p>
<p>Snap Hutao retrieves gacha records from the MiHoYo servers, which means that recently made wishes may not be immediately
available. When you see the latest batch of gacha records in the game's own history, then you can then obtain the corresponding
statistics from Snap Hutao.</p>
</div>
<h2>Fetch Wish History</h2>
<h3>SToken Refresh </h3>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Hint</p>
<ul>
<li>This method requires user to sign in to MiHoYo BBS account in Snap Hutao, refer to
<a href="/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html" target="_blank">MiHoYo BBS Account Switch</a> to get to know how to sign in to your MiHoYo BBS account</li>
<li><strong>SToken Cookie refresh method does not support oversea server (HoYoLAB)</strong></li>
</ul>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Make sure the account you want to refresh wish history has been signed in to Snap Hutao</li>
<li>Switch to <code>Wish History</code> feature page in Snap Hutao</li>
<li>Click on <code>Refresh</code> button and select <code>SToken Refresh</code></li>
<li>Wait for refresh task to complete</li>
</ul>
<h3>Refresh with Web Cache </h3>
<ul>
<li>Switch to <code>Wish History</code> feature page in Snap Hutao</li>
<li>Start the game, go to in-game wish history page</li>
<li>Go back to Snap Hutao, clock on <code>Refresh</code> button and select <code>Refresh with Web Cache</code></li>
<li>Wait for refresh task to complete</li>
</ul>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>If errors keep occur:</p>
<ul>
<li>Go to settings page in Snap Hutao</li>
<li>Execute operation <code>Delete game embeeded browser web cache</code></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h3>Input URL Manually </h3>
<ul>
<li>If you get your personal wish history URL, you can select <code>Manual Input</code> and submit your wish history URL</li>
<li>Be aware that the URL is time-sensitive</li>
</ul>
<h3>Full Refresh</h3>
<p>By default, Snap Hutao will stop importing gacha records once it matches a Wish ID that already exists locally.
However, if you wish to obtain all the historical records from the Genshin Impact servers
(even if they are already present in your local wish history), you can check the "Full Refresh" option.</p>
<p>Not selecting <code>Full Refresh</code> will <strong>not</strong> cause you to lose your wishing data,
and selecting <code>Full Refresh</code> will <strong>not</strong> cause your local records to mistakenly record the same wishing data twice.</p>
<h3>Import UIGF Wish History Data from Other Applications </h3>
<p>Snap Hutao supports importing wish history data file that in <code>UIGF data format</code><sup class="footnote-ref"><a href="#footnote1">[1]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"></a></sup></p><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
<p>If you need to import such type of data, you can:</p>
<ul>
<li>Start Snap Hutao, switch to <code>Wish History</code> feature page</li>
<li>Select <code>Import</code></li>
<li>Select your UIGF Json data file</li>
<li>Check the imported file information and confirm to import</li>
</ul>
</a><h2><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"></a><a class="header-anchor" href="#export-wish-history-data"><span>Export Wish History Data </span></a></h2>
<p>Snap Hutao support exporting wish history data to a Json file written in UIGF data format</p>
<p>If you need to export the wish history data, you can:</p>
<ul>
<li>Start Snap Hutao, switch to <code>Wish History</code> feature page</li>
<li>Switch to the archive you want to export, and select <code>Export</code>
<ul>
<li>In the pop-up window, confirm your export path</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Confirm and export data</li>
</ul>
<h2>Wish History Cloud Sync </h2>
<blockquote>
<p>Wish history cloud sync is designed on Snap Hutao Account.
You need to <a href="/en/features/hutao-settings.html#snap-hutao-account" target="_blank">register an account in the settings</a> to use this feature</p>
</blockquote>
<p>With this feature, you can upload your wish history to Hutao Cloud, to avoid risk of losing data, and make it easier to
transfer data between devices.</p>
<h3>Upload</h3>
<ul>
<li>In wish export page, select the archive you need to sync data</li>
<li>Click <code>Snap Hutao Cloud</code> button on the top right</li>
<li>Click <code>Upload Current Wish Archive</code>, and then your data will be backup to the cloud</li>
</ul>
<h3>Download</h3>
<ul>
<li>In wish export page, Click <code>Snap Hutao Cloud</code> button on the top right</li>
<li>Click download button on the right side of UID which data needs to be downloaded</li>
</ul>
<h3>Delete</h3>
<ul>
<li>In wish export page, Click <code>Snap Hutao Cloud</code> button on the top right</li>
<li>Click delete button on the right side of UID which data needs to be deleted</li>
</ul>
<hr class="footnotes-sep">
<section class="footnotes">
<ol class="footnotes-list">
<li id="footnote1" class="footnote-item"><p>Unified Standardized GenshinData Format is provided by <a href="https://uigf.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">UIGF-Org</a> <a href="#footnote-ref1" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</section>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01X360be1g6e0wf4UNv_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submit Bug Report</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/bug-report.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/bug-report.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Submit Bug Report</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao is an open-source program released on GitHub. We also utilize the GitHub Issues feature to collect feedback and address any issues. You can submit problem reports through GitHub Issues.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You can submit bug reports when you find reproducible issue that cannot be fixed by yourself</p>
<p>Before submitting your issue, please do the following checklist:</p>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-0" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-0"> Make sure you are in the latest version of Snap Hutao</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-1" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-1"> Check <a href="/en/advanced/FAQ.html" target="_blank">FAQ</a> document and <a href="/en/advanced/known-issue.html" target="_blank">known issues</a> document</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-2" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-2"> Search current issues in the project to see if there is same or similar issues</label></li>
</ul>
<p>If you don't get a solution from the above checklist, you can start a new issue on GitHub</p>
<p>If you need some examples of good issues, you can check them <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues?q=is%3Aissue+label%3A%E4%BC%98%E8%B4%A8%E9%97%AE%E9%A2%98+is%3Aclosed" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a></p>
<ul>
<li>Submit your issue on GitHub
<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/new/choose" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/new/choose</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>You should include these information in your issue:
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-3" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-3"> Your device ID</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-4" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-4"> Your operating system version</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-5" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-5"> Describe your issue in details, so the developer can replicate your problem</label>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-6" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-6"> How the issue being triggered?</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-7" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-7"> Is there any error or warning message from the program or your OS?</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-8" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-8"> Have you done any debug process by yourself? What's the outcome?</label></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-9" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-9"> If your issue is about program crash, you need to find <code>.NET error</code> on Snap Hutao in your Windows Event Viewer,
and include it in your issue</label></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Request Document Update</h2>
<p>If you think Snap Hutao document is missing some information or contains errors, you can start an issue on Snap.Hutao.Docs project</p>
<ul>
<li>Submit your issue on GitHubï¼š<a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs/issues/new/choose" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs</a></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/bug-report.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>