<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>Snap Hutao</title>
    <link>https://hut.ao/en/</link>
    <description>Super utilitarian Genshin Impact Toolkit</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:55:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:55:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>@vuepress/plugin-feed</generator>
    <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
    <category>FAQ</category>
    <category>Features</category>
    <category>Tutorials</category>
    <category>Feature</category>
    <category>Tutorial</category>
    <category>Open Source</category>
    <category>Development</category>
    <category>Dev Logs</category>
    <category>Functionality</category>
    <category>Announcement</category>
    <category>i18n</category>
    <category>Third-Party Tools</category>
    <category>Project</category>
    <item>
      <title>Loopback Network</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/loopback.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/loopback.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Loopback Network</source>
      <description>Introduction to Loopback Network and Solutions for Network Proxy Failures</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 04:59:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>What is Loopback Network</h2>
<p>"Appx container applications" are a type of application promoted by Microsoft, with many advantages. To ensure they are efficient, secure, stable and user-friendly, Microsoft has taken a series of restrictive measures for these applications. One of these measures is the "Loopback Network".</p>
<p>Windows by default <strong>disables Loopback Network for all Windows Appx container applications (including Snap Hutao)</strong>. This design aims to limit the network access range of applications, allowing them to only access the resources they need to operate.</p>
<h3>Understanding Loopback Network</h3>
<p>You can think of the "Loopback Network" as a "box" that an application is placed into. This "box" isolates the application's network environment from the local computer environment, allowing the application to interact with the external network only through a small hole.</p>
<p>When the external network environment changes (such as enabling a network proxy or a game accelerator), the small hole may become blocked, causing the application inside the box to be unable to communicate with the external network.</p>
<h2>Potential Issues</h2>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao cannot access the network after a proxy is enabled.</li>
<li>Certain network-related functions (such as Wish record export, Real-time Notes refresh, etc.) fail.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Solutions</h2>
<h3>1. Configure within Snap Hutao (Recommended)</h3>
<ol>
<li>Open Snap Hutao.</li>
<li>Click "Feedback Center" in the left menu.</li>
<li>In the right sidebar, find and click "Unblock Loopback Restriction".</li>
<li>Click the "Confirm" button in the pop-up window.</li>
</ol>
<p>This operation will remove the Loopback restriction, allowing Snap Hutao to use proxy networks normally.</p>
<h3>2. Configure in the Network Proxy Software</h3>
<ol>
<li>Enable <strong>TUN Mode</strong> (if your network proxy software provides this option).</li>
<li>Contact your network proxy service provider and ask for technical support on resolving network proxy issues for Windows Appx container applications to get targeted solutions.</li>
</ol>
<p>By using the methods described above, you can effectively resolve network proxy failures caused by Loopback restrictions and enable Snap Hutao to run normally in various network environments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/loopback.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imaginarium Theater</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/imaginarium-theater.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/imaginarium-theater.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Imaginarium Theater</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao&amp;apos;s built-in &amp;quot;Imaginarium Theater&amp;quot; feature allows players to record and analyze new challenge content in the game, providing detailed team setups, clear records, and server-wide statistical analysis to help players optimize their challenge strategies.</description>
      <category>Features</category>
      <category>Tutorials</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 04:59:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao's "Imaginarium Theater" feature is dedicated to providing players with data recording and statistical services for this challenge mode. Through this feature, players can archive their challenge data and participate in server-wide data statistical analysis.</p>
<p>This feature is mainly divided into the following two parts:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Phase Details</strong>: Displays the player's individual Imaginarium Theater challenge data, including detailed level progress, team configurations, clear records, etc.</li>
<li><strong>Current Phase Stats</strong>: Displays the character usage data generated by all players' challenges uploaded to the Snap Hutao database.</li>
</ul>

<h2>Viewing Personal Challenge Data (Schedule Details)</h2>
<ul>
<li>Click on the "Imaginarium Theater" page in the left menu bar, and select the "Schedule Details" tab.</li>
<li>View the challenge records for the current and past phases, including:
<ul>
<li>Opening character lineup, invited character, all standby characters, strongest strike, best record, etc.</li>
<li>The monster lineup of each act, the characters in the battle lineup, the brilliant blessings, and mysterious harvest</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Data Archiving</h3>
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao automatically archives each phase of the challenge, and players can view past challenge data to review historical performance and adjust strategies.</li>
<li>Click the "Refresh Data" button to get the latest game records.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Global Challenge Data (Current Schedule Statistics)</h2>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Data Scope</p>
<p>All statistical data is based on records uploaded by players and may not fully represent all players.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Click on the "Imaginarium Theater" page in the left menu bar, and select the "Statistics" tab.</li>
<li>View the character appearance information for this phase of the challenge.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Uploading and Sharing Data</h3>
<ol>
<li>Click the "Upload Data" button on the "Imaginarium Theater" page.</li>
<li>The system will automatically parse the latest challenge records and submit them to the Snap Hutao database.</li>
<li>After the upload is complete, players will receive a confirmation prompt.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01ykD0CZ1g6e0sAQMn1_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ðŸŽ‰ Successfully Updated to Version 1.15.12</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/latest.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/latest.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">ðŸŽ‰ Successfully Updated to Version 1.15.12</source>
      <description>ðŸŽ‰ Successfully Updated to Version 1.15.12 | English [ðŸ”¨Fix] Fixed an issue where the server switch function could not be used properly when launching the game #2941</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:54:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/zh/statements/latest.html" target="_blank">ç®€ä½“ä¸­æ–‡</a> | <strong>English</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the server switch function could not be used properly when launching the game <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2941" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2941</a></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support Us</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/support-us.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/support-us.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Support Us</source>
      <description>The Snap Hutao project accepts donations from the community to sustain its operations, and we sincerely thank everyone who has supported this project.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:13:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao, as an open-source project licensed under the MIT License, is dedicated to creating a completely free, ad-free, and privacy-focused program. Our development team members are currently self-funding the project's operation and, through modern technology, have minimized operating costs as much as possible. The current major expenses are for the network system components required for server operation (you can find our summarized annual expenditures at the bottom of this page). If you have surplus funds to support Snap Hutao, your generous donation will not only assist the development team but will also benefit every Snap Hutao user. Currently, you can donate to us through the following channels:</p>
<h2>Donation Channels</h2>
<p>We accept donations through the following methods:</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/support-us.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feedback Center</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/feedback-center.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/feedback-center.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Feedback Center</source>
      <description>The built-in Feedback Center in Snap Hutao includes important links related to the Snap Hutao project and incorporates a document search engine, helping users quickly resolve common issues.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:46:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01yGGrhz1g6e0u3q5L6_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="dashboard" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The Feedback Center is a feature page provided by the Snap Hutao development team to help users solve common problems. This page is laid out in a left-right structure.</p>
<h2>Left Side Functionality: Document Search</h2>
<p>The left side of the page provides a built-in document search entry point. Users can enter keywords in the search box to quickly find relevant pages and solutions.</p>
<h2>Right Side Functionality: Information and Links</h2>
<p>The right side of the page includes the following functional modules:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>First Section: Useful Key Information</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Device ID</strong>: Uniquely identifies the current device, often used for reporting bugs or retrieving error logs.</li>
<li><strong>Device Network Information</strong>: Includes IP address and network status.
<ul>
<li>Due to the different implementation methods of proxy software, some proxies may not be detected. Therefore, it is normal for "No proxy" to be displayed even when "Proxy enabled" is indicated.</li>
<li>The Alpha version always displays the location as Oversea, which is expected behavior.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Webview2 Runtime Version</strong>: Displays the version number of Webview2 on which Snap Hutao relies.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Second Section: Common Links</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>GitHub Issues</strong>: Quickly jump to the GitHub issue tracking page, making it easy for users to submit issues or view existing solutions.</li>
<li>Access the availability monitoring page of Snap Hutao services to understand service status.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Third Section: Function Guide</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Provides document links to the main functions of Snap Hutao, including "Home", "Launch Game", "Wish Records", "Achievement Management", etc., making it easy for users to quickly locate documentation entry points.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Interface Optimization and Precautions</h2>
<ul>
<li>If the data on the Feedback Center page is not displayed or loaded correctly, try restarting the application or checking the network connection.</li>
<li>Some display problems may be related to the user environment (such as proxy settings or system version). It is recommended to troubleshoot specific problems according to the prompts.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01yGGrhz1g6e0u3q5L6_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snap Hutao Passport</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-passport.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-passport.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Snap Hutao Passport</source>
      <description>The Snap Hutao Passport is the account system under the Snap Hutao project, which allows players to log in to the Snap Hutao Cloud system and access related benefits.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:46:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="/images/202501/hutao_account.webp" alt="account_page" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The Snap Hutao Passport is an account system created by the DGP-Studio team for Snap Hutao, used to provide cloud-based services, including the Snap Hutao Cloud Wish Record service. You can navigate to the Snap Hutao Passport page by clicking the Snap Hutao Passport button in the left menu bar of the Snap Hutao client, view and manage your Snap Hutao Passport.</p>
<h2>Cloud Service Description</h2>
<p>Cloud-related features consume a significant amount of server resources, therefore, they have time limits. Currently, Snap Hutao provides the following ways to enable cloud synchronization:</p>
<ol>
<li>For users who support Snap Hutao on AfDian, we will automatically add usage time to the Snap Hutao Passport that matches the AfDian email account as a token of appreciation from the Snap Hutao development team.
<ul>
<li>After payment, you should receive an email receipt. You can click the "Refresh" button on the right side of the Snap Hutao Passport to refresh the renewal status. Due to data synchronization delays, if the refresh fails, please wait about 5 minutes and try again.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>For all registered users, after each Genshin Impact account successfully uploads the Spiral Abyss challenge record to the Snap Hutao database for the <strong>first time in each period</strong>, you will get 3 days of Wish synchronization feature usage time.
<ul>
<li>You can use the Snap Hutao Cloud Wish Record service for free in the long term through this method.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Users who contribute to the Snap Hutao open-source community (including but not limited to code development, program design, and localization translation) can directly contact the development team to obtain a developer license or redemption code.</strong></li>
</ol>
<h2>Snap Hutao Cloud Wish Record Service</h2>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Warning</p>
<p>When your Snap Hutao Passport cloud synchronization permission expires, you will not be able to upload, download, or delete data, but your data will not be deleted. You can re-operate your cloud backup data after restoring your permissions.</p>
</div>
<p>If you have Snap Hutao Cloud permission, you will have the following privileges:</p>
<ol>
<li>The "Prediction" feature on the Wish Record page</li>
<li>Cloud synchronization feature of Wish records</li>
</ol>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Snap Hutao Passport and Genshin Impact Account Relationship</p>
<p>Note: The relationship between Genshin Impact account data and Snap Hutao Passport is "<strong>many-to-one</strong>". That is, one Snap Hutao Passport can be associated with the Wish data of multiple Genshin Impact accounts, but one Genshin Impact account can only be associated with one Snap Hutao Passport.</p>
<p>If you are unable to upload wish records due to reasons such as purchasing a second-hand account, please negotiate with the previous account holder for data security reasons. Snap Hutao will not and cannot resolve related wish conflicts.</p>
</div>
<h2>Snap Hutao Cloud CDN Service</h2>
<p>This feature allows users to download Snap Hutao updates through servers deployed in mainland China. Usually, this method can significantly improve the download speed for users in mainland China.</p>
<h2>Change Email/Change Password/Log Out Account/Refresh Account Status</h2>
<p>Click the corresponding button according to your needs. Please note that after changing your password or email, you will be automatically logged into the modified account.</p>
<p>If you have supported Snap Hutao on websites like AfDian but your account status is not updated, you can click the "Refresh" button on the right side of the account to manually refresh the status. If the status is still not displayed correctly after waiting for 5 minutes and manually refreshing, please contact the developers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hut.ao/images/202501/hutao_account.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/join.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/join.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Join Us</source>
      <description>If you possess expertise in any of the technologies mentioned on this page and are interested in joining the Snap Hutao development team to enhance the project and engage with more open-source projects related to Genshin Impact, we welcome you to join us!</description>
      <category>Open Source</category>
      <category>Development</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you possess expertise in any of the technologies mentioned on this page and are interested in joining the Snap Hutao development team to enhance the project and engage with more Genshin Impact open-source projects, we warmly welcome you to join us!</p>
<p><strong>We do not set specific skill thresholds. A spirit of exploring new fields, a passion for technology, and a responsible attitude are the most needed qualities in the open-source community.</strong></p>
<blockquote>
<p>If you have limited time or just want to solve a specific issue, you can directly read the <a href="/en/development/contribute.html" target="_blank">Contribution Guide</a> and initiate a Pull Request. We will take every constructive code submission seriously.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2></h2>
<p><strong>DGP-Studio Member Benefits:</strong></p>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-0" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-0"> Design and implement features for Snap Hutao and associated projects</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-1" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-1"> Connect with developers of other well-known Genshin Impact community projects</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-2" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-2"> Get free GitHub Copilot</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-3" checked="checked" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-3"> Get a free 1Password Team account</label></li>
</ul>
<p>You can view the current list of public organization members on the <a href="https://github.com/orgs/DGP-Studio/people" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GitHub DGP-Studio People</a> page.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/development/join.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Logs</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/blog/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/blog/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Dev Logs</source>
      <description>Dev Logs</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 08:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/blog/version-1-9-0-breaking-changes.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/blog/version-1-9-0-breaking-changes.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0</source>
      <description>Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0 This document is applicable to users upgrading from Snap Hutao versions 1.4.11 to 1.8.4 to version 1.9.0 and higher. This docume...</description>
      <category>Dev Logs</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 08:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This document is applicable to users upgrading from Snap Hutao versions <strong>1.4.11 to 1.8.4</strong> to version 1.9.0 and higher.</p>
<div class="hint-container important">
<p class="hint-container-title">This document has been archived</p>
<p>This page has been archived. To install Snap Hutao, please visit <a href="/en/quick-start.html" target="_blank">Quick Start</a> for more information.</p>
</div>
<h2>Introduction</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao is a Windows sandbox application in MSIX format, providing the convenience of installation and the security of AppX applications. Mandatory code signing in installation packages is a crucial factor in ensuring security. If the installation package is modified, Windows App Installer will raise an error due to the signature being compromised, preventing user installation. We can see this practice everywhere in today's mobile operating systems. On the Windows platform, due to strict identity verification procedure, the prices of code signing certificates have remained high.</p>
<p>Before version 1.4.11, Snap Hutao used a self-signed certificate. In this mode, users had to manually install DGP-Studio's certificate to allow the installation of applications signed by DGP-Studio's certificate on their computers. Starting from version 1.4.11, Snap Hutao was listed on the Microsoft Store, and Microsoft provided a GUID <code>35C8E923-85DF-49A7-9172-B39DC6312C52</code> for Hutao's developer account. This GUID was used as the publisher name of Snap Hutao, providing a special free signature (only used for Microsoft Store apps). If you are accustomed to updating the Snap Hutao with MSIX packages, you should always see this GUID in the publisher column.</p>
<p>Listing on the Microsoft Store eliminated the need for Snap Hutao users to manually install the signing certificate and supported the distribution of Snap Hutao installation packages, reducing a significant amount of costs for the development team. However, the cumbersome approval process often disrupted the development plans of the Snap Hutao. Therefore, over the past six months, the development team has been seeking a solution. SignPath is a company based in Vienna, Austria, that provides code signing integration software. In early December 2023, the Snap Hutao development team successfully obtained sponsorship from the SignPath Foundation, allowing us to use their code signing certificates for Snap Hutao free of charge. This greatly assisted the Snap Hutao project by not only allowing the Snap Hutao to get rid of constraints of the Microsoft Store but also avoiding the high annual certificate fees.</p>
<p><strong>Due to the migration to a new certificate causing package name conflicts, Snap Hutao provides the following detailed explanation to assist all users in updating to version 1.9.0 and future versions.</strong></p>
<h2>Upgrade to Version 1.9.0</h2>
<h3>Version Release</h3>
<p>Snap Hutao version 1.9.0 is scheduled to be released on the weekend before Christmas 2023. We will publish the download links for the installation package through GitHub, Jihu GitLab, this official website, and the community.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>1.9.0 version has been released, please download from <a href="/en/quick-start.html" target="_blank">Quick Start</a> page.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3>Uninstall Old Versions</h3>
<p>Directly installing this package will cause problems depending on your system version due to package name and signature conflicts.</p>
<p>| System Version |                                                      Expected Issues                                                      |
| :</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hut.ao/images/202312/1-8-5-installer.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute Your Code</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/contribute.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/contribute.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Contribute Your Code</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao is developed using C# and the .NET framework for both the desktop client and server. We greatly appreciate feedback from the open-source community, and if you&amp;apos;re willing to contribute your code, please refer to the instructions in this document.</description>
      <category>Open Source</category>
      <category>Development</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 07:23:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao is developed using <code>C#</code> and the <code>.NET Framework</code> for both the desktop client and server. We greatly appreciate feedback from the open-source community. If you are willing to contribute your code, please read the following guidelines.</p>
<p>You can find all <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues?q=is%3Aissue+is%3Aopen+-label%3A%E5%B7%B2%E5%AE%8C%E6%88%90" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">unsolved opened issues</a> on GitHub.</p>
<h2></h2>
<ol>
<li>Download and install <a href="https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/downloads/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Visual Studio</a>
<ul>
<li>You need to install the following components:
<ul>
<li><code>.NET desktop development</code></li>
<li><code>Desktop development with C++</code></li>
<li><code>Windows application development</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Install <code>Single-project MSIX Packaging Tools for VS 2022</code> provided by Microsoft from the Visual Studio Marketplace.</li>
<li>Use Git to clone the project repository: <code>https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.git</code>.</li>
<li>Switch the branch to <code>develop</code>.</li>
<li>Open the project solution with Visual Studio, and then you are ready to start developing.</li>
</ol>
<h2></h2>
<ol>
<li>Download and install <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/productid/9P7KNL5RWT25" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sysinternals Suite</a> from the Microsoft Store or download it from the <a href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/sysinternals/downloads/sysinternals-suite" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Microsoft website</a>.</li>
<li>Locate and run the <code>DebugView</code> program (either in the Start menu or in the unzipped files).</li>
<li>Launch the Snap Hutao main program.</li>
<li>Observe the debug information output by <code>DebugView</code>.</li>
</ol>
<h2></h2>
<ul>
<li>All Pull Requests not initiated from other branches of the project are only allowed to be merged into the <code>develop</code> branch.</li>
<li>If your code is related to an existing issue, please use <a href="https://docs.github.com/en/get-started/writing-on-github/working-with-advanced-formatting/using-keywords-in-issues-and-pull-requests" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">keywords</a> to link your PR to the relevant issue. This will automatically close the issue when the PR is merged into the <code>main</code> branch.</li>
</ul>
<h2></h2>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Attention</p>
<p>If you want to try the latest Alpha version, please download and install <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Automation/Hutao-Auto-Release/releases/download/certificate-ca/DGP_Studio_CA.crt" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>DGP_Studio_CA.crt</strong></a> to <strong>Trusted Root Certification Authorities</strong> first.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>After each <code>push</code>, a GitHub Actions script will automatically run to build the latest solution:
<ul>
<li>For the <code>main</code>, <code>develop</code>, and <code>feat</code> branches, the script will automatically upload the built <code>Snap Hutao Alpha</code> archive for testing.</li>
<li>Other branches will only verify code buildability and will not provide an upload feature.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>You can view all build logs in the <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/actions/workflows/alpha.yml" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Alpha pipeline</a>.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/development/contribute.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster WIKI</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/monster-wiki.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/monster-wiki.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Monster WIKI</source>
      <description>The Monster Wiki is an integrated monster database within Snap Hutao. Players can use this feature to access detailed information on all monsters in Genshin Impact. By analyzing the monsters, players can strategize and reduce the difficulty of the game.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:35:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Known Issues</p>
<p>Some monster information is missing, and it's difficult to improve for various reasons. Issues related to monster data will not be accepted for the time being.</p>
</div>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01WdFqdC1g6e0sAREwO_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="monster-wiki" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The Monster Wiki is a built-in database in Snap Hutao for querying <strong>base stats, stats at each level, elemental RES, and drop items</strong> data of each monster.</p>
<h2>Included Data</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Monster List</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Use the button in the upper left corner of the list to switch the display mode:
<ul>
<li>"Thumbnails and Names": Displays the monster's avatar and corresponding name for quick browsing and searching.</li>
<li>"Thumbnails Only": Displays only the monster's avatar, suitable for players already familiar with monster appearances.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Data is sourced from Genshin Impact; some monsters may lack complete information due to incomplete data.</li>
<li>Click on the thumbnail or name in the list to jump to the corresponding monster details page.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Data Content</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Monster Stats</strong>
<ul>
<li>Key data such as the monster's base HP, ATK, and DEF.</li>
<li>Switch the monster's level through the interface to view its stat changes at different levels.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Elemental RES</strong>
<ul>
<li>Includes the percentage of each monster's resistance to elemental damage, helping players optimize their output choices.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Drop Items</strong>
<ul>
<li>Lists all the items a monster may drop and their drop probability ranges, making it easier for players to plan material acquisition.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01WdFqdC1g6e0sAREwO_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initialization Guide</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/setup.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/setup.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Initialization Guide</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao&amp;apos;s new user onboarding feature helps users quickly check the availability status of specific program functionalities and set them to an available state.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 19:09:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>When launching Snap Hutao for the first time, the program will automatically enter the initialization guide to help users correctly configure the various functions of the tool.
The guide process includes setting the language, confirming important user agreements, checking the necessary system environment, and downloading static resources.</p>
<h2>Language Settings</h2>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>Details</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN016IMEtP1g6dyEFo5uK_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="language-selection" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In the language settings section, you can choose the interface language supported by Snap Hutao. If you change the language, the program will automatically restart to apply the changes.</p>
<ul>
<li>Simplified Chinese is the base language of Snap Hutao, and the development team also maintains the English translation.</li>
<li>Traditional Chinese, Japanese, and Korean translations are contributed by the Crowdin community.</li>
<li>The remaining languages are translated by the Google Gemini AI model.</li>
</ul>
<p>If you are interested in contributing to the translation, you can visit <a href="https://translate.hut.ao" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://translate.hut.ao</a> to provide assistance.</p>
</details>
<h2>User Agreement</h2>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>Details</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01SzKgb61g6dy2MZH5s_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="user-agreement" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In the user agreement section, you need to read and agree to the relevant agreements and terms of service provided by Snap Hutao. These documents are designed to help you understand the nature of the Snap Hutao project and the rules for using the tool.</p>
<p>After confirming and accepting the agreement, you can continue to complete the initialization process.</p>
</details>
<h2>Environment Check</h2>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>Details</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01T3lLLI1g6dyDspUsf_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="environment-check" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Snap Hutao will automatically detect the following key runtime environments and prompt the user whether they need to be installed or updated:</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Segoe Fluent Icons font</strong>: Provides a better interface icon display effect.<br>
Download address: <a href="https://aka.ms/SegoeFluentIcons" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Segoe Fluent Icons</a></li>
<li><strong>WebView2 Runtime</strong>: A modern browser component that supports the core functions of the tool.<br>
Download address: <a href="https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?linkid=2124701" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">WebView2 Runtime</a></li>
</ol>
<p>If a missing environment is detected, you can click the corresponding link to download and complete the installation.<br>
The above image shows the expected display effect of this step under a complete environment.</p>
</details>
<h2>Resource Download</h2>
<details class="hint-container details"><summary>Details</summary>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01QILPRh1g6dyHTUpV9_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="resource-download" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In the resource download section, Snap Hutao will automatically obtain the required static image resources. After the resource download is complete, the initialization process will automatically close, and the main interface of the tool will be loaded.</p>
<p>If the resource download fails, Snap Hutao can still be used normally and will automatically download missing resources when loading images.</p>
</details>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/features/setup.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snap Hutao Open Platform</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/platform.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/platform.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Snap Hutao Open Platform</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao incorporates ideas from the community, and as our way of giving back, we also make certain services available to the community. If they are helpful to your development, feel free to use them, and we will do our best to maintain these forked projects.</description>
      <category>Open Source</category>
      <category>Development</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Since its establishment on GitHub on April 18, 2022, the Snap Hutao project has received extensive support from the open-source community and users. As the project has developed, we have built a series of supporting services as middleware for Snap Hutao.</p>
<p>Currently, the development team is making some of these practical services available to the open-source community in the form of open interfaces, for use by developers who share our vision. We have written detailed usage documentation for these interfaces, provide maintenance support, and answer frequently asked questions. Whether you are an experienced developer or a beginner, we hope that these interfaces can assist you in your application development.</p>
<h2>Snap Hutao API &amp; Snap Hutao Cloud Developer License</h2>
<p>The Snap Hutao API is an interface service that exposes the Snap Hutao Spiral Abyss Database, designed to provide data access support for open-source software developers.</p>
<p>By applying for the Snap Hutao API Developer License, developers will not only gain access to the database but also receive full access to the Snap Hutao Cloud features within Snap Hutao as a bonus.</p>
<p>Developers can submit applications through the <a href="https://homa.snapgenshin.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Snap Hutao API Open Platform</a> to obtain a developer license.</p>
<h2>UIGF Interchangeable Data Record</h2>
<p>The Snap Hutao project is committed to promoting the free flow of user data among different open-source tools, and to this end, it has drafted the initial version of the <a href="https://uigf.org/en/standards/UIGF.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Uniformed Interchangeable Gacha Log Format (UIGF)</a>.</p>
<p>This standard has now been recognized and adopted by an increasing number of developers and is continuously being improved.</p>
<p>Many developers have gathered at the <a href="https://github.com/UIGF-org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">UIGF-Org</a> open-source organization. We hope to use this platform to promote communication between developers and users, obtain more feedback and technical advancements, and further create excellent open-source Genshin Impact tools.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/development/platform.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Development</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/development/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/development/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Open Source Development</source>
      <description>Open Source Development</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:35:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site Menu</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/menu.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/menu.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Site Menu</source>
      <description>Site Menu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:41:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/dashboard.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/dashboard.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Home Dashboard</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao&amp;apos;s home dashboard provides features such as account overview, real-time game announcements, and event countdowns, helping users efficiently manage game information.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 01:37:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01Nlz8ca1g6e0tyxrBa_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="Dashboard" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>When you launch Snap Hutao, it will default to the home dashboard. The dashboard is divided into two parts: the upper part displays a summary of personal game data in the form of cards, and the lower part displays recent game announcements and event countdowns. The homepage cards can be closed or re-enabled in the settings.</p>
<h2>Feature Overview</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Snap Hutao Announcements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>If the development team releases a new announcement, it will be displayed at the top of the dashboard. Most announcements can be closed.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Game Launcher</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Users can directly select an account and launch the game from the dashboard.
<ul>
<li>If the "Use MiYouShe / HoYoLAB Login" option is enabled, the account selection function will be unavailable.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Wish History</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Displays the UID of the current wish archive and presents the pity count in the form of a progress bar.</li>
<li>For users with multiple wish archives, you can switch between archives using the arrow buttons on either side of the wish history area.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Achievement Statistics</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Displays the total number of completed achievements, completion percentage, and the latest achievements obtained for the achievement archive.</li>
<li>For users with multiple achievement archives, you can switch between archives using the arrow buttons on either side of the achievement statistics area.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Real-Time Notes</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Provides quick access to real-time note data.</li>
<li>For users with multiple real-time notes, you can switch between archives using the arrow buttons on either side of the real-time notes area.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Calendar Function</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Displays the characters who have a birthday on the current day, as well as the talent, character, and weapon materials that can be farmed.
<ul>
<li>If the "Cultivation Plan" includes materials that can be farmed on the current day, the corresponding icons will be highlighted.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>The calendar data is based on the current computer time, and users can change the data to a specific server time zone in the settings.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Game Announcements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Provides quick access to browse real-time game announcements.</li>
<li>The default data source is the official announcements of the Domestic servers. Users can switch to other data sources in the settings.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>The dashboard is designed to help players efficiently manage all important information related to Genshin Impact, providing convenient functional entry points and rich data displays.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01Nlz8ca1g6e0tyxrBa_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/quick-start.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/quick-start.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Quick Start</source>
      <description>Follow this quick start guide to quickly set up Snap Hutao.</description>
      <category>Functionality</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 11:59:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Follow this quick start guide to quickly set up Snap Hutao.</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>| Requirement                      | Specification                                                         |
|</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01mpzxPR1g6e22IjFMh_!!1797064093.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join the User Community</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/community.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/community.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Join the User Community</source>
      <description>Here you can join the Snap Hutao community and interact with other players on various topics.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 11:59:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As an open-source software, community engagement is a vital part of the Snap Hutao ecosystem. You can join the Snap Hutao user community through the following ways.</p>
<div class="vp-card-container">
  </div>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01mpzxPR1g6e22IjFMh_!!1797064093.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Advanced</source>
      <description>Advanced</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 05:38:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall Snap Hutao</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/uninstall.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/uninstall.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Uninstall Snap Hutao</source>
      <description>Uninstalling Snap Hutao is a simple and quick process. You can follow the tutorial on this page to uninstall Snap Hutao to the extent that suits you best.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:53:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Uninstalling Snap Hutao is a straightforward process. If you want to completely remove the program and its associated data, please follow these steps:</p>
<h2>Uninstalling the Snap Hutao Application</h2>
<ol>
<li>Open the <strong>Start Menu</strong>.</li>
<li>Search for <code>Snap Hutao</code>.</li>
<li>Right-click on Snap Hutao and select <strong>"Uninstall"</strong>.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Clearing the Data Folder (for Complete Uninstallation)</h2>
<ol>
<li>Open File Explorer.</li>
<li>Navigate to the following path: <code>%userprofile%/Documents/Hutao</code>.</li>
<li>Delete the <code>Hutao</code> folder.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
<h3>Why does the "You'll need a new app to open this" dialog box pop up?</h3>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01b3j0eY1g6duBXLJXg_!!1797064093.jpg_.webp" alt="uninstall-error" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>If you see a prompt like "You'll need a new app to open this hutao link" after uninstalling Snap Hutao as shown above, it means that the real-time notes scheduled task was not cleared before uninstallation. This issue only occurs in older versions of Snap Hutao.</p>
<p>Solution:</p>
<ol>
<li>Reinstall Snap Hutao.</li>
<li>Clear the real-time notes scheduled task in the settings.</li>
<li>Uninstall Snap Hutao again.</li>
</ol>
<p>If you cannot find the relevant task in the system's scheduled tasks but the problem persists, please refer to <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs/issues/18" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">this document</a> for further solutions.</p>
<h3>How to Fully Backup/Restore Client Data?</h3>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Data Security Warning</p>
<p>The <code>Userdata.db</code> file contains all of your client data, including your sensitive MiHoYo BBS Cookie. Please keep this file safe and do not share it with anyone.</p>
</div>
<h4>Backing Up Data</h4>
<ol>
<li>Go to the Snap Hutao data directory (default path is <code>%userprofile%/Documents/Hutao</code>).</li>
<li>Copy the <code>Userdata.db</code> file from the folder to your chosen backup location.</li>
</ol>
<h4>Restoring Data</h4>
<ol>
<li>Copy the backed-up <code>Userdata.db</code> file back into the Snap Hutao data directory.</li>
<li>Launch Snap Hutao to restore your data.</li>
</ol>
<p>By following the above steps, you can safely backup or restore all of your Snap Hutao data.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/uninstall.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known Issue</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/known-issue.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/known-issue.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Known Issue</source>
      <description>We use a variety of labels on our GitHub issue page to categorize and track the status of user-submitted issues. You can rely on these labels to determine the status of issue.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 08:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You can view all issues on <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues?q=is%3Aissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GitHub Issue page</a></p>
<p>| Category                                                                                                                                          | Flag                                        |
|</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/known-issue.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Logs</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Update Logs</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao strives to provide users with the best user experience by continuously updating and fixing known issues and releasing new features. We will always publish update logs to track the changes made to the program.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 08:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>1.15.12 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the server switch function could not be used properly when launching the game <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2941" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2941</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.11</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Support for UIGF 4.1</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Development plan now allows adding unreleased characters from character WIKI</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Character WIKI page now displays Trace Effects and Visions <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2875" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2875</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved performance of material calculation in development plan</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized performance of some features</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed issue where game region could not be correctly identified in some cases</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed Embedded Yae not working properly in version 5.8 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2916" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2916</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed crash when viewing some new character profiles</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed incorrect admin prompt display on some pages <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2920" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2920</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.10</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when launching the game after using the injection feature in version 5.8 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2885" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2885</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.9</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when Hoyolab users triggered CAPTCHA during login <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2880" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2880</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue that could occur when launching the game after using the injection feature <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2881" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2881</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.8</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Character/Weapon cultivation calculation now supports unreleased characters</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved connection stability when downloading game resources in the game management feature on the game launch page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the Imaginarium Theater statistics (Lightbearer) could not be displayed correctly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2845" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2845</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where Hoyolab users could not log in properly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2845" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2849</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the game management feature on the game launch page could not correctly update pre-downloads</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Other known issues fixed</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when opening the main window as an international server user <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2844" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2844</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed unexpected crashes in some cases</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.6</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program could not be used normally when the device name was not in English</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.5</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added user prompts for MiYouShe/HoYoLAB account login mode in the homepage game launch card</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added preview redemption code viewing feature to the homepage</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added "End Process" button to the game launch page for convenient handling of leftover game processes</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added tutorial hints for some injection features on the game launch page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added fragile resin consumption estimation to resin estimation in the Dev Plan page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added Imaginarium Theater page to view and save related challenge records</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added "Check for Updates" feature to the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added friendship level display to grid view on My Characters page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1283" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1283</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added custom range batch calculation to cultivation calculation on My Characters page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2831" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2831</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Achievement page now allows right-click to copy achievement ID <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2832" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2832</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Refreshed UI design</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Hutao Passport now uses a more secure V2 API</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where clicking copyright info in the settings page would not open the browser when using online backgrounds</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue on the Imaginarium Theater page when incomplete data was present. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2822" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2822</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.3</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the filter box on the Dev Plan page would provide incorrect prompts.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where switching to the Imaginarium Theater page could still cause a crash. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2816" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2816</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where restarting in administrator mode would not exit the current process.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Other known issues fixed.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.1</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when switching to the Imaginarium Theater page. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2799" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2799</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the hotkey enable prompt in the overlay window would not update correctly. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2809" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2809</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where archives/plans would be deselected after closing and reopening the program on the Wish/Achievement/Dev Plan pages. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2813" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2813</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Other known issues fixed.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.15.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added new navigation animations for homepage cards when jumping to corresponding pages.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added support for Ldiff pre-download/update on the game launch page.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Supported dynamic avatars for MiYouShe/HoYoLAB.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where there was no prompt when hotkey registration failed.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where there was no prompt when the notification area icon failed to be created.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the Snap Hutao process would not exit properly in special cases, preventing it from being launched again.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where unlocking to excessively high frame rates via injection could cause the game to crash or display error 10612-4001. Please do not use the injection feature to gain unfair advantages in certain challenges; we reserve the right to disable this feature. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2794" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2794</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the notification area icon would not be recreated after restarting Explorer. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2737" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2737</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when importing achievements using Embedded Yae. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2754" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2754</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where an incorrect notification about Bilibili channel server not supporting account features would appear when first entering the homepage, game launch page, or updating the game. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2754" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2754</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where viewing certain talents or skills of some characters could cause an infinite loop. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2789" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2789</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Other known issues fixed.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.9</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> The character profile page now correctly displays hyperlinks in some character skills/talents.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The guide window can now display in-app notifications.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Homepage cards can now be reordered by dragging in the settings page.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed multiple issues that could cause the program to crash.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.8</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed multiple issues that could cause the program to crash</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a new redirect synthesis function to the injection feature on the game launch page. Clicking the button in item details in-game will now open the synthesis page instead of map tracking.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Removed the "Resource Download" tab from the game launch page. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2681" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2681</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the width of the main window navigation bar. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2681" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2681</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Migrated some underlying components from C# to C++ for better performance and memory usage.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when switching pages before the homepage sign-in card finishes loading. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2694" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2694</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where improperly formatted UIGF files could be imported. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2704" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2704</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.6</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added double-click operation on the notification icon to directly open the main window.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Removed the ScatteredFiles server conversion mode. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2682" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2682</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where auto-click/auto-press could not restart after being stopped with a hotkey. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2673" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2673</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where Embedded Yae could not be used normally. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2678" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2678</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where metadata might not initialize correctly on the first startup after an update.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.5</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the miHoYo account would not automatically switch after launching the game from the Real-time Notes page. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2623" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2623</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where using Embedded Yae to import achievements after launching the game would not terminate the game process. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2630" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2630</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the Dev Plan on the My Characters page would not check if characters were ascended when calculating all characters and weapons. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2658" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2658</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where deleting a wish record archive would not attempt to reselect the first archive. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2659" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2659</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when attempting to pre-download. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2660" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2660</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue that could occur when failing to download image files under specific conditions.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved the startup experience:
<ul>
<li>A popup will now appear if database migration fails during startup.</li>
<li>The application will wait for initialization to complete before closing or restarting.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Resin estimation in the Dev Plan now calculates combinable materials.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an option for hotkeys to take effect only after the game starts. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2606" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2606</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Game file management now prompts required and available space before starting operations.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the UI might freeze in certain situations. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2617" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2617</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where closing the window might cause a crash in certain situations.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the notification area icon was always created. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2590" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2590</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the updater could not start properly on some systems. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2597" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2597</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where exiting the game might cause a crash in certain situations.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the frame rate setting in the game launch page was incorrectly bound to the field of view toggle. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2596" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2596</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where uploading data on the Spiral Abyss page redirected to an incorrect login page. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2607" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2607</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.3 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added independent switch for overlay window, rollback injection switch panel <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2582" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2582</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where application redirection failed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2576" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2576</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where compact web window would crash on non-first launch <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2586" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2586</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where some devices could not bind hotkeys <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2570" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2570</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2585" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2585</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.2 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the overlay window will resume visible when hidden by hotkey and switch between windows</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.1 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a custom shortcut key setting on the game launch page to control the display and hiding of the overlay window <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2562" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2562</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.14.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a shortcut key to toggle window display/hide for compact web window <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2382" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2382</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a sign-in card on the homepage <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1322" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1322</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a semi-transparent overlay window in the game <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2506" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2506</a>
<ul>
<li>The overlay window will replace the original hotkey prompt in the title bar</li>
<li>The overlay window will replace the original injection options in the game launch page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an injection option to remove the elemental burst camera close-up</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an injection option to remove battle damage numbers</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an injection option to apply touch input <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2535" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2535</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added platform type parameter in the game launch page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2521" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2521</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added sorting options in the My Characters page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2512" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2512</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added display of character and weapon promotion levels in the My Characters page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added filters in the Development Plan</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Introduced a new updater <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2456" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2456</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Resource download progress in the guide page will now inherit existing progress</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Correct prompts when no available game characters after community login</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Simplified the logic of the injection feature <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2531" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2531</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The My Characters page will now automatically scroll to the top after switching characters <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1731" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1731</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Character development will now recognize if the character has ascended <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2403" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2403</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added validation before changing the data directory</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added relevant prompt texts in some settings</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the lag issues on some pages</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Fixed many memory leak issues</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the display text of hotkey prompts</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the main window closing could cause a crash during real-time note auto-refresh</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the tray popup would not reappear after pressing Alt + F4 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2532" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2532</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where clicking to change email/password/logout on Snap Hutao Passport page might not respond</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an error prompt when the game directory is not set</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when attempting to take over the game process <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2540" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2540</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a freeze issue when updating the game on the channel server <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2327" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2327</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the wish timer incorrectly included some permanent characters</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where removing an achievement archive in the Achievement Management page would not automatically switch to the next archive <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2519" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2519</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some achievement versions were displayed incorrectly in the Achievement Management page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where Embedded Yae could not be used normally in version 5.5</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some monsters were displayed incorrectly in the Spiral Abyss</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where resin estimation data in the Development Plan could be incorrect</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when drawing UI under certain scaling conditions</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where WebView2 could not load properly in some cases</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a freeze issue when closing the window before WebView2 finished loading <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2544" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2544</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some devices could not set the language correctly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some images could not be displayed correctly</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where closing the game process during game startup under certain conditions could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where selecting the data directory to the root of a disk partition and then opening the settings page could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where failing to download wallpaper when the wallpaper source is not local could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where failing to fetch game announcements could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where closing the web window before WebView2 finished loading could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where wallpaper switching with local wallpaper sources could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where closing the main window while a notification is about to show or hide could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where switching/deleting users while loading the My Characters page could cause data synchronization issues</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where using auto-click/auto-press under system permission pages could cause the program to crash, now it will automatically stop the corresponding operation</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where refreshing/backward operations before WebView2 finished loading could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where managing game functions on the game launch page with certain non-fixed SSD devices could cause the program to crash, now it defaults to HDD for subsequent operations</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where attempting to reopen the task area icon menu upon program exit could cause the program to crash</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added WebView2 load failure prompts to the web window</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The compact web window can now be resized to any size</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Game launch now checks for already running game processes and attempts to take over</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.6</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added time zone settings to the Dev Plan
<ul>
<li>Time zone will be set when creating a plan</li>
<li>Time zone cannot be changed after the plan is created</li>
<li>Existing Dev Plans will default to the time zone corresponding to the calendar server in Hutao settings</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where importing achievements from other applications would not display the import popup</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when Real-time Notes auto-refreshes in the background <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2491" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2491</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted telemetry method, now using Sentry for better exception information collection and processing</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> After logging into the user panel for the first time, the default character configured in MiYouShe will now be selected first <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2391" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2391</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Modified the transparency logic of the compact web window
<ul>
<li>The window will now be opaque when focused</li>
<li>The window will be semi-transparent when out of focus</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.5</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added Bilibili Wiki to character guides on the character profile page (Simplified Chinese only) <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2435" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2435</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Character profile page now displays character skin illustrations</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed some issues with international server features</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when exiting Hutao from the tray menu</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the calendar card time zone was not applied <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2467</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the game configuration file might revert to the wrong server if missing</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where game file management did not support USB solid-state drives <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2469" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2469</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a UI misalignment issue in the resin estimation on the Dev Plan page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2443" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2443</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized UI layout for certain scaling settings</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.4 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where using the game management function on the game launch page would cause a crash again <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2457" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2457</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where achievements could not be synchronized via Embedded Yae <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2458" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2458</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where backpack items could not be synchronized via Embedded Yae in the Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2461" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2461</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.3 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where using the game management function on the game launch page would cause a crash</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where wish records could not be refreshed via web cache <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2413" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2413</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the homepage could not display correctly when the number of enabled cards was less than one row <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2416" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2416</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where high constellation characters could not be added to the Dev Plan after version 5.2 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2422" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2422</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the data folder could not be changed if the target folder did not exist <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2425" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2425</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some users could not change the data folder due to file encryption <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2433" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2433</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the taskbar icon menu could still be opened when a dialog box was displayed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2434" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2434</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Administrator privileges are now required to disable Loopback</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the data import experience for Embedded Yae
<ul>
<li>Changed the UI of related features, now requires administrator privileges to use</li>
<li>Now requires enabling the injection feature on the game launch page to use related features</li>
<li>Now uses the account configured on the game launch page to log in</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.1</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added German/Spanish/Italian/Thai/Turkish languages</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Achievements and backpack items can now be obtained from the game via Embedded Yae</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added clear backpack items feature in the Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2332" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2332</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added character guides on the character profile page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1526</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where two instances of Hutao might start simultaneously <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2368" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2368</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some devices could not correctly obtain the Loopback status</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where starting the game before user services were fully initialized might prevent logging in with MiYouShe account</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where wish records could not be obtained via web cache <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2363" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2363</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the UID in real-time note notifications might display as Unknown</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the Spiral Abyss did not display the upper and lower halves correctly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where resin estimation in the Dev Plan might cause a crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where resin estimation data in the Dev Plan might overflow <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2361" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2361</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The guide page now displays localization sources</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the operation logic of the Hutao Passport related dialogs</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Real-time notes will now automatically refresh after Hutao starts</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The data folder will now be stored in the container by default and will be deleted upon uninstallation</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Modifying the data folder will now automatically copy data to the new directory <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1835" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1835</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.13.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Changed the program icon - Su Xue Tao Hong</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added calendar server time zone settings, allowing adjustment of the time zone used by the homepage calendar card</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added metadata loading indicator to the title bar</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added Hutao Passport page and removed the Hutao Passport section from the settings page
<ul>
<li>Added email reset function</li>
<li>Added refresh user information function</li>
<li>Integrated redemption code function</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added static image file download prompt to the guide interface</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Reintroduced MiYouShe QR code login function in the user panel</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Hutao Passport's change password/delete account now defaults to the current logged-in account</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Hutao Passport's wish record cloud service and CDN cloud service no longer display as 1970 when no time is obtained</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Display DNS information when network request fails</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted Hutao notifications display, now severe (red) / important (yellow) notifications cannot be manually closed</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added loading indicator/refresh button to the compact web window</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the issue where frequent window resizing might cause content flickering</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game launch function now correctly prompts for empty paths</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game launch function now correctly disables the select game path button</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved crash popup when using unsupported custom background images <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2335" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2335</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The new window popped up by the game file management in the game launch function now maintains the same theme style as the main window</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game file management in the game launch function now supports resuming installation after interruption</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game file management in the game launch function now calculates an additional 1 GB of installation cache</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game file management in the game launch function now dynamically cleans up unnecessary files during installation</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game file management in the game launch function now correctly skips files that have already been updated</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The guide interface no longer automatically proceeds to the next step after selecting a language</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> In-app error prompts can now copy text</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the display effect of the main attributes of artifacts on the My Characters page to distinguish them from sub-attributes</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The My Characters interface now displays a default prompt after a search yields no results</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the UI of the Hutao Cloud function on the wish record page</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now checks if the executable file exists when automatically searching for the game path</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The resin estimation function on the material statistics tab of the Dev Plan page now remembers the selected world level</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The Dev Plan page now displays talent levels in separate rows for cultivation items</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some devices could trigger certain keys without using the quick click function <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2296" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2296</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue on devices with high scaling when the window is small <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2290" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2349</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue on some devices when deleting cultivation items <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2290" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2290</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where importing achievements from other applications would not display the import popup when already on the achievements page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2306" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2306</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where multiple dialogs might be opened in specific situations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2307" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2307</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the game path could not be changed while pre-download is available <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2317" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2317</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some devices could not correctly enumerate container applications, causing crashes <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2339" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2339</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where Tartaglia's talent bonus to normal attack skill level was not displayed on the My Characters page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the number of prompts was incorrect when adding to the Dev Plan from the My Characters page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the usage rate statistics on the Imaginarium Theater page were not vertically centered</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where logging in again after Cookie expiration would still display network errors</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the quick click function did not stop clicking after turning off the quick click switch</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the character name card background was not vertically centered in the grid view on the My Characters page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some icons in the search box suggestions were not fully displayed in My Characters/Character Data/Weapon Data</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the window size might initialize to an incorrect size in specific situations</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where pools that had not yet started were included in the timing tab on the wish record page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where real-time notes did not send notifications correctly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a layout issue in the character exploration section of real-time notes at certain scaling rates</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where logging out of Hutao Passport would still log out even if the unregistration failed</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.8</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added keyboard F key auto-press feature, which can be enabled and configured in the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program would crash when entering the game launch page without having any game path</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program would crash when entering the game launch page without setting the game path</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.6</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> The game launcher now automatically detects the game path</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The "Remove team configuration progress bar" feature is now only effective when team switching is allowed</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where updates could not be checked without logging into Hutao Passport</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the background color of the homepage calendar card might be incorrect</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a potential memory leak when modifying the speed limit during game download</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue that might occur when canceling a game download</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when reading Unity logs to get wish records using web cache without setting the game path <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2272" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2272</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.5</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added quick resolution switch customization in the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added historical pool records to the wish history countdown</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added resin estimation to the cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/323" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#323</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1540" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1540</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the background might not change when switching themes</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some elements might display the wrong color theme in certain situations</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a potential vulnerability through metadata initialization injection <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2240" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2240</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the local game version might not be read in certain situations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2251" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2251</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the international server could not refresh wish records in certain situations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2252" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2252</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where characters or weapons might appear without materials after overwriting the cultivation plan</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the transparency settings of the compact web window were not effective <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2258" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2258</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a buffer overflow issue when exiting Snap Hutao from the tray menu on some systems</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The game launcher page will now replace the account with the same name instead of creating a new one</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The cultivation plan will now attempt to obtain more accurate backpack material quantities</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the size of Snap Hutao</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the resolution settings could not be saved after launching the game <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2229" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2229</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the achievement completion time was displayed incorrectly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2184" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2184</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the cultivation plan's backpack could not be refreshed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2212" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2212</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the shortcut keys for fast-forward/rewind in the compact web window were not working</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where selecting a file window would cause a crash on some systems</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where selecting a download source when updating Snap Hutao was not effective</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now checks proxy and loopback status at startup and guides users to remove loopback restrictions if unable to connect to the internet</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The compact web window now remembers the page from the last close</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.3 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue caused by the tray icon not syncing <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2198" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2198</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the program became unusable due to metadata initialization failure caused by tray icon initialization failure <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2202" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2202</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added shortcut keys for fast-forward/rewind in the compact web window</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the cultivation plan's abnormal selection state prevented Snap Hutao from starting <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2174" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2174</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the tray icon might not be created correctly after restarting as an administrator from the tray menu</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the announcement time was displayed incorrectly before the game version update <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2175" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2175</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where reselecting the game path when starting the game might cause a crash</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where game file management might get stuck when repairing the game</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the achievement profile could not be switched using the mouse when the window was too small <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2181" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2181</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where uploading Sprial Abyss records without logging into the Hutao Passport caused a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2169" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2169</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the international server could not refresh the Imaginarium Theater properly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2170" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2170</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where adding weapons to the cultivation plan might cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2168" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2168</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the display effect of the pre-download prompt icon in game file management</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added a launch game button for each game character on the Real-time Notes page, which will jump to the game launch page and automatically switch the MiYouShe/HoYoLAB user to the corresponding user of the note <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1318" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1318</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the loading speed of character and weapon icons</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.1 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the program could not start due to database migration failure <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2159" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2159</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.12.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Upgraded to .NET 9</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a command to the right-click menu of the notification icon to launch a compact web window
<ul>
<li>The compact web window is a topmost window that can become semi-transparent when not interacted with</li>
<li>You can set the shortcut key for playing/pausing videos in the web window on the settings page</li>
<li>Using the compact web window requires running as an administrator</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a new page for Role Combat <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1671" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1671</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when switching game servers using the SophonChunk mode</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a logic error in some specific cases with the game launch injection option</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some switches in the injection options were not interactive after a forced game termination due to injection failure</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the international server could not refresh wish records via web cache <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2141" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2141</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the attack wave details on the Spiral Abyss page might not fully expand in non-Chinese languages <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2152" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2152</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue caused by the failure to initialize the auto-click hotkey in special cases</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> When launching the game from the Real-time Notes notification, the MiYouShe/HoYoLAB user will automatically switch to the corresponding user</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.9 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added countdown for wish history pools <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1341" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1341</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game launch injection option did not match the actual situation <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2134" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2134</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where enabling field of view adjustment could cause stuttering in team and some character elemental burst scenes <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2137" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2137</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where WebView might crash when it fails to pop up normally</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.8 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the injection feature for the oversea server was not working <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2121" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2121</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where refreshing wish records via web cache was not working <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2124" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2124</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the logic between the game launch injection option switches <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2122" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2122</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> / <strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the UI of the game launch interface
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Removed the progress bar from the team configuration interface</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added "Let me in! Mickey Mouse Clubhouse" feature (yes, really)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added chunk mode for server switching in the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added character name cards to character WIKI <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1424" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1424</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where Snap Hutao might crash on the first launch of the day <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2101" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2101</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the error report window might not display correctly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue with incorrect duration of homepage announcements</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where game file management might crash on certain types of disks <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2077" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2077</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where refreshing wish records via web cache might cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2083" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2083</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where window size might be incorrect after restarting across monitors</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The calendar card now highlights materials that can be farmed today in the current cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2045" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2045</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The "My Characters" and character WIKI no longer show filters for 1-star to 3-star items <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2110" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2110</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adding MiYouShe/HoYoLAB accounts now displays a dialog to prevent user operations until completion</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.6 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where features requiring verification would crash after verification <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2074" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2074</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where features requiring resource downloads might freeze</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.5</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added MiYouShe / HoYoLAB account login in the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added filters on the My Characters page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1786" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1786</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an option to save images from web activities in the settings <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1804" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1804</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added account and third-party login for oversea server <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1966" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1966</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when refreshing background images</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed display issues with multi-monitor scaling</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the error report window might not display correctly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed incomplete display of real-time note settings in some languages <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2040" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2040</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where some lists were not processed correctly when updating the cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2022" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2022</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where syncing backpack items in the cultivation plan might not respond <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2044" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2044</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the number of backpack items might be incorrect when syncing the cultivation plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2061" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2061</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash issue when entering the verification code directly without clicking "Get" during MiYouShe phone login <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2058" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2058</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the enable logic of the game update button</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Increased the monster level cap to 110 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1988" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1988</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The verification window will now automatically pop up when encountering a CAPTCHA <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1616" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1616</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added an error report window that pops up when the program crashes</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the program might crash on the first launch after installing/updating Snap Hutao</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where multiple Discord statuses could be set simultaneously <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2024" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2024</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the first line of the game announcement might not respond to clicks</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where international server announcements could not be retrieved <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2030" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2030</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where unlocking the frame rate might not take effect after the 5.1 version update</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where game updates could not be completed properly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the installation progress in the game update window might exceed 100%</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game resource pre-download might get stuck <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2029" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2029</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the completion mark might not display when the game resource pre-download is finished</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the material statistics on the cultivation calculation page might not respond <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2014" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2014</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where MiYouShe phone verification code login might fail</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added "Priority for incomplete sets" in the material statistics on the cultivation calculation page</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now displays materials that can be obtained today in the material statistics on the cultivation calculation page</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.3</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a calendar card on the homepage <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1923" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1923</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added artifact attribute recommendations on the My Characters page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where some monsters were not displayed correctly on the Spiral Abyss page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the character/weapon data page could freeze <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1999" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1999</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the crash issue when switching game servers</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Prevented closing the operation window directly when game file operations are not completed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/2002" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#2002</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added import/export buttons on the Wish Records page for easier access to the import/export buttons on the settings page</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the ability to filter only commission achievements in the achievement management page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/897" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#897</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added download game speed limit feature in the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added web tool link for upgrading UIGF versions in the wish records import/export section of the settings page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where copying files within the application package on certain devices would prompt that the specified file cannot be encrypted
<ul>
<li>This issue previously caused
<ul>
<li>Inability to create desktop shortcuts</li>
<li>Inability to unlock game frame rate</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue of abnormal CPU usage when downloading games on the launch game page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1964" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1964</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where game updates were not taking effect</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where switching to a character without artifacts in the My Characters page would cause the program to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1954" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1954</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue of real-time note requests failing with error code -1</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where some devices were unable to switch save files in the achievement management page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1987" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1987</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Achievements titles and tooltips in the achievement management page can now be selected and copied <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1726" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1726</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Searching achievements in the achievement management page now filters by achievement category as well <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1907" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1907</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the interface link for the CN server announcements <a href="https://github.com/Scighost/Starward/issues/1089" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Scighost/Starward#1089</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.1</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a command to execute debug scripts in the right-click menu of the notification icon</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a command to restart in administrator mode in the right-click menu of the notification icon <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1825" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1825</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> The update log window on the first launch after an update now correctly recognizes Snap Hutao's language <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1900" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1900</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the download and repair game functions in the game launcher could not be used properly</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the launcher background option did not work properly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1908" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1908</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where importing UIGF v4.0 files did not select the correct parts for import <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1941" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1941</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the dialog layout was incorrect when importing UIGF v4.0 files</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where checking or unchecking achievements in the achievement management would deselect the achievement category if an achievement category was selected <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1946" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1946</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now the HoYoLAB text will be hidden when hovering over the HoYoLAB user in the user panel <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1824" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1824</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The cultivation plan can now correctly recognize the talent and weapon breakthrough materials of Natash</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the field of view for unlocking the frame rate</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the multi-threaded download logic when switching servers</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the UI of the pop-up window for the download and repair game functions in the game launcher</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.11.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added long-term expedition point display on the Real-time Notes page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1841" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1841</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> <strong>[BETA]</strong> Added game download/repair/pre-download/update functionality to the game launcher</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where can't logging in to MiYouShe via QR code, removed QR code login option, added phone verification code login method <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1819" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1819</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where character skill levels displayed inconsistently in the My Character page list and grid view due to constellation bonuses <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1838" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1838</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where switching to another page while the home page announcement was still loading would cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1845" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1845</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where reading local package version information failed when switching game servers would cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1851" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1851</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where obtaining wish records on the international server displayed "AuthKey Expired" <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1873" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1873</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where navigating to My Character/Spiral Abyss pages without logging in to MiYouShe or HoYoLAB prevented further operations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1877" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1877</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where refreshing Real-time Notes on certain devices would cause a crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1893" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1893</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where home page announcements were not displayed correctly and some text colors were rendered incorrect in dark mode</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the application background did not switch correctly</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the display position of in-app notifications <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1832" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1832</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the in-app error messages for network requests</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved the experience of downloading updates, now you can choose a mirror for downloading</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the frame rate unlock feature, removed classic mode, added field of view modification/fog removal/compatibility mode in injection mode</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.7</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the feature to export selected character's information in text to the clipboard on the My Character page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1497" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1497</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added UIGF 4 import and export support in the settings page, removed UIGF 2 and UIGF 3 import and export support in Wish Export feature</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the view would not refresh when deleting a save file on the Wish Export page</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where Real-time Notes auto-refresh was enabled by default</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the title would not display correctly when the webview width was too narrow</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where HoYoLAB accounts could not add characters or weapons in Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1810" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1810</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue of failing to unlock the frame rate <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1820" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1820</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the navigation interaction of the main window, now navigate to other pages when the page is not fully loaded is disallowed, and the update log window will now be displayed on the first launch after the update</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the display of in-app notifications</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the process of adding items to the Dev Plan, now you can choose the save mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the information prompt for HTTP requests <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1720" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1720</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.6</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the application could not start due to user changing the game path manually <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1792" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1792</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the content of the page was not updated after refreshing the wish records <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1791" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1791</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash that occurred when the refreshed wish records differed from the current UID <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1794" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1794</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the web window size was incorrect on monitors with a scaling rate other than 100% <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1795" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1795</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed a crash that occurred when binding the Real-time Notes UID on the game launcher page</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the time display format for expedition dispatches in the Real-time Notes <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1796" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1796</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.5</h2>
<ul>
<li>Added injection unlock mode, which can be tried when classic mode is ineffective</li>
<li>WebView now displays in a separate window</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where switching from OS server to CN server could cause game data abnormalities <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1750" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1750</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where certain screen recording software could capture the wrong window <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1771" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1771</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where adding a HoYoLAB account under specific conditions could cause the program to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1774" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1774</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where certain controls displayed incorrectly in dark mode <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1633" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1633</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where importing achievements via URL protocol would not display the interface correctly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1763" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1763</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where skill icons would not display correctly in certain scenarios <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1784" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1784</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where some event announcements had incorrect time</li>
<li>Fixed alignment issues with multiple elements</li>
<li>Optimized the display effect of some pages</li>
<li>Refactored the underlying code</li>
<li>Other QA issues</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.4</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added previous data comparison in Spiral Abyss - Current Statistics/Character Data/Weapon Data section of Snap Hutao Database</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the ability to obtain backpack materials in Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1651" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1651</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added right-click copy support to all images</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the functionality to display game character avatars in the user panel</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where unlocking the frame rate would prevent game server conversion due to file occupation <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1703" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1703</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where importing achievements from other programs using URL protocol would cause freezing when Snap Hutao is not running <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1704" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1704</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the actual refresh time of real-time notes was magnified by 60 times <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1710" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1710</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Boost the maximum resin notification threshold to 200 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1711" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1711</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> The background image of the launcher now uses the version without text <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1688" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1688</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Changed the logic of activation from the Windows notification center, fixing the issue where notifications could not be correctly redirected in administrator mode</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where all materials or all backpack items would be rendered incorrectly on Dev Plan page in certain scenarios</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved the display effect of some controls</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Changed the activation/closing logic of windows, now they are directly closed instead of being hidden when already open</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Adjusted the UI for displaying package lists in the Launch Game - Game Resources section</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Weapon data page now uses in-game sorting</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized punctuation and wording of some texts</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other performance improvements and QA testing issue fixes</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.3</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> The notification area icon now supports show the menu with a left click <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1656" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1656</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the frame rate unlock feature in the game launcher failed in version 4.7 of the game <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1675" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1675</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where closing the main window on Windows 10 system would not correctly pop up the tray icon notification</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the tray icon location could not be correctly obtained on Windows 10 system, causing crashes</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the window would not be remembered when resized to smaller than the initial size <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1657" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1657</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where application redirection failed in some scenarios</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the launch game window data expired in some scenarios</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where all materials in the cultivation plan are highlighted on Sundays</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the guide window can be maximized</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game screenshot folder cannot be opened when it does not exist</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the dev version and the official version use the same notification identifier, causing repeated activation </li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Temporarily disabled the MiYouShe web login entry in the user panel</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Removed the jump list of the right-click menu of Snap Hutao icon in the taskbar and the start menu</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the style of in-app notifications <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1650" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1650</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the style of the character property panel in My Characters</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the style of real-time notes settings in Real-time Notes</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the brightness performance of the game announcement images on the homepage in dark mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the brightness performance of the pool images in the global wish statistics in the wish records in dark mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the display effect of some texts</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the loading speed of some pages</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other performance improvements</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŒLocalization]</strong> Added Vietnamese language support</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.2</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Introduced retry mechanism for static resource downloads</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added Real-time Note feature to view Archon Quest progress <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1203" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1203</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Highlighted all relevant materials on Sunday in the Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1607" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1607</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added option to display icon in system notification area (system tray)
<ul>
<li>Added notification area icon switch in settings</li>
<li>Application behavior changes when notification area icon is enabled</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Application will not exit when all windows are closed; only exits when selected from the right-click menu of the system tray icon</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Closing the window triggers a prompt if the icon is in the collapsed area</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization/Break Change]</strong> Real-time Note timed refresh no longer triggers when not running in the background (refresh by Windows Scheduled Task is removed)</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Real-time Note refresh switch/refresh time settings no longer require administrator mode</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where images might not load when switching to list view if the default view of character data/weapon data/monster data/achievement management interface was not list view</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where occasional inability to exit the program normally was caused by checking system proxy settings</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where the bag items did not switch accordingly when switching the growth plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1609" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1609</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed an issue where modifying the completion status of a single achievement would incorrectly deselect the achievement category <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1631" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1631</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where the shortcut key settings would be obscured by the title bar when opening the auxiliary button panel near the title bar <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1632" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1632</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where the time range of some new announcements did not match correctly <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1613" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1613</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fixed]</strong> Fixed an issue where the statistics tab on the wish record page would show the pool ratio of 0 draws as NaN <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1588" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1588</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Removed the task list from the right-click menu of the taskbar icon</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added a second confirmation dialog for deleting a growth plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1608" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1608</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added a prompt for HoYoLAB error code 2001 <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1542" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1542</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Added quality comparison tab to the quality selection page of the guide interface <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1595" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1595</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Disabled auto-click shortcut settings in non-administrator mode</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other performance improvements</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŒLocalization]</strong> Added French language support</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.1 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the game server conversion issue</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.10.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added options for image quality, users can now choose a significant smaller size with nearly lossless image quality. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1430" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1430</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added display of not obtained items in the Character and Weapon tabs of the Wish Export. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1355" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1355</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added a new method to start the program in administrator mode by default. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1558" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1558</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸŽ‰New]</strong> Added the option to display only unfinished achievement categories on the achievement record page. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/896" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#896</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the hidden taskbar couldn't be displayed when maximizing the main window in Windows 10. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1571" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1571</a></li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the incorrect top card margin on the settings page.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the game or program would crash when starting after hot-plugging a monitor.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the Global Wish Statistics on the Wish Export page couldn't be viewed when there was no wish record.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the cache image lookup pointed to the wrong path, which caused the need for repeated image resource downloads.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where the announcement start and end times were incorrect when the version was not yet updated.</li>
<li><strong>[ðŸ”¨Fix]</strong> Fixed the issue where launching Hutao in Discord's update check could cause a crash.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Improved the display effect of the floating window before and after clicking the show button in the password input box. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1485" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1485</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> The software update process now starts only after user confirmation, no longer starting by default. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1297" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1297</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> When users are not logged in to Hutao Cloud, they will be prompted with a pop-up before uploading Abyss records to avoid missing the opportunity to claim rewards. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1245" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1245</a></li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the game launch feature, it will now attempt to generate the configuration file automatically when it can't be found, and also provides a manual generation function.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Updated Windows App SDK to 1.5.2.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized overall memory usage of the program.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Now clearing the cache folder when resetting image resources.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the creation of shortcuts to start in administrator mode, now even if pinned to the taskbar, it can be used normally.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Optimized the login pop-up for Hutao Passport, now viewing the password in plain text does not cause the dialog width to change repeatedly.</li>
<li><strong>[âœ¨Optimization]</strong> Other significant underlying refactoring.</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.9</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add âž•
<ul>
<li>Added Chronicled Wish in Global Wish Stats tab under Wish Export page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the interact launch error with Better Genshin Impact <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1467</a></li>
<li>Fixed the full package name error in Advanced Game Launcher - Resource Download page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1476" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1476</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that game would be launched when failed to unlock frame rate limit <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1495" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1495</a></li>
<li>Updated outdated links in Settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1503" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1503</a></li>
<li>Fixed the crash issue when adding accounts; fixed sporadic issue that selected users and characters could not be cleared correctly; optimized the UI display after logging in. <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1504" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1504</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Optimized keyword searching UI in WIKI pages <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1475" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1475</a></li>
<li>Optimized UI in WIKI page when search result is empty <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1479" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1479</a></li>
<li>Optimized collected item display in Dev Plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1513" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1513</a></li>
<li>Optimized the smoothness and stability of the waterfall layout in the Dev Plan page</li>
<li>Optimized the default sorting of backpack materials and material stats tabs on the Dev Plan page, and now displays completion markers for items with sufficient quantities <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1510" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1510</a></li>
<li>Optimized the alignment of the scroll bar at the bottom of the Statistics tab on the Wish Export page</li>
<li>Optimized the logic of displaying items in the Global Wish Stats tab on the Wish Export page</li>
<li>Optimized the smoothness and stability of the grid view on the Achievement Management page</li>
<li>Added security hint in Web Login page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.8</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added support for Chronicled Wish <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1470" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1470</a></li>
<li>Added support for UIGF v3.0 wish data format</li>
<li>Added dark/light mode setting option in the settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1434" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1434</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the card display issue under some particular Windows display settings values <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1429" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1429</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that network issue may cause client conversion between CN server and oversea server failed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1433" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1433</a></li>
<li>Fixed the wrong OTA package name and link in downloadable resource page in Advanced Game Launcher</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>The WIKI search/filtering feature has been greatly enhanced, users will now get prompts when typing <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1120" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1120</a></li>
<li>Optimized the text in some InterProcess features in Advanced Game Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1432" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1432</a></li>
<li>Optimized the display UI of Wanderlust Invocation in Wish Export page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1460" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1460</a></li>
<li>Optimized the time range text when the wish data is empty <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1443" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1443</a></li>
<li>Re-enabled the background material in main window</li>
<li>Background image will now be refreshed immediately after changing the background image source setting</li>
<li>Optimized the Teams UI in Spiral Abyss page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.7</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added <a href="https://bgi.huiyadan.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Better Genshin Impact</a> joint start up option in the advanced launcher, users now can start Genshin Impact and BGI together in Snap Hutao <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1388" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1388</a></li>
<li>Added multiple client background wallpaper sources, including:
<ul>
<li>No wallpaper (default)</li>
<li>Random images in local background folder</li>
<li>Bing daily wallpaper</li>
<li>Hutao daily wallpaper</li>
<li>Genshin Impact official launcher background</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that when Discord is running with administrator privilege and Snap Hutao is running in normal privilege, Snap Hutao will crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1400" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1400</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that reorder game account in Advanced Launcher with administrator privilege would cause the clint to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1379" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1379</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that scroll down the in-game announcement in Dashboard would cause the announcement disappear <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1365" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1365</a></li>
<li>Fixed some human unreadable text in character WIKI, again <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1316" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1316</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that searching result in Feedback Center was not HTML decoded <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1391" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1391</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Added two 4K resolution options in Advanced Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1375" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1375</a></li>
<li>Client will now memorize selected character in each account in MiHoYo BBS account panel <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1233" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1233</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.6</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added customized background image feature, users now can open background image folder and add images they like <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/357" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#357</a></li>
<li>Added responsive settings page, layout will be updated while window size and shape changes, <a href="https://github.com/Scighost" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@Scighost</a> realized this feature <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1337" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1337</a></li>
<li>Added container loopback status and unlocker feature in Feedback Center</li>
<li>Added displaying current network proxy status feature in Feedback Center</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed <code>653366069</code> error when submit Spiral Abyss data <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1351" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1351</a></li>
<li>Fixed <code>653366069</code> error when sync character from MiHoYo BBS Battle Chronicle and Development Plan sources</li>
<li>Adapt new Asia server UID rule</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that font size in game announcements is too small <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1347" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1347</a></li>
<li>Fixed MiYouShe QR code login issue, now ZZZ login page is used to handle QR code login method <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1345" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1345</a></li>
<li>Replace unreadable text in character voice/story with normal text in Character WIKI <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1316" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1316</a></li>
<li>Fixed the display issue in Home Dashboard when Parametric Transformer is not achieved <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1331" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1331</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that in some cases, swap Home Dashboard to bottom side would cause the client to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1365" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1365</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>User's MiHoYo BBS accounts in Account Panel can be dragged and reordered now, to allow users to have a better operation experience <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1334" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1334</a></li>
<li>Game account records in Game Launcher can be dragged and reordered now, to allow users to have a better operation experience</li>
<li>Optimized title text in Wish Export (<code>Statistics</code> is renamed to <code>Global Wish Stats</code>) <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1344" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1344</a></li>
<li>Optimized text under Resource Download page in Game Launcher (<code>Client</code> is renamed to <code>Full Package</code>) <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1279" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1279</a></li>
<li>Optimized image download error hint in wizard <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1333" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1333</a></li>
<li>Update Spiral Abyss wave information text of Genshin Impact version 4.4</li>
<li>Added permission error hint in Realtime Notes notification settings</li>
<li>Limit active thread count when downloading client update package</li>
<li>Added two new resolutions in Game Resolution Quick Settings</li>
<li>Allow developers using NamedPipe to activate the application </li>
<li>Make Windows App SDK embedded</li>
<li>Optimized Win32/COM API calls</li>
<li>Redesigned client UI to fit background images</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Localization ðŸŒ
<ul>
<li>Portuguese (PT-BR) is now a new client language, thanks to contribution from <a href="https://github.com/t0piy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@t0piy</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.5</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added monitor identification button in game launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1261" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1261</a></li>
<li>Brand new Feedback Center is introduced <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1039" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1039</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that when the game in under <code>Program Files</code> path, <code>server conversion failed</code> error would be raised <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1262" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1262</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that static packages download cannot be completed in the setup wizard <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1242" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1242</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Added support of changing proxy settings during Snap Hutao is running</li>
<li>Added game status in Game Launcher Card in the dashboard</li>
<li>Added data folder size auto refresh after server conversion cache is deleted</li>
<li>Optimized the logic to identify whether server conversion is needed when game launch process is requested</li>
<li>Optimized the English translation</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.4 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the crash issue for Bilibili server users when entering the main window</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.3</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the crash issue for new users when entering the main window</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.2</h2>
<ul>
<li>New âž•
<ul>
<li>Added Windows native HDR option in Game Launcher</li>
<li>Added support of HoYoverse accounts in Game Launcher account switch feature</li>
<li>Added option of deleting server conversion cache file in Settings page</li>
<li>Added restart as admin option in Settings page</li>
<li>Added the function of sharing pictures to the clipboard in WebView</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix ðŸ”¨
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that some MiHoYo BBS pages operations cannot be done in Webview</li>
<li>Added conspicuous mark of Admin Mode on windows title to indicate whether if Snap Hutao is running as administrator</li>
<li>Fixed game path error after server conversion</li>
<li>Fixed the document link on Spiral Abyss page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization âœ¨
<ul>
<li>Added account identification field in Real-time Note data forwarding webhook</li>
<li>All options in Danger Zone on Settings page now have double confirmations</li>
<li>Change to way of game account switch from PowerShell of directly modify regedit to avoid error when Windows Long Path is not enabled</li>
<li>Optimized UI of auto-click feature shortcut settings card</li>
<li>Added checks for special paths such as Program Files during server conversion</li>
<li>Optimized the scrolling performance of WebView on some pages</li>
<li>Optimized the performance of Discord Activity</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.1 </h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Fix ðŸ”¨</strong>
<ul>
<li>Fixed crash on Game Launcher page when user text zoom is not set as 100%</li>
<li>Fixed crash caused by Realtime Notes during the program startup</li>
<li>Fixed the issue where Realtime Notes may be loaded simultaneously with user account information, result in reentrancy</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Optimizations âœ¨</strong>
<ul>
<li>Enhanced prompt to add or select game path in Game Launcher</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.9.0</h2>
<div class="hint-container important">
<p class="hint-container-title">Breaking Changes</p>
<p>Snap Hutao recently obtained sponsorship from the SignPath Foundation for code signing certificates. Starting from version 1.9.0, we will use a brand-new certificate to sign Snap Hutao installation packages.</p>
<p>Programs with the new signature will be incompatible with old versions. Users updating from versions 1.8.4 and older to 1.9.0 and newer versions need to uninstall the old version first and then perform a fresh installation of the new version of the client. Due to the design of Snap Hutao's data directory, users will not lose any important data.</p>
<p>You can read the article <a href="/en/blog/version-1-9-0-breaking-changes.html" target="_blank">Explanation of Breaking Changes in Version 1.9.0</a> for a deeper understanding of how the signature changes in this version update affect the Snap Hutao project.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>New Features âž•</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The game launcher now supports multiple game paths <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#525</a></li>
<li>Added QR code login method for miHoYo in the user panel <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/870" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#870</a></li>
<li>The client now automatically detects network status and displays the results in the settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/pull/1161" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1116</a></li>
<li>Added an option in the game launcher to start Genshin Impact in touch mode <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1173" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1173</a></li>
<li>Add option to change in-game announcement source in the settings page, now you may select oversea severs as the source and display announcements with same lanague of your Snap Hutao <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1112" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1112</a>
<ul>
<li>Only available when there is valid regular expression in Crowdin translation (Simplified Chinese, Traditional Chinese and English are supported now)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Added an option in the settings to enable the console. Users can now get more error prompts when troubleshooting by enabling this option.</li>
<li>Introduced a completely new logic for software updates.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Bug Fixes ðŸ”¨</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue with miHoYo API returning a <code>5003</code> error when fetching character information <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1060" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1060</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that Game Launcher cannot unlock framerate limit in Genshin Impact 4.3 version <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1190" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1190</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue with incorrect countdown data for miHoYo announcements in specific situations.</li>
<li>Fixed incorrect PowerShell statements.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Optimizations âœ¨</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Improved error prompt statements in development calculations, making error messages more explicit <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1163" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1163</a></li>
<li>Optimized the interface of development calculations, now showing specific goals for each item <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1016" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1016</a></li>
<li>Optimized the display of Hutao account information on the main interface, no longer displaying user email addresses <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1160" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1160</a></li>
<li>Updated error prompts for Hutao API.</li>
<li>Optimized the settings page interface; users can now view the size of data and cache directories generated by Snap Hutao in the settings.</li>
<li>Removed Microsoft Store buttons</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Localization ðŸŒ</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Added Indonesian language option in the client, thanks to contribution by <a href="https://github.com/NatsumeAoii" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@NatsumeAoii</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1188" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1188</a></li>
<li>Added Russian language option in the client, thanks to contribution by <a href="https://github.com/QweRezOn" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@QweRezOn</a></li>
<li>Improved client localization string character coverage <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1198" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1198</a></li>
<li>Updated translations for existing languages.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.5 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Tested changes caused by certificate change</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.4 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that daily-checkin shows activity end</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that <code>pwsh.exe</code> cannot be selected as PowerShell host <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1145" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1145</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1153" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1153</a></li>
<li>Fixed display language error when Snap Hutao being pulled up by third-party software <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1147" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1147</a></li>
<li>Fixed PowerShell not found error on desktop shortcut <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1151" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1151</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1154" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1154</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Updated Snap Hutao Cloud prompts text</li>
<li>Optimized Discord Activity tracking performance at the beginning and the end of game</li>
<li>Optimized resize performance on Character WIKI/Weapon WIKI/My Character pages</li>
<li>Optimized performance of server conversion, multi-thread downloading on multipart content is now enabled</li>
<li>Optimized server conversion logic, Snap Hutao will not check folder writing permission before the task</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.3 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the crash issue when Discord client is not running <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1134" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1134</a></li>
<li>Fixed wrong wish record time <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1138" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1138</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Includes .NET environment with the package</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.1</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added Discord Activity synchronization functions in <em>Game Launcher</em>, it syncs game status when playing Genshin Impact <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1082" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1082</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue where navigating from <em>Wish Export</em> page <em>Hutao Cloud</em> panel to <em>Spiral Abyss</em> page would not synchronize the navigation bar options <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1116" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1116</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that <em>Auto Click</em> feature cannot bind with <code>Alt</code> key <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1119" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1119</a></li>
<li>Fixed item refresh issue after switching plans in <em>Dev Plan</em> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1099" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1099</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that only blank name json file can be imported in <code>Achievement</code> page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1124" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1124</a></li>
<li>Fixed full package download link under <em>Resource Download</em> page in <em>Game Launcher</em>, it is replaced with split files link <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1126" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1126</a></li>
<li>Fixed the notification issues from <em>Realtime Note</em>, includes wrong content, repeated notifications and unexpectedly bypass client mode <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1123" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1123</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Added overtime refresh rules for Fingerprint/CookieToken, users don't need to click <code>Refresh Cookie</code> in <em>User Panel</em> so often <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1121" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1121</a></li>
<li>Remake <em>Character WIKI</em> page UI</li>
<li>Added hint text when there is no signed in MiHoYo BBS account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1127" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1127</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.8.0</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Upgraded .NET version to 8</strong> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1103" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1103</a></li>
<li>Fixes
<ul>
<li>Fixed translation issues with <em>Hutao Passport</em> registration/logoff/reset password prompts <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1087" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1087</a> by @Tangweirui2021</li>
<li>Fixed an issue with the first-row items on the <em>Dev Plan</em> page not refreshing correctly after switching plans <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1099" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1099</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue on the <em>Game Launcher</em> page where borderless and exclusive fullscreen could not be set simultaneously <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1106" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1106</a></li>
<li>Replaced the file pickers implementation, resolving the problem of being unable to use the file pickers under administrator privilege <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1096" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1096</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where initializing user information at startup could lead to program freezing</li>
<li>Fixed unnecessary exceptions occurring on certain pages after being switched from</li>
<li>Fixed issues with some exceptions not being captured properly</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Added more detailed failure information for metadata initialization</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.17</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue that the first item in Dev Plan won't be refresh after switching the plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1079" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1079</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that wish record URL for global server cannot be found <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1081" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1081</a></li>
<li>Fixed the issue that error log cannot be captured correctly in some specific situations</li>
<li>Fixed wrong wish record time issue</li>
<li>Fixed the data exception in MiHoYo BBS web pop-ups</li>
<li>Fixed the issue of wrong corner radius settings of mask of history/character/weapon page in Wish History</li>
<li>Fixed the wrong announcement time in time zone other than UTC+8</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimized the UI of MiHoYo BBS web pop-ups, supports backward and refresh feature, supports showing the web title</li>
<li>Auto click feature now can be switched off and hot key can be changed <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/961" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#961</a></li>
<li>Added support of UIGF v2.4 format import and export
<ul>
<li>Added time zone inference based on account's server <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/830" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#830</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.16</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Add screen resolution quick switch dropdown in Game Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1062" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1062</a></li>
<li>Add support to allow user to cooperate <a href="https://github.com/Scighost/Starward" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Starward</a> with Snap Hutao to collect game play time stats <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1071" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1071</a></li>
<li>Add resource download link copy option in Game Launcher <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1074" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1074</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue that MiHoYo BBS returns <code>5003</code> error when fetching data <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1060" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1060</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that page cannot be scrolled in some particular situations <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1068" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1068</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1072" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1072</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that characters' skill levels are not shown in My Character <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1069" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1069</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimized update log display logic <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1015" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1015</a></li>
<li>User's setting selection on each button will be memorized in global scope <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/778" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#778</a></li>
<li>Improved client stability</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.15</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added option to recover full wish history record backup from Snap Hutao Cloud service into new archive <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/886" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#886</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue that invalid game launching parameter can be parsed; added switch for some launch parameters <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1052" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1061</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that user cannot register Snap Hutao account in the client <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1059" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1059</a></li>
<li>Fixed notification issue after Realtime Note Webhook Url is set</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimized Snap Hutao account's change password and delete account logic in the client</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.14 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue causes the program to crash when opening some specific dialog boxes <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1052" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1052</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1054" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1054</a></li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.13</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added option to forward Realtime Note data to specified webhook <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/431" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#431</a></li>
<li>Added date range of wish history records <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/899" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#899</a></li>
<li>Added detail view of Adventure Encounter Points in Realtime Note, support view of current Adventure Encounter Points status <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1021" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1021</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed <code>Argument error</code> when using quick launcher from task bar in some conditions <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/925" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#925</a></li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when using advanced launcher in some conditions <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1035" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1035</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that cannot go back on embedded MiHoYo BBS browser <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1023" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1023</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue on converting server from bilibili server to global server <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1041" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1041</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that Snap Hutao cannot identify game client status</li>
<li>Fixed issue on Snap Hutao Cloud status on wish export page, after switching Snap Hutao account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/903" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#903</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Added localization support on prompts that returned by Snap Hutao Cloud server</li>
<li>Redesigned Snap Hutao Passport UI, and now it is embedded in settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1021" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#911</a></li>
<li>Redesigned advanced game launcher page UI</li>
<li>User now can view and select launcher parameters in advanced game launcher</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.11 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed the game launching arguments error (hotfix)</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.10</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed login issue with HoYoverse account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1011" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1011</a> <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1012" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1012</a></li>
<li>Fixed daily check-in issue on HoYoLAB account <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1013" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1013</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that <code>Invalid item</code> error show up when language does not match in UIGFv2.2 data file <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1001" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1001</a></li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when an invalid CAPTCHA Url is input in the setting</li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when an invalid channel setting is given when launching the game</li>
<li>Fixed crash when switching account while WebView2 Runtime version is too low to have necessary feature</li>
<li>Fixed crash issue when an invalid record is displayed in Spiral Abyss page</li>
<li>Fixed a memory overflow issue in embedded pages</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Current game account now can be automatically identified when reaching the game launcher page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.9</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue that prevented the program from launching with the correct window size after the monitor
resolution was changed after exiting the program</li>
<li>Fixed login issue of MiHoYo BBS <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1005" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1005</a></li>
<li>Fixed HoYoverse login issue <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1007" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1007</a></li>
<li>Fixed crash log upload issue in version 1.7.7</li>
<li>Fixed UI display issue on Team Lineup page in Spiral Abyss feature <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/1008" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#1008</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.7</h2>
<ul>
<li>Added card shadow in the following elements to optimize visual effect
<ul>
<li>Dashboard and in-game announcements</li>
<li>Download resource card in advanced game launcher page</li>
<li>Overview card in wish export page</li>
<li>Statistics card in wish export page</li>
<li>Real-time note card</li>
<li>List view in my character page</li>
<li>Image card in character WIKI</li>
<li>Image card in weapon WIKI</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed top margin error under grid view</li>
<li>Fixed grid view crash issues from multiple causes</li>
<li>Fixed server conversion issue from CN server to Bilibili server</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Optimize button position for manual account validation
<ul>
<li>You can now find it directly from account panel</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Added retry logic for fetching abyss record and record upload
<ul>
<li>User who does not set up CAPTURE verification API can retry after manually validating account from account panel</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>## 1.7.6</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added mouse auto click feature triggered by F8, under Administrator privilege mode
<ul>
<li>In the upcoming Genshin Impact 4.1 and 4.2 version, this feature may help you skip some task conversation you dislike</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed crash issue when switching account after validating cookie on Realtime Notes page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/947" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#947</a></li>
<li>Fixed failure of matching current in-game account after rebooting Snap Hutao and game client <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/865" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#865</a></li>
<li>Fixed display issue on Achievement page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/956" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#956</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue that Genshin Impact 4.1 version metadata will cause program to crash on Spiral Abyss page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Optimized some user interface details on some pages</li>
<li>Optimized announcement text color in some particular situation</li>
<li>Optimized download logic of downloading static images</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.5 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added version number for each achievement</li>
<li>Added monster waves data in Abyss Data page (data provided by <a href="https://space.bilibili.com/3537104994831140" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@å¦®å¯å°‘å¥³</a>)</li>
<li>Added Microsoft Store rating button on settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/876" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#876</a></li>
<li>Added a document button above user panel, user will be redirected to current page's document when click on it <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/875" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#875</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed game launcher card on dashboard showing empty account issue <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/924" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#924</a></li>
<li>Fixed achievement status cannot be saved when be manually unchecked <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/880" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#880</a></li>
<li>Fixed issue that Realtime Note verification on wrong MiHoYo BBS account</li>
<li>Fixed issue that sometime spiral abyss statistics data are missing</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimizations
<ul>
<li>Optimized some error messages, added solution hints <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/930" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#930</a></li>
<li>Snap Hutao Announcements content on dashboard now is copyable <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/929" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#929</a></li>
<li><strong>Abyss Stats page is now merged into Abyss Records page</strong></li>
<li>Optimized time format in multiple places</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.4 </h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Added option to change PowerShell entry in settings page</li>
<li>Added option to create desktop shortcut in settings page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/912" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#912</a></li>
<li>Added option to switch display of cards on home dashboard</li>
<li>Added batch-add to Dev Plan option on My Character page</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue which event start time is not accurate on Home Dashboard <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/887" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#887</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue on My Character page that caused crashes when clicking on weapon that is not synchronized by Enka API <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/904" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#904</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue of weapon value display error on My Character page <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/907" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#907</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where Bilibili server cannot be converted to some other servers <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/893" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#893</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where fetching Novice Wish history will cause the program to crash <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/917" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#917</a></li>
<li>Fixed an issue where a Dev Plan was not pre-selected before entering the Dev Plan page, which had caused the
Dev Plan page to need to be entered at least once to add a Dev Plan archive</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that failed to claim checkin reward when triggered anti-bot verification, even when anti-bot API returns success result</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Optimized monsters' display order on Monster WIKI page</li>
<li>Optimized launch speed of Wish History page</li>
<li>Optimized local database thread on UI display functions</li>
<li>Optimized the scrolling experience for some views of Dev Plan, it may now take longer for views to be loaded</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.3</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed the issue of HoYoverse web login not working</li>
<li>Upgraded the Windows App SDK version to fix the issue where the top of the title bar could not resize the window</li>
<li>Adjusted the prompt for UIGF v2.2 file import failures, now allowing for faster issue identification based on IDs</li>
<li>Fixed the issue where the user panel would display a successful claim of login rewards even if it failed</li>
<li>Fixed the problem where launching the game from the taskbar would open both the game window and the main program window simultaneously</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.2</h2>
<ul>
<li>Wish Export
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue where full refresh was not working correctly.</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where no-error UIGF files were not being imported correctly</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where Hutao Cloud records were not being retrieved correctly</li>
<li>Adjusted the UI of the Hutao Cloud window to display the number of wishes corresponding to the UID archive</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>My Characters
<ul>
<li>Adjusted the UI to make it more compact</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Adjusted the UI of the homepage notifications to align them with the right edge</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.7.0</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add a startup guide to help user familiarize Snap Hutao on start launch
<ul>
<li>Guiding users to select a language</li>
<li>Guiding users to confirm terms of service</li>
<li>Guiding users to install Segoe Fluent Icons font and WebView2 Runtime</li>
<li>Guiding users to download static assets</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Main Interface
<ul>
<li>Adjusted icon styles in the navigation bar</li>
<li>Fixed a bug where adjusting window size could lead to unexpected crashes</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>User Panel
<ul>
<li>Adjusted styles of the user panel</li>
<li>Added a button to allow the current user to claim sign-in rewards</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where in some cases, the current user and character could not be selected correctly on startup</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Home Dashboard
<ul>
<li>Added Snap Hutao announcement</li>
<li>Real-Time Note now display refresh time for each card</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where Real-Time Note card fail to load correctly, leading program to freezing or crashing</li>
<li>Corrected start/end times for certain event announcements</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where some paragraphs were not displaying correctly when viewing details of certain announcements</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Game Launch (Advanced Launcher)
<ul>
<li>Added game status indicator text to the command bar</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where server switch function was not working</li>
<li>Adjusted server switch function logic to allow retries after resource download failure</li>
<li>Adjusted unlocked frame rate logic; game process will automatically end if unlocking fails</li>
<li>Removed multi-client</li>
<li>Fixed an issue in resource download page where game client had no names and couldn't be downloaded</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Wish History
<ul>
<li>Adjusted card style on the overview page, making items larger and collapsing multiple text items</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where entering the wish history page without logging in or without Snap Hutao Cloud service caused errors</li>
<li>Fixed progress bar and color display issues in the card list view on the overview page</li>
<li>Fixed incorrect text for Snap Hutao Cloud's upload reward</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that UIGF formatted data file with incorrect item ID can be imported</li>
<li>Fixed the issue that failed to locate game cache directory</li>
<li>Optimized page load speed when there is a large amount of items</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Achievement
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting achievement categories in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
<li>Optimized page load speed</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Real-Time Notes
<ul>
<li>Adjusted the style of the <code>Verify Current User and Role</code> button</li>
<li>Adjusted the style of the notification settings view</li>
<li>Added an option to disable auto-refresh for real-time notes (toggle available only in non-administrator mode; users who have previously accessed the real-time notes page in administrator mode might not be able to toggle this option)</li>
<li>Adjusted the style of real-time notes</li>
<li>Adjusted text prompts for locked Serenitea Pot and unowned Parametric Transformations</li>
<li>Added previous refresh time for each Real-time note cards</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>My Characters
<ul>
<li>Adjusted width of character list when using list view</li>
<li>Added a button to toggle display of refresh time in command bar</li>
<li>Added previous refresh time for each refresh function</li>
<li>Added display of times artifacts were enhanced in character details</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Dev Plan
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue failure of saving active archive when switching page from dev plan to others</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Character WIKI
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting character in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Weapon WIKI
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting weapon in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
<li>Added ascension material section for each weapon</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Monster WIKI
<ul>
<li>Fixed a display issue that occurs after selecting monster in list/grid view and switching to the other view type</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Settings
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue that unable to clear game cache directory</li>
<li>Added configuration field for Geetest CAPTCHA verification API, correct configuration on this field can handle anti-bot verification from MiYouShe</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Improved program frame rate performance</li>
<li>Optimized memory usage for multi-thread scheduling</li>
<li>Optimized loading speed of item image assets</li>
<li>Adjusted database read/write methods to optimize memory usage and responsiveness</li>
<li>Adjusted text prompts for return codes <code>-100</code> and <code>-10001</code> to help users better understand their meanings</li>
<li>Other minor changes</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.6</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao Cloud tab will show expiration time and developer's license on the wish history page now</li>
<li>Wish statistics are now available on the wish history page, with data supported by Snap Hutao Cloud</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fix failure of web cache refresh method for wish history export</li>
<li>Fix Traditional Chinese metadata loading error</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.5</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Japanese is now a new language option;
community members can contribute Japanese language on <a href="https://translate.hut.ao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">translate.hut.ao</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue that cannot add weapons to dev plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/747" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #745</a></li>
<li>Issue on some users failed to unlock frame rate limit under certain environment
<a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/747" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #747</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Refine dashboard UI</li>
<li>Introducing Metadata v2</li>
<li>Sorting order of materials in dev plan <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/749" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #749</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.4</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Export wish history data with <a href="https://uigf.org/zh/standards/UIGF.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">UIGF v2.3</a> data format</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>FPS unlocker <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/733" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue #733</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>When running program without administrator privilege, features require administrator privilege will have text hints</li>
<li>Support of HoYoLAB</li>
<li>Localization updates</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.3</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Home dashboard, including Hutao Cloud account, game launcher, wish history, achievement stat and real-time notes</li>
<li>Enable notification box will now automatically hide in-app notification</li>
<li>CN server option without TapTap account</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue that user cannot get Hutao Cloud bonus after uploading Abyss record</li>
<li>Issue that cannot sign in to HoYoLAB with Facebook</li>
<li>HoYoLAB check-in issue</li>
<li>Issue when facing empty value during wish history fetch progress</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li><strong>Project refactoring, brings a 20% performance improvement</strong></li>
<li>Add localization support for WIKI features</li>
<li>Add support for all international channels (which affect payment gateway)
<ul>
<li>Supporting HoYoverse official, Google Pay, Epic</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>When Unlock framerate limit is enabled, limit value can be modified during the game, and will take effect immediately</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.2 </h2>
<ul>
<li>New Feature
<ul>
<li><strong>Wish history cloud backup</strong> based on Hutao account system
<ul>
<li>Currently, sponsors on AFDIAN and beta users will receive corresponding cloud membership time; All registered users will receive 5 days membership time after uploading Abyss record.</li>
<li>This feature will be optimized constantly in the following 1.6 versions</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue that BiliBili server account cannot receive data for Real-time Notes</li>
<li>Issue on HoYoLAB login</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimize
<ul>
<li>Static assets download logic</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.6.0</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Hutao account system with registration and login available now</li>
<li>Support of HoYoLAB account login, and add its support to the following features:
<ul>
<li>Web login and Stoken Cookie login</li>
<li>Abyss record</li>
<li>Daily check-in reward</li>
<li>My character</li>
<li>Real-time notes</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Performance of frame rate unlock</li>
<li>Multi-client</li>
<li>Now users must unlock advanced features in the settings page before actually using them</li>
<li>Settings page layout</li>
<li>Tiles image on Windows 10</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.5.4</h2>
<ul>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Game Launcher
<ul>
<li>Game resource package download</li>
<li>Allow multiple Genshin Impact process to run</li>
<li>Allow users to select the specified monitor to start the game</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>New icons have been used</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Issue caused unlimited file writing during server switch</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimize default language selection</li>
<li>Allow device ID be copied with button</li>
<li>Setting page UI optimization</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.5.1</h2>
<ul>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Replace <code>JumpList</code> menus with <code>JumpTask</code>,</li>
<li>Add option to allow user set language over system default setting</li>
<li>Add translation contribution entry</li>
<li>Add options to reset the image resource</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Add
<ul>
<li>Monster WIKI</li>
<li>Korean translation</li>
<li>Internationalized Metadata</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.4.15</h2>
<ul>
<li>New
<ul>
<li>Static image reset method</li>
<li>Cookie refresh</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fix
<ul>
<li>Fix <a href="/advanced/known-issue.html#_2-%E6%9C%8D%E5%8A%A1%E5%99%A8%E5%88%87%E6%8D%A2%E5%AF%BC%E8%87%B431-4302%E6%8A%A5%E9%94%99" target="_blank">#2 31-4302 caused by server switch</a></li>
<li>Fix the failure of clearing scheduled task in some specific situations</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Optimization
<ul>
<li>Optimize Dev Plan UI <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/486" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">#486</a></li>
<li>Optimize English and Traditional Chinese translations</li>
<li>Add hints when Windows long path limits are triggered</li>
<li>Optimize wake-up for scheduled tasks</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.4.14</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fix issue that new dev plan cannot be added</li>
<li>Support English UI</li>
<li>Other minor bug fix</li>
</ul>
<h2>1.4.11</h2>
<ul>
<li>First version on Microsoft Store</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/update-log.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Program Exceptions</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/exceptions.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/exceptions.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Common Program Exceptions</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao utilizes specific error codes to indicate particular errors. If you encounter a program error during usage and have an error code, you can try searching for it on this page.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 06:20:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This document lists common issues and corresponding solutions that may occur while using Snap Hutao.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/exceptions.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localization</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/i18n.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/i18n.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Localization</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao hopes to help players from all over the world. In addition to maintaining the Simplified Chinese and English versions of the program, we also accept translations provided by community members.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <category>i18n</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 06:31:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao primarily focuses on supporting the Genshin Impact Chinese server. Currently, we are gradually improving support for oversea servers, encompassing language localization and feature internationalization.
Due to the different types of restrictions on both types of server, the implementation of some features may vary. For example, the wish history export for oversea servers does not support the more convenient SToken refresh method.</p>
<h2>Language Support</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao currently supports the following languages:</p>
<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th>Language</th>
      <th>Progress</th>
      <th>Maintainers</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td>Simplified Chinese</td>
      <td>Base Language</td>
      <td rowspan="2" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: middle;">Maintained by DGP Studio</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>English</td>
      <td style="text-align: center; vertical-align: middle;">
        <img alt="en translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=en&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.1.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Traditional Chinese</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="zh-TW translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=zh-TW&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.13.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
      <td rowspan="2" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: middle;">Maintained by Crowdin community members</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Japanese</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="ja translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=ja&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.6.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Korean</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="ko translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=ko&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.7.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
      <td rowspan="2" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: middle;">Partially maintained by Crowdin community members; <br>Partially translated using Google Gemini</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Indonesian</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="id translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=id&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.4.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>German</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="de translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=de&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.0.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
      <td rowspan="10" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: middle;">Translated using Google Gemini</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Spanish</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="es-ES translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=es-ES&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.2.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>French</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="fr translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=fr&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.3.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Italian</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="it translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=it&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.5.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Portuguese</td>
       <td>
        <img alt="pt-PT translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=pt-PT&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.8.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Russian</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="ru translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=ru&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.9.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
     <tr>
      <td>Thai</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="th translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=th&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.10.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Turkish</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="tr translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=tr&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.11.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Vietnamese</td>
      <td>
        <img alt="vi translation" src="https://img.shields.io/badge/dynamic/json?color=blue&amp;label=vi&amp;style=flat&amp;logo=crowdin&amp;query=%24.progress.12.data.translationProgress&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbadges.awesome-crowdin.com%2Fstats-15670597-565845.json">
      </td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<h2>Participate in Globalization</h2>
<ul>
<li>We have created an issue named <code>[Hoyolab]: Globalization support</code> on GitHub <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/638" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Issue</a>
<ul>
<li>We will update the current internationalization progress of the main program in this issue.</li>
<li>You can announce your participation in the internationalization support of a certain part of the main program here, and we will provide support for it.
<ul>
<li>We also welcome direct Pull Requests through branches.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>You can participate in the client translation work at <a href="https://translate.hut.ao" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">translate.hut.ao</a></strong></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/i18n.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/star-request.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/star-request.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml"></source>
      <description>If you believe Snap Hutao is a good project and helps you, you can support us by the following ways Star our project on GitHub â­ Snap.Hutao hutao.stars Snap.Hutao.Docs hutao.doc...</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>If you believe Snap Hutao is a good project and helps you, you can support us by the following ways</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Star our project on GitHub â­
<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Snap.Hutao</a> <img src="https://img.shields.io/github/stars/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?style=plastic&amp;color=red" alt="hutao.stars" loading="lazy"></li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Snap.Hutao.Docs</a> <img src="https://img.shields.io/github/stars/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs?style=plastic&amp;color=red" alt="hutao.docs.stars" loading="lazy"></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Promote our project in your network</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="https://img.shields.io/github/commit-activity/y/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?style=for-the-badge" alt="commit_activity" loading="lazy"> <img src="https://img.shields.io/github/last-commit/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?label=Hutao Last Commit&amp;style=for-the-badge" alt="hutao-last-commit" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.shields.io/github/stars/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao?style=plastic&amp;color=red" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other Common Issues</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/FAQ.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/FAQ.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Other Common Issues</source>
      <description>This page contains some common questions and solutions related to user network and program lifecycle issues.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 08:44:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>How to Create a Desktop Shortcut for Snap Hutao (Non-Administrator Mode)</h2>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Community Power</p>
<p>Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao.Docs/issues/12" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CzHUV for providing the solution</a></p>
</div>
<ol>
<li>Use <code>Win+R</code> to open the Run window, and enter <code>shell:AppsFolder</code> in the input box.
<img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01Jj8c6i1g6du728e5A_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="Run" loading="lazy"></li>
<li>Windows will open the application directory. Find Snap Hutao.</li>
<li>Right-click the Snap Hutao icon and select "Create shortcut".</li>
<li>Follow the system prompts to create a desktop shortcut.</li>
</ol>
<h2>How to Create a Desktop Shortcut for Snap Hutao (Administrator Mode)</h2>
<ul>
<li>Go to the program settings page of Snap Hutao and click the "Create shortcut" button to generate a shortcut with administrator privileges on the desktop.</li>
</ul>
<h2>How to Make Snap Hutao Start Automatically on Boot</h2>
<h3>Method 1: Using a Batch File</h3>
<ol>
<li>Create a batch file. Refer to the command provided in <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/184" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">this Issue</a> to make Snap Hutao run directly with administrator privileges.</li>
<li>Configure the batch file to start automatically using the following methods:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Create a scheduled task to execute the batch file when the system starts.</li>
<li>Add the batch file to the system's startup items.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Method 2: Using a Tool</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use a program like <code>SkipUAC</code> to make Snap Hutao start silently with administrator privileges.</li>
</ul>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Notes</p>
<p>The above methods may fail due to system configurations or other issues. Snap Hutao does not directly support automatic startup on boot; attempting these methods is at your own risk.</p>
</div>
<h2>Unable to Start Snap Hutao in Administrator Mode</h2>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Scope of the issue</strong>: Only applies to Windows 10 versions lower than 22H2.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>When the user's system version is lower than <code>Windows Build 19045</code> (i.e., Windows 10 22H2 version), it may not be possible to start Snap Hutao in administrator mode.</li>
<li><strong>Solution</strong>: It is recommended to upgrade the system to the latest version of Windows 10 to avoid such compatibility issues.</li>
</ul>
<h2>How to Use Snap Hutao with a Network Proxy</h2>
<blockquote>
<p>Snap Hutao provides a good cloud network structure to ensure users around the world can enjoy high-quality services.</p>
</blockquote>
<ol>
<li>Configure system or software proxy services.</li>
<li>It is recommended to enable <code>Loopback Network</code>. For a detailed tutorial, see <a href="/en/advanced/loopback.html" target="_blank">here</a>.</li>
</ol>
<h1>Notification Icon Creation Failed</h1>
<p>Open PowerShell and run the following command to fix the issue</p>
<div class="language-powershell line-numbers-mode" data-highlighter="shiki" data-ext="powershell" data-title="powershell" style="--shiki-light:#383A42;--shiki-dark:#abb2bf;--shiki-light-bg:#FAFAFA;--shiki-dark-bg:#282c34"><pre class="shiki shiki-themes one-light one-dark-pro vp-code"><code><span class="line"><span style="--shiki-light:#383A42;--shiki-dark:#ABB2BF">irm hut.ao</span><span style="--shiki-light:#383A42;--shiki-dark:#56B6C2">/</span><span style="--shiki-light:#383A42;--shiki-dark:#ABB2BF">install.ps1 | iex</span></span></code></pre>
<div class="line-numbers" aria-hidden="true" style="counter-reset:line-number 0"><div class="line-number"></div></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/faq.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Data and Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/privacy-notice.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/privacy-notice.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">User Data and Privacy Notice</source>
      <description>Please read this page carefully to understand the user data handling and privacy rights for the Snap Hutao project.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 07:17:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao is committed to protecting user privacy and data security. The following provides detailed information about our user data handling and privacy rights.</p>
<h2>Personal Information Data</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao is designed with respect for user privacy as its primary principle, and the project itself does not actively collect any personal information data.</p>
<h2>Regular Data Usage</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao handles and uses user data according to the following rules during its operation:</p>
<h3>Local Storage</h3>
<p>Snap Hutao will store the following information as database files in the user's <strong>data directory</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>MiYouShe and HoYoLAB Cookies</strong></li>
<li><strong>Snap Hutao's configuration information</strong></li>
<li><strong>All of the user's local data</strong></li>
</ul>
<h3>Error and Statistical Information Collection</h3>
<p>To optimize software performance and improve user experience, Snap Hutao may collect the following information anonymously:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>User Device ID</strong></li>
<li><strong>Program error and crash logs</strong></li>
<li><strong>Statistical information of user activity data</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>This data is used for development and statistical purposes only.</p>
<h3>Data Upload</h3>
<h4>Snap Hutao Database (Abyss Record, Abyss Stats, and Imaginarium Theater)</h4>
<p>When the user chooses to use the <code>Upload Data</code> feature, the following data will be uploaded to the Snap Hutao API:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>User's Game UID</strong></li>
<li><strong>User's Spiral Abyss records</strong></li>
<li><strong>User's character information and their equipped weapons and artifacts</strong></li>
</ul>
<h4>Advanced Launcher (Server Switching)</h4>
<p>After using the <code>Server Switching</code> feature in the <code>Advanced Launcher</code>, Snap Hutao will store necessary files related to server conversion in the local data directory.</p>
<h4>Snap Hutao Passport Function</h4>
<p>Snap Hutao Cloud Service will encrypt and store the following information:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>The email address used for registration</strong></li>
<li><strong>The encrypted password</strong></li>
</ul>
<h2>Trusted Domains</h2>
<p>The following are the trusted domains officially held by the Snap Hutao project. Please be wary of information from domains outside this list to avoid unknown sources (including websites, emails, etc.).</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>hut.ao</strong></li>
<li><strong>snapgenshin.com</strong></li>
<li><strong>dgp-studio.cn</strong> (Only used for public email contact)</li>
<li><strong>snapgenshin.cn</strong> (Only used for sending system emails)</li>
<li><strong>snaphutao.com</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Please always verify that the resources you are accessing come from the above domains to ensure data security.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/privacy-notice.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obtaining Stoken-containing Cookies Using Third-Party Tools</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/get-stoken-cookie-from-the-third-party.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/get-stoken-cookie-from-the-third-party.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Obtaining Stoken-containing Cookies Using Third-Party Tools</source>
      <description>There are some third-party tools that can help you obtain the cookie from the miHoYo community with the Stoken field value and use it for Snap Hutao.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <category>Third-Party Tools</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:24:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Warning</p>
<ul>
<li>The software, open-source projects, and resources mentioned in the following steps are sourced from the internet and are not affiliated with DGP-Studio.</li>
<li>This documentation provides solutions for educational purposes only. Specific operations and their consequences are not associated with this project.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2>Android</h2>
<p>Android users can utilize the open-source project GetToken to acquire cookies containing the Stoken field.</p>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">GetToken Open-Source Project</p>
<ul>
<li>GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/HolographicHat/GetToken" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HolographicHat/GetToken</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<ul>
<li>The GetToken project's release includes two APK files, both ultimately achieving the same outcome. Choose the version suitable for your device:
<ul>
<li><code>app-release.apk</code> is an LSPosed plugin that enables users to use GetToken functionality within the official miHoYo community app.</li>
<li>APK files ending with <code>lspatched</code> are modified versions of the miHoYo community app with GetToken functionality included.
<ul>
<li>You'll need to uninstall the official miHoYo app to install this version.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After enabling the plugin or installing the modified miHoYo app, open the miHoYo app, click "Me" at the bottom, and log in to your account.</li>
<li>Click ðŸ”‘ icon in the top right corner.</li>
<li>Check the <code>Stoken</code> option.</li>
<li>Click <code>Copy Login Information</code>.</li>
<li>Send the copied Stoken to the computer where the Snap Hutao is installed.</li>
<li>In the Snap Hutao's account login section, click <code>Manual Input</code>.</li>
<li>Enter the previously obtained cookie. You should now complete the login process.</li>
</ul>
<h2>iOS</h2>
<p>iOS Users can download the packet capture software Stream from the App Store to obtain cookies containing the Stoken field.</p>
<ul>
<li>Download <a href="https://apps.apple.com/cn/app/stream/id1312141691" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Stream</a> from the App Store.</li>
<li>Perform packet capture analysis on the domain <code>api-takumi.mihoyo.com</code>.</li>
<li>Locate and copy the data containing <code>Stoken</code>.
<ul>
<li>It will be in the form of <code>stuid=****;stoken=v2****;mid=****;</code>.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Send the copied Stoken to the computer where the Snap Hutao is installed.</li>
<li>In the Snap Hutao's account login section, click <code>Manual Input</code>.</li>
<li>Enter the obtained cookie. You should now complete the login process.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/get-stoken-cookie-from-the-third-party.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development Plan</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/develop-plan.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/develop-plan.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Development Plan</source>
      <description>The Development Plan feature in Snap Hutao assists players in creating lists of goals for character and weapon development, making it easy to track progress and required materials.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:18:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="/images/202501/character_develop_plan.webp" alt="dev-plan" loading="lazy"></p>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>Green icons indicate items that can be farmed on the current day.</p>
</div>
<h2>Adding Development Goals to the Material Checklist</h2>
<h3>Adding from Wiki Data</h3>
<ol>
<li>In the left sidebar of Snap Hutao, click the "Character Data" or "Weapon Data" feature.</li>
<li>Click the "Development Calculator" button in the upper right corner of the interface.</li>
<li>In the "Add or Update to Current Development Plan" window that pops up, fill in the starting and target levels for the character or weapon.</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>For development goals added from Wiki data, the default starting level is Level 1 (adjustable as needed).</li>
</ul>
<h3>Adding from My Characters Data</h3>
<ol>
<li>In the left sidebar, click the "My Characters" feature page and select the character you want to add to the development plan.</li>
<li>Click the "Development Plan - Current Character &amp; Weapon" button in the upper right corner of the interface.</li>
<li>In the "Add or Update to Current Development Plan" window that pops up, fill in the starting and target levels for the character.</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>For development goals added from player data, the default starting level is the character's current level.</li>
<li>For more details, see the <a href="/en/features/character-data.html#sync-character-data" target="_blank">My Characters</a> document.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Creating a New Plan and Syncing In-Game Inventory Items</h2>
<ol>
<li>In the left sidebar, click the "Development Plan" feature.</li>
<li>Click "Create New Plan" in the upper right corner and name it.</li>
<li>Follow the instructions in <a href="/en/features/character-data.html#sync-character-data" target="_blank">Adding the Currently Selected Character to the Development Calculator</a> or <a href="/en/features/character-wiki.html#add-a-character-from-the-wiki-to-the-development-plan" target="_blank">Adding a Character from the Wiki to the Development Plan</a> to add characters to the new plan.
<ul>
<li>At least one character with an incomplete level or weapon level must be added; characters at max level cannot be added to the development plan.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Switch to the "Inventory Items" tab and click the "Sync Inventory Items" button.
<ul>
<li>The system will automatically sync the inventory items of the currently logged-in account.</li>
<li>You can select different development plans for different accounts using the dropdown option box to the left of the "Sync Inventory Items" button.</li>
<li>Click any item icon or number area to manually edit the quantity of that material.</li>
<li>The modified item information will automatically be linked to the selected development plan.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>View the estimated number of days needed to farm the materials on the "Material Statistics" page.</li>
</ol>
<p><img src="/images/202501/character_develop_predict.webp" alt="Material Statistics" loading="lazy"></p>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>If the item names and images are inconsistent or display issues such as stacking occur, switch pages and then return to this page to resolve the problem. This issue is caused by Microsoft and cannot be completely fixed at this time.</p>
</div>
<h2>Delete a Development Plan</h2>
<p>In the upper-right section of the Snap Hutao interface, click the "Delete Plan" button to delete the current development plan. After deletion, the character information, inventory item information, and other data in the plan will be cleared.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hut.ao/images/202501/character_develop_plan.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapon WIKI</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/weapon-wiki.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/weapon-wiki.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Weapon WIKI</source>
      <description>The Weapon WIKI is an integrated weapon database within Snap Hutao. Players can use this feature to query detailed information about all weapons in Genshin Impact and select suitable weapons for their characters.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 09:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN018rs0K91g6e0ylQ4XT_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="weapon-wiki" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The Weapon Data is a built-in WIKI feature in Snap Hutao, specifically designed for querying information about all weapons in Genshin Impact, including their <strong>appearance, stats, refinement effects, and recommended pairings</strong>. With this feature, players can efficiently choose the right weapons for their characters and get detailed weapon data support.</p>
<h2>Included Data</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Weapon List</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The list supports two display modes, which can be switched using the button in the upper-left corner:
<ul>
<li><strong>List View</strong>: Displays weapon thumbnails, names, and some information.</li>
<li><strong>Grid View</strong>: Displays more weapon items in thumbnail form.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>In "List View", click on a thumbnail or name to jump to the detailed introduction page of the weapon.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Basic Weapon Information</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Weapon icon comparisons before and after ascension, making it easier to recognize visual changes after upgrading.</li>
<li>Full-body image display, showing the complete appearance of the weapon.</li>
<li>Weapon introduction, providing the weapon's background story or related descriptions.</li>
<li>Supports switching to the corresponding level to view various weapon stats (such as Base ATK, secondary attributes, etc.).</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Weapon Refinement Information</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Displays the specific attribute bonuses for each refinement rank, making it easier for players to evaluate refinement value.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Weapon Ascension Materials</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lists the materials and quantities required for upgrading and ascending.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Weapon Usage Recommendations</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Based on Snap Hutao database statistics, shows recommended character pairings and usage scenarios, helping players optimize their weapon choices.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN018rs0K91g6e0ylQ4XT_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Settings</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-settings.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-settings.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Software Settings</source>
      <description>The Settings page of Snap Hutao contains various options to customize different aspects of the program. By modifying the settings on this page, users can personalize Snap Hutao to achieve the desired user experience.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 07:34:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01wDQfRa1g6e0ylR4ov_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="settings" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The following content is presented in the order of the settings features within Snap Hutao.</p>
<h2>About Snap Hutao</h2>
<p>This section contains the following information:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Snap Hutao icon: You can view its original image on the <a href="/" target="_blank">homepage</a>.</li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DGP-Studio</a> is authorized to use this icon.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Administrator Mode Tools</h2>
<p>On the right side of the settings page, administrator mode tools are provided for users who require them.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Create shortcut</strong>: Creates a shortcut on the desktop to launch Snap Hutao with administrator privileges.</li>
<li><strong>Restart as administrator</strong>: Right-click the Snap Hutao icon in the bottom right corner of the taskbar and select "Restart as administrator" from the pop-up menu to obtain administrator privileges.</li>
</ul>
<h2>CAPTCHA</h2>
<ul>
<li>If the daily check-in and Real-time Notes features trigger a <code>-1034</code> error from miHoYo, you can configure a third-party verification service through this setting to automatically pass the Geetest verification.</li>
<li>Once configured successfully, Real-time Notes and check-in will automatically complete the verification, avoiding request failures.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Appearance Settings</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Language</strong>: Defaults to the system language; users can forcibly set the display language.</li>
<li><strong>Week Start Day</strong>: Sets the display date for the first column in the game calendar.</li>
<li><strong>Background Material</strong>:
<ul>
<li>Options include None, Acrylic, Mica (Windows 11 only), and Mica Alt (Windows 11 only).</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Color Theme</strong>: Allows switching between Light and Dark themes; defaults to the system settings.</li>
<li><strong>Background Image</strong>:
<ul>
<li>Options include No background image, Local random image, Bing daily image, Snap Hutao daily image, and Official launcher wallpaper.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Notification Area Icon</strong>: Choose whether to display the Snap Hutao icon in the notification area.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Storage Management</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Data Folder</strong>:
<ul>
<li><strong>Open Folder</strong>: Opens the folder containing user data and metadata.</li>
<li><strong>Change Data Directory</strong>: Changes the storage location of the data folder.</li>
<li><strong>Delete Server Conversion Cache</strong>: Clears the cache generated by the game server transfer feature.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Cache Folder</strong>:
<ul>
<li><strong>Open Folder</strong>: Opens the folder containing the image cache.</li>
<li><strong>Reset Image Resource</strong>: Deletes and re-downloads image resources.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Shortcut Key Settings</h2>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Administrator Privileges Required</p>
<p>You need to launch Snap Hutao with administrator privileges to modify shortcut key settings.</p>
</div>
<ul>
<li>Set up automatic mouse click and keyboard shortcut key functions.</li>
<li>If shortcut key registration fails (due to insufficient permissions or conflicts), a prompt will appear at the bottom of the interface, and the user needs to reconfigure the settings.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Home Settings</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Home Cards</strong>: Set whether to display specific feature cards (such as Launch Game, Wish History).</li>
<li><strong>Calendar Server</strong>: Modify the game calendar data source.</li>
<li><strong>Announcement Server</strong>: Change the game announcement data source.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Game Settings</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Delete Game Webpage Cache</strong>: Used to resolve issues with abnormal Wish History refreshes.</li>
<li><strong>Download Speed Limit</strong>: Limits the download speed of game resources.</li>
<li><strong>Convert Server Mode</strong>: Sets the execution mode for server conversion.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Wish History Settings</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Hide History Activities with No Records</strong>: Hides wish activities with no records.</li>
<li><strong>Hide Unobtained Wish Items</strong>: Hides unobtained wish items.</li>
<li><strong>Data Migration</strong>: Supports import and export in UIGF 4 format.</li>
</ul>
<h2>WebView Settings</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Share Save Mode</strong>:
<ul>
<li>Choose how to save shared images, including saving to the clipboard or locally.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01wDQfRa1g6e0ylR4ov_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Notes</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/real-time-notes.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/real-time-notes.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Real-time Notes</source>
      <description>The Real-time Notes feature in Snap Hutao synchronizes dynamic information from Genshin Impact to your local computer by periodically refreshing your MiYouShe data. It allows you to set conditions for message reminders and push notifications based on your preferences.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:26:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Prerequisites</p>
<p>This feature requires you to log in to your MiYouShe / HoYoLAB account in Snap Hutao. See the <a href="/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html" target="_blank">MiHoYo Multi-Account Switching</a> document for login instructions.</p>
</div>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01YUyKil1g6e0x3SpKX_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="live-data-tracking" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2>Adding Real-time Notes</h2>
<ol>
<li>Click the "Add Real-time Notes" button.</li>
<li>In the "Add Real-time Notes" pop-up window, find the game character UID you want to add and click the plus button to its right.</li>
<li>The added game character will be displayed on the "Real-time Notes" page.
<ul>
<li>Real-time Notes will automatically refresh data at fixed intervals.</li>
<li>Click "Notification Settings" in the upper-right corner of the window to set the refresh interval.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>To get the latest data immediately, click the "Refresh Now" button.</li>
<li>If a <code>-1034</code> error occurs when refreshing data, it means that miHoYo's anti-bot risk control mechanism has been triggered. This can be resolved by configuring invisible verification in the Snap Hutao settings.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Verifying User and Character</h2>
<p>If you are using a MiYouShe account, the anti-bot mechanism may trigger a verification code, preventing Real-time Notes data from refreshing.
The following steps can solve this issue:</p>
<ol>
<li>Click the "Verify Current User and Character" button in the upper-left corner of the Real-time Notes page.</li>
<li>Snap Hutao will display a verification window. Complete the verification to refresh the data for the affected account.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Global Notification Settings</h2>
<p>Clicking "Notification Settings" in the upper-right corner of the window allows you to configure the global behavior of the Real-time Notes feature, including:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Enable/Disable Automatic Data Refresh</strong>.</li>
<li><strong>Set the Automatic Data Refresh Interval</strong>.</li>
<li><strong>Do Not Disturb Mode</strong>:
<ul>
<li>When enabled, notifications will only appear in the system notification center.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>High Priority Notifications</strong>:
<ul>
<li>Prevents notifications from being automatically moved to the action center, but may interfere with daily use.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Custom Data Forwarding Webhook</strong>:
<ul>
<li>Snap Hutao allows users to forward Real-time Notes data to third-party programs to reduce direct requests to the miHoYo API.</li>
<li>Enter the third-party program's <code>HTTP API</code> interface address in the "Real-time Notes Webhook URL" field. Snap Hutao will forward the raw data to this interface using a <code>POST</code> request.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Account-Specific Settings</h2>
<ol>
<li>Hover your mouse over the Real-time Notes window of the character whose settings you want to modify.</li>
<li>Click the settings button in the upper-right corner of the window to access the following settings options:
<ul>
<li><strong>Original Resin Reminder Threshold</strong> (range: 0â€“200)</li>
<li><strong>Realm Currency Reminder Threshold</strong> (range: 0â€“2400)</li>
<li><strong>Enable Parametric Transformer Reminder</strong> (on/off)</li>
<li><strong>Enable Daily Commission Cap Reminder</strong> (on/off)</li>
<li><strong>Enable Expedition Completion Reminder</strong> (on/off)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After modifying the settings, click the "Save" button to save the current settings.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Deleting a Character</h2>
<ol>
<li>Hover your mouse over the Real-time Notes window of the character you want to delete.</li>
<li>Click the remove button in the upper-right corner of the window to delete the Real-time Notes for that character.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
<h3>Why does setting automatic refresh for Real-time Notes display "Failed to modify Scheduled Task"?</h3>
<ul>
<li>Automatic refresh of Real-time Notes relies on the Windows Task Scheduler.</li>
<li>To avoid permission issues, Snap Hutao sets task schedules in non-administrator mode.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Solutions:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>If you have enabled automatic refresh in an older version, you can manually delete the old task schedule in Task Scheduler. The task schedule name is <code>SnapHutaoDailyNoteRefreshTask</code>.</li>
<li>If you have not enabled task schedules before, the current Windows user account may not have sufficient permissions. Try using an administrator account.</li>
<li>If the problem persists, you may need to reinstall the system.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01YUyKil1g6e0x3SpKX_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Characters</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-data.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-data.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">My Characters</source>
      <description>The &amp;quot;My Characters&amp;quot; feature in Snap Hutao can retrieve and display detailed data of the characters under a Genshin Impact account, including level, constellations, talents, and artifact attributes, and provide analysis.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 03:38:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Prerequisites</p>
<p>This feature requires logging in to a MiYouShe or HoYoLAB account. For specific login instructions, please refer to <a href="/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html#mihoyo-bbs-account-switch" target="_blank">MiHoYo BBS Account Switching</a>.</p>
</div>
<p>The "My Characters" feature can read the detailed data of all characters in the user's current account, including levels, constellations, weapons, talents, and artifacts, helping players optimize character development and management.</p>
<p><img src="/images/202501/characters_data.webp" alt="Grid View Example" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2>Synchronize Character Information</h2>
<p>Click the "Synchronize Character Information" button in the upper right corner to update the following data:</p>
<ul>
<li>Character level and constellations</li>
<li>Friendship level</li>
<li>Weapon level and refinement rank</li>
<li>Talent levels</li>
<li>Outfit information</li>
<li>Artifacts and their detailed attributes</li>
</ul>
<h2>Add the Currently Selected Character to the Development Plan</h2>
<ol>
<li>Ensure that the character data has been synchronized.</li>
<li>On the "My Characters" page, select the character you want to add to the Development Plan.</li>
<li>Click the "Development Plan - Current Character and Weapon" button in the upper right corner.</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>The system will automatically pre-fill the synchronized character level, talent level, and weapon level. Users can freely modify the target level.</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="/images/202501/character_develop.webp" alt="Development Example Image" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>After adding, you can view the set development goals on the "Development Plan" feature page.</p>
<p>For a detailed feature description, please refer to the <a href="/en/features/develop-plan.html#development-plan" target="_blank">Development Plan</a> document.</p>
<h2>Export Character Details to Clipboard</h2>
<p>The "My Characters" page supports exporting character data as text:</p>
<ul>
<li>After selecting the target character, click the "Export Text to Clipboard" button in the upper right corner.</li>
<li>The exported data is stored in the system clipboard and can be directly pasted and shared.</li>
<li>An example of the text style is as follows:</li>
</ul>
<div class="language-text line-numbers-mode" data-highlighter="shiki" data-ext="text" data-title="text" style="--shiki-light:#383A42;--shiki-dark:#abb2bf;--shiki-light-bg:#FAFAFA;--shiki-dark-bg:#282c34"><pre class="shiki shiki-themes one-light one-dark-pro vp-code"><code><span class="line"><span>// =====================</span></span>
<span class="line"><span>// Kamisato Ayaka [Lv.90, â˜†5, C6] [Lv.10, Lv.13 (10 +3), Lv.13 (10 +3)]</span></span>
<span class="line"><span>//</span></span></code></pre>
<div class="line-numbers" aria-hidden="true" style="counter-reset:line-number 0"><div class="line-number"></div><div class="line-number"></div><div class="line-number"></div></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hut.ao/images/202501/characters_data.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character WIKI</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-wiki.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/character-wiki.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Character WIKI</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao&amp;apos;s Character WIKI feature integrates basic information, talent values, constellations, and other important data for Genshin Impact characters, providing players with a convenient way to look up character information.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 03:38:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01OKw2Tc1g6e0qbmLe0_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="characters-wiki" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Character Data is a comprehensive built-in query tool in Snap Hutao that covers detailed data such as basic information, talent values, constellations, and character ascension materials of Genshin Impact characters, providing players with a one-stop information query service.</p>
<h2>Included Data</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Character List</strong>
<ul>
<li>Use the button in the upper-left corner of the list to switch the display mode:
<ul>
<li>"List" mode displays character avatars, names, and detailed information.</li>
<li>"Grid" mode displays only character avatars and names.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>In "Grid" mode, click on a character's thumbnail or name to switch back to the "List" view and jump to the corresponding character introduction page.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Data Content</strong>
<ul>
<li><strong>Basic Character Information</strong>
<ul>
<li>Includes basic character information, CV information, attributes, and ascension materials.</li>
<li>Detailed attribute values at each level.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Talents</strong>
<ul>
<li>Basic introduction and detailed values at each level:
<ul>
<li>Normal Attack</li>
<li>Elemental Skill</li>
<li>Elemental Burst</li>
<li>Passive Talents</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Supports switching to view talent values at the corresponding level.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Constellations</strong></li>
<li><strong>Recommended Builds</strong>
<ul>
<li>Provides common character team compositions, weapon recommendations, and artifact set recommendations based on statistical information from the "Snap Hutao Database."</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Other Information</strong>
<ul>
<li>Includes character splash art, namecard, avatar, special dish, outfit information, character stories, and background stories.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Adding a Character from the WIKI to the Development Plan</h2>
<ul>
<li>On the character data page, after selecting a character, click the "Add to Development Plan" button in the upper-right corner to add the character to the development plan.
<ul>
<li>By default, the development plan starts from character level 1 (users can adjust it themselves).</li>
<li>If you need to create a development plan based on an existing character, you can use the development calculation feature on the "<a href="/en/features/character-data.html#%E5%B0%86%E5%BD%93%E5%89%8D%E9%80%89%E5%AE%9A%E8%A7%92%E8%89%B2%E5%8A%A0%E5%85%A5%E5%85%BB%E6%88%90%E8%AE%A1%E7%AE%97" target="_blank">My Characters</a>" page. For specific operations, refer to <a href="/en/features/develop-plan.html#%E5%9F%BA%E4%BA%8E%E7%8E%A9%E5%AE%B6%E6%95%B0%E6%8D%AE%E6%B7%BB%E5%8A%A0" target="_blank">this tutorial</a>.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01OKw2Tc1g6e0qbmLe0_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Game Launcher</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/game-launcher.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/game-launcher.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Advanced Game Launcher</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao&amp;apos;s advanced launcher offers features such as custom launch parameters, server switching, and frame rate unlocking, significantly enhancing the user&amp;apos;s gaming experience.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 03:12:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN014YLRnj1g6e0zQaBl6_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="Game Launcher" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Snap Hutao's advanced launcher provides a more flexible game launch experience through various settings options.</p>
<div class="hint-container caution">
<p class="hint-container-title">Caution</p>
<p>Using <strong>any unofficial software</strong> may <strong>potentially</strong> result in <strong>damage to your virtual property</strong>. Continuing to use the related functions of this software will be deemed as you acknowledging and agreeing to our <a href="/en/statements/tos.html" target="_blank">Terms of Service</a>.</p>
</div>
<h2>Initial Settings</h2>
<ul>
<li>Click "Launch Game" on the left sidebar to enter the advanced launcher feature.
<ul>
<li>The first time you use it, you will be redirected to the settings page to set the game path.</li>
<li><strong>Please select the game's main program path (<code>YuanShen.exe</code>), not the launcher path (<code>launcher.exe</code>).</strong>
<ul>
<li>Example path: <code>D:\miHoYo Launcher\games\Genshin Impact Game\YuanShen.exe</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After successfully detecting the game path, click "Confirm."</li>
<li>If the game is not installed, click the "Install Game" button and follow the prompts to set the installation directory. Snap Hutao will automatically download and install the game.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After configuration, click the "Launch Game" button in the upper right corner to launch the game.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Server Switching</h2>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Permission Notice</p>
<p>Using this feature requires running Snap Hutao with administrator privileges.
Snap Hutao will create a folder named <code>ServerCache</code> in the data directory to store the files needed for switching servers and will automatically check for updates.</p>
</div>
<ol>
<li>Go to the "Launch Game" page.</li>
<li>Select the target server in the "Server" section.</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Available servers include:</strong></p>
<p>| Option          | Server                                                                     |
|</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN014YLRnj1g6e0zQaBl6_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Agreement and Legal Notices</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/tos.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/tos.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">User Agreement and Legal Notices</source>
      <description>User agreement and legal notices of Snap Hutao project.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 14:59:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>General Provisions</h2>
<ul>
<li>This "User Agreement and Legal Disclaimer" (hereinafter referred to as "Terms" or "User Agreement") applies to all software works developed by the DGP-Studio development team (hereinafter referred to as "the team" or "we"), the official website of each development project, and affiliated self-hosted media accounts.
<ul>
<li>Please read all the contents of this User Agreement carefully. If you have any objections to any terms of this User Agreement after reading it, please immediately stop using any projects developed by the team.</li>
<li>If you are under 18 years old, please read and fully understand this agreement with the accompaniment of a legal guardian, and obtain the consent of the legal guardian before using any projects developed by the team.</li>
<li>If you have installed, used, or referenced any projects developed by the team during development, it means that you have actively read (read it completely) and fully agree to the terms listed in this User Agreement, that is, you have fully understood this Agreement and promised to accept the constraints of the agreement, legal statements, privacy policies, rules, norms, statements, notices, and other content related to any projects developed by the team.</li>
<li>This "User Agreement" is a user agreement and legal disclaimer entered into by the user (hereinafter referred to as "you") and any projects developed by the team. This agreement has legal effect on both the user and the team.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Nature of the Project, Services, and Definition of Responsibilities and Obligations</h2>
<ol>
<li>
<p>As all projects developed by the team are "open-source" and "non-business" in nature, the team can make full decisions at any time, including but not limited to changing the "User Agreement" and modifying any content within any projects developed by the team. If there are any changes to the "Terms" or the content of the works, we will post notices on the relevant project display website. The revised "Terms" will take effect automatically after they are published on the official website.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The development of this software is aimed at "learning development knowledge" and "accumulating development experience." All functions provided by all projects are "open-source" and "non-business" in nature. If you are dissatisfied with the security of any projects developed by the team, please uninstall/delete/stop using them immediately. If you continue to use them normally, it means that you approve of the security of any projects developed by the team.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Any "unexpected losses (including but not limited to: software, hardware, property, virtual items, etc.)", "contractual damage", "defamation", "copyright or intellectual property infringement," and the resulting losses and liabilities caused by the use of any content in any projects developed by the team are all "losses and liabilities" caused by the user's own use behavior of open-source software on the Internet. Based on the MIT license declared in all works at their open-source location (i.e., GitHub) and the content stipulated in this declaration, it should be deemed that the aforementioned "losses and liabilities" have no responsibility relationship with all the relevant developers of the projects.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During the user's use of any projects developed by the team, the team does not make any guarantees that do not occur under the following circumstances:</p>
<ul>
<li>The user cannot use or update normally due to network conditions, communication lines, and other technical reasons;</li>
<li>Negative results caused by using "plug-ins in this software developed by a third party," "modified versions of this software compiled by a third party," and "software compiled by reusing project code created by this development team."</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Users acknowledge that any project developed by our team requires active user trigger for any information upload, except for necessary upload reports or related information in passive receipt of software or other related projects.</p>
<ul>
<li>Users acknowledge that any project developed by our team fully respects and protects the "personal privacy rights" of all users. The project code is also fully open, and users do not have subjective reasons to accuse the development team or team members of "violation of privacy rights".</li>
<li>Any personal information of users will not be shared or transferred to third parties by any project developed by our team, unless with the user's prior authorization or the shared and transferred personal information has been de-identified and the third party cannot re-identify the natural person subject of such information.</li>
<li>Any project developed by our team contains links to other sites. When you visit third-party links, please read the user agreement and statement of the third-party site carefully. Our team is not responsible for the content, privacy terms, and usage agreements of third-party sites.</li>
<li>When using any project developed by our team, we cannot guarantee that the information you submit will be saved successfully. You need to properly store and keep the information you submit. Some projects developed by our team provide storage for "authorized data," but there are various force majeure factors in the storage process. Our team cannot promise to keep users' stored information indefinitely. Please back up your important information yourself.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<h1>Rights and Obligations</h1>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<p>Our team allows any individual or organization to conduct secondary development, functional modification, and reuse of our code for other projects without our team's authorization, for any project developed by our team. However, we reserve the right to pursue legal action against any infringement of our team's computer software copyright.</p>
<ul>
<li>Our team shall not be responsible for any consequences resulting from the public release of the contents of any project developed by our team (including but not limited to video production, articles with content of this software, uploading to download sites not designated by our development team, etc.) by any individual or organization using the project developed by our team.</li>
<li>Our team shall not be responsible for any consequences resulting from the use of "third-party subsidiary programs or additional code that can be used for any project developed by our team", "modified versions of any project developed by our team that have been compiled by third parties", or "software compiled using the project code created by our development team".</li>
<li>Based on the legal definitions of "computer software" and "documents" in Article 2 and Article 3 of the "Regulations on the Protection of Computer Software," DGP Studio reserves all computer software copyright for all of our development projects. This includes but is not limited to all information necessary to construct the project and all document data related to the project (i.e. program design specifications, flowcharts, user manuals, etc.), with the actual content subject to the "Computer Software Copyright Registration Certificate" for each project.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Any project developed by our team is only intended for lawful and compliant learning and research use and shall not be used for illegal activities.</p>
<ul>
<li>Our team is only a development team (not a legal entity composed of natural persons), and shall not be held responsible for any joint liability for any use of the software or any project developed by our team that results in any legal consequences.</li>
<li>If a user has already started using any project developed by our team, it means that they have agreed to the "Usage Agreement" and that our team has already fulfilled the notification requirements in Section 10 of this Usage Agreement.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Copyright of the developed projects.</p>
<ul>
<li>Our software development team holds the ownership of all trademarks in the software itself (excluding display content other than functional modules), all historical versions of the aforementioned works, and the surrounding websites. We also hold any related rights and interests regarding copyright.</li>
<li>All statistical data of any project developed by our team comes from users who submit data voluntarily. After the data is screened, it is displayed. Therefore, our team is not responsible for the accuracy of the data, and the data is not related to us.</li>
<li>During the use of any project developed by our team, there may be data that has original copyright. For these data, our team does not own their ownership. In order to avoid infringement, the user has the obligation to fully read and comply with the content of Section 10 of this Usage Agreement. The resources used in this software (including but not limited to fonts, images, and text) are from public information on the Internet. If infringement occurs, you can contact us at our GitHub to remove it.</li>
<li>Snap Hutao program and hut.ao website are not affiliated with miHoYo.</li>
<li>The copyright of Genshin Impact's game content and various materials and trademarks belongs to miHoYo.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>Other Terms</h2>
<ol start="9">
<li>
<p>Determination of "Non-Business Nature" of Projects Developed by the Team.</p>
<ul>
<li>Any project developed by the team has no business nature.</li>
<li>If individual or certain members of the development team, during their participation in the development of any project developed by the team, have entered into relationships with third-party users, including but not limited to gifts, exchanges, sales, etc., the resulting relationships are unrelated to the development team. This occurrence is not based on the fact that the team developed a related project, but rather on independent events that occurred at the location where the user entered into the aforementioned relationship on the Internet or in reality. The nature of this behavior should be determined based on the user terms of use at the Internet interaction location where the aforementioned relationship occurred, or in combination with specific behaviors that occurred in reality.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Any project (including websites) developed by the team is developed for the purpose of "learning development knowledge" and "accumulating development experience," and is only for learning and communication purposes. It is strictly prohibited to use it for commercial purposes. After downloading or viewing the learning materials, please delete all related information within 24 hours. If you ignore this requirement, the software development team is not responsible for "possible copyright disputes, infringement of intellectual property rights, and civil disputes."</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The establishment, effectiveness, performance, interpretation, and dispute resolution of this agreement shall be governed by the laws of the mainland of the People's Republic of China. If any provision of this agreement conflicts with the laws of the People's Republic of China and is invalid, these provisions will be reinterpreted as closely as possible to the original intent of this agreement. The other provisions of this agreement shall remain in full force and effect.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The place of signing this agreement is Liaohe Oilfield Mining Area, Panjin City, Liaoning Province, China. If a dispute arises in the performance of this agreement, the parties shall resolve it through consultation. If no agreement can be reached through consultation, the Liaohe People's Court shall have jurisdiction, and the appellant shall bear the costs of each stage immediately.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The titles (including subtitles) in this agreement are for convenience and reading only and do not affect the meaning or interpretation of any provisions of this agreement.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Both you and the development team are independent entities, and under no circumstances does this agreement constitute any express or implied guarantee or condition of the development team towards users. There is also no agency, partnership, joint venture, or employment relationship between the two parties.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In this "User Agreement and Legal Statement," the term "our party" or "the development team" (as distinguished from "you" or "the user") refers to the entire team of DGP-Studio Development Team, including each individual member.</p>
</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/tos.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hutao Database / Abyss Statistics</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-API.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/hutao-API.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Hutao Database / Abyss Statistics</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao&amp;apos;s built-in Hutao Database feature helps players archive and query Spiral Abyss challenge data, providing comprehensive statistical analysis and supporting players to upload data to the database.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao provides two main Spiral Abyss challenge statistics functions:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Schedule Details</strong>: Helps players save data for each period of the Spiral Abyss challenge for personal data review and statistics.</li>
<li><strong>Current Statistics</strong>: Displays Spiral Abyss data from all players who have uploaded it to the Hutao Database, providing players with a reference for character and team usage.
<ul>
<li>"Current Statistics" relies on the "Schedule Details" data submitted by players.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>

<h2>Viewing Abyss Data</h2>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Data Scope Limitations</p>
<p>All calculations are based on <strong>player data uploaded to the Hutao Database</strong> and may not represent the average data of all Genshin Impact players. It is for reference only.</p>
</div>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Data Refresh Cycle</p>
<ol>
<li>Spiral Abyss statistics data (character usage rate, character appearance rate, team appearance) are automatically updated at 4 AM on the 1st and 16th of each month in the time zone of the account's server.</li>
<li>If a user does not re-upload data within 30 days, their character ownership records will be cleared.
:::</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Click "Spiral Abyss" in the left menu bar and select the "Current Statistics" tab.</li>
<li>View Data:
<ul>
<li><strong>Character Usage Rate</strong>:
<ul>
<li>Formula: Character Usage Rate = Number of times a character appears in the current floor<sup class="footnote-ref"><a href="#footnote1">[1]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"></a></sup><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"> / Total number of records of players who own that character on that floor.</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"><strong>Character Appearance Rate</strong>:
</a><ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">Formula: Character Appearance Rate = Number of times a character appears in the current floor<sup class="footnote-ref"></sup></a><a href="#footnote2">[2]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2"> / Total number of records on the current floor.</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">
</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2"><strong>Character Ownership Rate</strong>:
</a><ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">
</a><li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref2">Formula: Character Ownership Rate<sup class="footnote-ref"></sup></a><a href="#footnote3">[3]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3"> = Number of players who own the character / Total number of players.</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
<li><strong>Team Appearance Count</strong>: Displays the ranking of team combinations by their number of appearances.</li>
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
</a></li><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
</a></ul><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3">
</a><h2><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref3"></a><a class="header-anchor" href="#uploading-spiral-abyss-data"><span>Uploading Spiral Abyss Data</span></a></h2>
<h3>Using the Snap Hutao Client</h3>
<div class="hint-container important">
<p class="hint-container-title">Snap Hutao Cloud Privilege Reward</p>
<p>After successfully submitting data for the first time, you will receive a 3-day "Snap Hutao Cloud Wish Record Backup Service" privilege as a reward (even if you have not cleared Floor 12).</p>
</div>
</div>
<ol>
<li>Click "Spiral Abyss" in the left menu bar.</li>
<li>Click "Refresh Data" in the upper right corner to ensure Snap Hutao has obtained the latest personal Spiral Abyss data.</li>
<li>Click the "Upload Data" button to submit the data.</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Uploading may take a few seconds. A success message will be displayed when complete.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Using a Browser</h3>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Info</p>
<p>This method does not apply to HoYoLAB.</p>
</div>
<ol>
<li>Open the <a href="/upload-abyss-data.js">JavaScript script</a> link and copy the code.</li>
<li>Create a new bookmark in your browser:
<ul>
<li>Enter a suitable name.</li>
<li>Paste the copied code into the bookmark URL.
<img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01p0KOqU1g6dvfDQO6e_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="add-bookmark" loading="lazy"></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Open MiYouShe and wait for the page to load, then click the bookmark.</li>
<li>Confirm the upload prompt to complete the upload.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Data Sharing</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao jointly maintains the Hutao Database with other developers. Users can view Spiral Abyss statistics and upload data in multiple applications. Currently, collaborating applications include:</p>
<div class="vp-card-container">
</div>
<hr class="footnotes-sep">
<section class="footnotes">
<ol class="footnotes-list">
<li id="footnote1" class="footnote-item"><p>If the same character appears multiple times within different chambers of the current floor, they are only counted once. <a href="#footnote-ref1" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
<li id="footnote2" class="footnote-item"><p>If the same character appears multiple times within different chambers of the current floor, they are only counted once. <a href="#footnote-ref2" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
<li id="footnote3" class="footnote-item"><p>Having the character counts as ownership, even if they did not appear in the Spiral Abyss. Uploading a record counts the player in the total player statistics. <a href="#footnote-ref3" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</section>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01ykD0CZ1g6e0sAQMn1_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiHoYo BBS Account Switching</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">MiHoYo BBS Account Switching</source>
      <description>The Multi-account Panel feature in Snap Hutao allows users to log in to multiple MiHoYo BBS accounts and switch between them freely, enabling the use of various functions within the tool with different accounts.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 04:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>Snap Hutao supports accounts from the mainland China version of the MiHoYo forum, <strong>MiYouShe</strong>, and the international version, <strong>HoYoLAB</strong>. HoYoLAB blocks network connections from mainland China by default, and Snap Hutao cannot bypass this restriction on its own.</p>
<ul>
<li>The account switching described in this document refers to <strong>MiYouShe / HoYoLAB accounts</strong> used for obtaining game data, not <strong>in-game Genshin Impact accounts</strong>.</li>
<li>Before using this feature, you need to log in to your account using the official MiYouShe app to initialize your MiYouShe functions.
<ul>
<li>If the account name logged into Snap Hutao is in the format "user_123456789", it may not have been initialized.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1797064093/O1CN01ZhnkRl1g6e0tz18y9_!!1797064093.png.png_.webp" alt="Multi-Account Management Example" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>You can find the account menu in the lower-left corner of the main program interface, above the settings button, to manage the MiYouShe accounts you've logged into Snap Hutao. In the pop-up panel, you can add MiYouShe or HoYoLAB accounts. The login methods are similar:</p>

<ul>
<li>After completing this, you can switch between logged-in MiYouShe accounts in the account management panel.
<ul>
<li>After adding a new MiYouShe account, you need to manually click on the newly logged-in account in the account switching function in the lower-left corner of the main interface to set it as the active account.</li>
<li>You can copy the corresponding account's Cookie or remove the account from Snap Hutao in the account management menu.</li>
<li>When the program is not running in administrator mode, you can drag and drop to sort the accounts.</li>
<li>After selecting a logged-in account, you can:
<ul>
<li>Click the "Refresh Cookie" button to update the currently stored Cookie.</li>
<li>Click the "Check-In" button to perform the MiHoYo forum check-in. For MiYouShe accounts, you need to resolve the risk control status first to successfully perform the check-in.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Security Tips</p>
<ul>
<li><code>SToken</code> is a security-sensitive Cookie field, and you <strong>should not</strong> store Cookies containing the <code>SToken</code> field on any cloud or other devices where data security cannot be guaranteed.</li>
<li>The Cookie obtained from Snap Hutao contains this field. Please carefully consider whether to provide the <code>SToken</code> field to the receiving party.</li>
<li><strong>When you log in to MiYouShe via password or Cookie in Snap Hutao, your data is only processed by the MiYouShe server and the local Snap Hutao, and does not pass through any third-party services, including the Snap Hutao server.</strong></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2>Common Issues</h2>
<h3>Why does the MiYouShe account login status often expire, and added accounts disappear?</h3>
<ul>
<li>We maintain the login status by storing the account's MiYouShe Cookie.</li>
<li>However, when a user <strong>logs out of the account</strong> in a browser or on another device, the Cookie maintaining the login status will <strong>expire</strong>.</li>
<li>This will cause the MiYouShe account in Snap Hutao to be automatically removed after startup.</li>
<li>This situation may also occur due to network connection issues preventing the validation of the Cookie. Therefore, please prioritize restarting Snap Hutao if this happens.</li>
<li>Since October 2022, MiYouShe has greatly increased the probability of an account being flagged as at risk. When an <a href="/en/advanced/exceptions.html#%E7%8A%B6%E6%80%811034-%E9%AA%8C%E8%AF%81%E5%A4%B1%E8%B4%A5" target="_blank">account is at risk</a>, the Cookie may also not be recognized as valid.</li>
<li>Since version 1.4.15, you can refresh the login status by refreshing the Cookie in the account panel.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Features</source>
      <description>In the Feature directory, you can find a comprehensive list of all the features currently available in Snap Hutao. You can refer to this directory to search for the corresponding documentation of each feature based on your specific needs.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 02:37:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statements</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Statements</source>
      <description>This page contains the toc of statements and announcements of Snap Hutao project.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 02:37:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The Snap Hutao project does not support, participate in, or cooperate with any Genshin Impact private servers or cheat projects. Snap Hutao was originally designed to provide users with a better gaming experience, and we oppose gaining PvP advantages by exploiting game mechanics through Snap Hutao or any other tools.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gacha System and Export Principles</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Gacha System and Export Principles</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao uses various methods to obtain users&amp;apos; login information and combines it with the Genshin Impact API to retrieve wish records.</description>
      <category>FAQ</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 01:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao's wish system has undergone a complete architectural redesign compared to Snap Genshin.</p>
<p>This article will explain the wish record mechanism of Genshin Impact and the technical principles behind the wish export feature of Snap Hutao.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html&amp;has_description=False" type="image/"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Description</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/project.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/project.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Project Description</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao is an open-source program project on GitHub, and we highly appreciate collaborations from the community to keep this project dynamic.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <category>Project</category>
      <category>Features</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div style="text-align:center">
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01eHCaOA1g6e2ZLa3PA_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="banner" loading="lazy">
<a href="https://trendshift.io/repositories/2009" target="_blank"><img src="https://trendshift.io/api/badge/repositories/2009" alt="DGP-Studio%2FSnap.Hutao | Trendshift" style="width: 250px; height: 55px;" width="250" height="55"></a></p>
</div>
<p>Snap Hutao is an open-source Genshin Impact toolkit under the MIT license, specifically designed for the modern Windows platform to enhance the gaming experience for desktop players. By integrating official resources with new features developed by the team, it offers a comprehensive and practical set of tools without relying on any mobile devices. Furthermore, it strictly adheres to non-destructive principles, ensuring the tool's safety by not modifying the game client.</p>
<p>The Snap Hutao project is packaged using the MSIX format. MSIX is a native Windows application packaging format that provides streamlined software installation, updates, and uninstallation. With its sandboxing technology, MSIX-packaged applications operate in isolated environments, preventing direct modifications to system resources and significantly improving system security and stability. Additionally, the MSIX format ensures no residual files or registry entries remain after uninstallation, maintaining system cleanliness. These advantages make MSIX a powerful tool for both developers and users for managing software, providing a smooth, secure, and clean software experience.</p>
<h2>Genshin Impact Desktop Issues Solved by Snap Hutao</h2>
<p>|           Feature            | Mobile                                | Desktop                             | Snap Hutao Solution                                                                        |
| :</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01mpzxPR1g6e22IjFMh_!!1797064093.png" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achievement Management</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/achievements.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/achievements.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Achievement Management</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao provides Genshin Impact achievement management, allowing you to browse and manage the status of all achievements. Use the powerful filtering system to easily search for specific achievements.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Snap Hutao offers comprehensive Genshin Impact achievement management, allowing you to browse and manage the status of all achievements. Users can quickly locate achievements through various filtering methods, optimizing the management experience.</p>
<!-- more -->
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01fApvim1g6e0xyGQvS_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="Achievement Management Interface" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>When using it for the first time, follow the prompts and click the "Create New Archive" button to create an achievement archive and name it. After creating the first archive, users can create separate achievement archives for different accounts by clicking the "Create New Archive" button in the upper right corner.</p>
<h2>Achievement Filtering</h2>
<p>Snap Hutao supports various flexible achievement filtering methods:</p>
<ul>
<li>Click the hidden menu in the upper right corner and select the <code>Only Commission Achievements</code> option to filter out hidden achievements that need to be completed through daily commissions.</li>
<li>Enter a version number (e.g., <code>5.3</code>) in the search box to find achievements from the corresponding version.</li>
<li>Enter the name of a related monster (e.g., <code>Pyro Hypostasis</code>) to quickly locate related achievements.</li>
<li>Enter part of an achievement name (e.g., <code>four winds</code>) to perform a fuzzy search.</li>
<li>Enter the full achievement number (e.g., <code>84575</code>) to precisely find the target achievement.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Achievement Import </h2>
<p>Snap Hutao supports importing achievement data through the <a href="https://uigf.org/en/standards/uiaf.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">UIAF Uniform Interchangeable Achievement Format</a>.</p>
<ul>
<li>Users can import data from <strong>third-party achievement export tools</strong> via URL protocol or clipboard.</li>
<li>Click the "Import" button in the hidden menu in the upper right corner of the achievement page, and select "Import from UIAF File" to load achievement data in the UIAF data format.</li>
</ul>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>If you have multiple versions of Snap Hutao installed (such as the Alpha version and the official version), you need to change the default application for the <code>URL:hutao</code> link. You can find the <code>URL:hutao</code> entry in "Windows Settings - Apps - Default apps - Choose default apps by protocol" and click the icon to change it.</p>
</div>
<h2>Achievement Export </h2>
<p>Click the "Export" button in the hidden menu in the upper right corner of the achievement page. After selecting the directory and setting the file name, the achievement data will be exported in UIAF format and saved to the specified location.</p>
<h2>Delete Archive</h2>
<p>Users can delete the current achievement archive by using the "Delete Current Archive" option in the hidden menu in the upper right corner.</p>
<h2>Recommended Achievement Recognition Tools</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/HolographicHat/YaeAchievement" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">YaeAchievement</a> </li>
<li><a href="https://cocogoat.work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Coconut Sheep cocogoat</a> </li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1797064093/O1CN01fApvim1g6e0xyGQvS_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wish History</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/features/wish-export.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/features/wish-export.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Wish History</source>
      <description>The Wish Export feature allows players to freely export their current wish data from their game accounts and permanently store and back it up locally, enabling long-term data accumulation for tracking and analyzing wish data.</description>
      <category>Feature</category>
      <category>Tutorial</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The gacha system is one of the core gameplay elements in Genshin Impact. Whether for commemorative or show-off purposes, or for seriously planning your pulls, analyzing historical gacha data is crucial. However, Genshin Impact only provides one year of wish history, which isn't enough for long-term players (<s>though they do track how many of Timmie's pigeons you've eliminated in a year</s>).</p>
<p>Therefore, the Wish Export feature of Snap Hutao was created to help players transfer their wish data locally for permanent storage and long-term analysis.</p>
<p>For the technical principles of exporting Genshin Impact wish records, please refer to <a href="/en/advanced/Gacha-system-and-export-principal.html" target="_blank"><strong>Gacha System and Export Principles</strong></a>.</p>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01otuXYg1g6e0wnNwX2_!!1797064093.png_.webp" alt="Wish Export" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>As shown above, Snap Hutao's Wish Export feature helps users clearly track and analyze their gacha data, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Total number of wishes</li>
<li>Current pity count</li>
<li>Number and percentage of weapons and characters obtained by different rarities</li>
<li>Number of wishes per 5-star pull and pity status</li>
</ul>
<p>Additionally, <strong>Snap Hutao Cloud users can access gacha prediction data calculated by the cloud servers</strong>.</p>
<div class="hint-container note">
<p class="hint-container-title">Delay in Genshin Impact Wish Records</p>
<p>Snap Hutao's data source is the miHoYo server. Therefore, recently made wishes may not be immediately available.
When you see the latest records in the in-game wish history, the corresponding statistics can be obtained in Snap Hutao.</p>
</div>
<h2>Fetch Wish Data</h2>
<h3>SToken Refresh </h3>
<div class="hint-container info">
<p class="hint-container-title">Hint</p>
<ul>
<li>A logged-in MiYouShe account is required to use the SToken refresh method. Please refer to the <a href="/en/features/mhy-account-switch.html" target="_blank">MiYouShe Account Switching</a> document to log in to your account in Snap Hutao.</li>
<li>The SToken refresh method does not currently support the Global server (HoYoLAB).</li>
</ul>
</div>
<ol>
<li>Ensure that the MiYouShe account from which you want to retrieve records is logged in to Snap Hutao.</li>
<li>Go to the "Wish History" page in the left-hand menu bar.</li>
<li>Click the "Refresh" button in the upper-right corner and select "SToken Refresh."</li>
<li>Wait for the process to complete, and then you can view the latest wish records.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Web Cache Refresh </h3>
<ol>
<li>Launch Genshin Impact and enter the game, then open the in-game wish history.</li>
<li>In Snap Hutao, go to the "Wish History" page in the left menu, click the "Refresh" button in the upper-right corner, and select "Web Cache Refresh."</li>
</ol>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">If the web cache refresh function malfunctions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Click on "Settings-Storage Space" in the bottom-left menu of the program.</li>
<li>Execute the "Delete In-Game Web Cache" operation.</li>
<li>Reopen the wish history in the game.</li>
<li>Try refreshing the wish records again.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<h3>Manual URL Input </h3>
<ol>
<li>If you have obtained the wish history URL from another tool, select "Manual URL Input" and follow the prompts.</li>
<li>Please note that the URL <strong>has a time limit</strong>, so complete the operation as soon as possible.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Full Refresh Mode</h3>
<ul>
<li>By default, Snap Hutao will stop importing after matching existing local records to avoid duplicates.</li>
<li>If you wish to fully retrieve all historical records from the Genshin Impact server, select "Full Refresh" before starting the refresh process.</li>
</ul>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Not selecting full refresh</strong> will not cause wish data loss.</li>
<li><strong>Selecting full refresh</strong> will not cause duplicate data imports.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2>Import UIGF Wish Data </h2>
<p>Snap Hutao supports importing wish records in <code>UIGF data format</code><sup class="footnote-ref"><a href="#footnote1">[1]</a><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"></a></sup><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">. Follow these steps to import:</a></p><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1">
<ol>
<li>Export the UIGF data file from another tool.</li>
<li>In Snap Hutao, click "Settings-Wish History-Migration-Import."</li>
<li>Select the <code>UIGF Json</code> data file in the file selector that appears.</li>
<li>Confirm the data and complete the import.</li>
</ol>
<div class="hint-container warning">
<p class="hint-container-title">Upgrading Old UIGF Files</p>
<p>If the wish record version is too old, click "Settings-Wish History-Migration-Upgrade Older UIGF Files", complete the upgrade and then import.</p>
</div>
</a><h2><a class="footnote-anchor" id="footnote-ref1"></a><a class="header-anchor" href="#export-uigf-wish-data"><span>Export UIGF Wish Data </span></a></h2>
<p>Snap Hutao supports exporting wish records to a Json file in <code>UIGF data format</code>. Follow these steps to export:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to "Settings" in the left-hand menu bar.</li>
<li>Find the "Wish History-Migration" section and click the "Export" button.</li>
<li>Select the account whose data you need to export.</li>
<li>Choose a file save location in the pop-up window, and click "Export" to complete the operation.</li>
</ol>
<div class="hint-container tip">
<p class="hint-container-title">Tips</p>
<p>You can export wish records for multiple accounts to a single file without performing separate operations for each one.</p>
</div>
<h2>Wish Record Cloud Sync</h2>
<blockquote>
<p>Cloud sync is based on a Snap Hutao Cloud account. You must <a href="/en/features/hutao-settings.html#snap-hutao-account" target="_blank">register and log in to a Snap Hutao account</a> to use it.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li><strong>Upload</strong>: In the "Wish History" interface, select the archive to be synced, click the "Snap Hutao Cloud" button, and then select "Upload Current Archive".</li>
<li><strong>Download</strong>: Click the "Snap Hutao Cloud" button and then click the download button on the right side of the archive corresponding to the UID to complete synchronization.</li>
<li><strong>Delete</strong>: Click the "Snap Hutao Cloud" button and then click the delete button on the right side of the archive corresponding to the UID to remove data from the cloud.</li>
</ul>
<hr class="footnotes-sep">
<section class="footnotes">
<ol class="footnotes-list">
<li id="footnote1" class="footnote-item"><p>UIGF (Unified Interchangeable Genshin Data Format) is provided by <a href="https://uigf.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">UIGF-Org</a>. <a href="#footnote-ref1" class="footnote-backref">â†©ï¸Ž</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</section>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1797064093/O1CN01otuXYg1g6e0wnNwX2_!!1797064093.png_.webp" type="image/webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submitting a Bug Report</title>
      <link>https://hut.ao/en/statements/bug-report.html</link>
      <guid>https://hut.ao/en/statements/bug-report.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hut.ao/en/rss.xml">Submitting a Bug Report</source>
      <description>Snap Hutao is an open-source program released on GitHub. We also utilize the GitHub Issues feature to collect feedback and address any issues. You can submit problem reports through GitHub Issues.</description>
      <category>Announcement</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you encounter a reproducible issue or one that you cannot fix yourself while using Snap Hutao, you can inform the developers by submitting a bug report.</p>
<p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1797064093/O1CN01jXBMbe1g6du15k9kx_!!1797064093.jpg_.webp" alt="suggestion" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2>Before Submitting an Issue</h2>
<p>Before creating a new Issue, please complete the following checklist:</p>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-0" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-0"> Ensure you are using the latest version of the Snap Hutao client.</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-1" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-1"> Use the search function to look for your issue and check the <a href="/en/advanced/known-issue.html" target="_blank">Known Issues</a> document.</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-2" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-2"> Search the project's Issue page to see if there are any existing issues that are the same or similar.</label></li>
</ul>
<p>If you still cannot find a solution after completing the above steps, you can create a new Issue on GitHub.</p>
<h2>How to Submit an Issue</h2>
<h3>Preparation Before Submitting an Issue</h3>
<p>When submitting an Issue, please make sure to provide the following information:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><strong>Device Information</strong></p>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-3" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-3"> Your device ID.</label></li>
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-4" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-4"> Your operating system version.</label></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Issue Description</strong></p>
<ul class="task-list-container">
<li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" id="task-item-5" disabled="disabled"><label class="task-list-item-label" for="task-item-5"> Describe your issue in detail so that the developers can reproduce the problem based on your description.</label>
<ul>
<li>How was the issue triggered?</li>
<li>What kind of error messages were displayed by the program or the operating system?</li>
<li>What troubleshooting steps have you tried, and what were the results?</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Program Crash Information</strong></p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>If your issue involves a program crash, please look for <code>.NET errors</code> related to Snap Hutao in the Windows Event Viewer and attach the detailed content in your Issue.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Submit the Issue</h3>
<ul>
<li>Go to the <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues/new/choose" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GitHub submission page</a>.</li>
<li>Fill in the content according to the template and submit.</li>
</ul>
<p>If you are not sure what a good issue looks like, please refer to some <a href="https://github.com/DGP-Studio/Snap.Hutao/issues?q=is%3Aissue%20label%3A%E4%BC%98%E8%B4%A8%E9%97%AE%E9%A2%98" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">high-quality issues</a>.</p>
<h2>Remote Debugging</h2>
<p>When developers cannot reproduce certain issues on their own devices, they may need to perform remote debugging to locate the problem. If you agree to participate in remote debugging, a designated administrator will add you as a friend via QQ/Discord and invite you to a remote assistance group for communication.</p>
<p><strong>The computer participating in remote debugging must meet the following conditions:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>At least 15GB of free hard drive space.</li>
<li>Sufficient network traffic to support the debugging operations.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Preparation Before Debugging</h3>
<ol>
<li>Perform steps <code>1~3</code> in <a href="/en/development/contribute.html" target="_blank">Contribute Code - Setting Up Snap Hutao Project</a>.</li>
<li>Download and install the <a href="https://uuyc.163.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Netease UU</a> remote tool or <a href="https://parsec.app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Parsec</a>.</li>
</ol>
<p>Remote debugging will help us solve problems more quickly. Thank you for your support!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://opengraph.snapgenshin.cn/generate?url=https://hut.ao/en/statements/bug-report.html" type="image/"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>